Yes, but it
has to be in the light.
I know, I'll move it back.
Put your hand away.
Daddy, Daddy,
the lamp is in the...
We were all there.
Help.
Anybody?
They're dead because of you.
Now look at us.
Don't touch that.
Get up. Come on, don't have
time for this shit already.
Okay.
Uh, this is a waste of time,
so I'll see you
back in New York.
If they let your drunk
ass back on the plane.
Hey, where you going?
Come back.
Devin, wait.
Hey, wait.
-Oh, fuck, ah!
-Yo, bro!
We made it.
Now we just gotta
make it to the top.
I'm not going up there with you,
-you obsessed asshole.
-Hey.
Hey. Are you kidding me?
If you ever touch this
again, I swear to God.
Who's the dude?
Me? I'm nobody.
He's my dealer.
You don't know me
and I don't know you.
Fuck this shit.
I'm not going up that
stupid mountain with you.
You're coming with me.
It'll help us both.
How the hell is this
gonna help us, man?
Tell me here.
Why does it have to be up there?
Hey, you wanna make
a couple extra bucks?
Doing what?
Yeah, doing what?
Ride with me in the cable
car to the top of the mountain.
How much?
5,000 kroner.
Five thou...
You never offered me
any money for this.
You don't have enough kroner.
Oh, I have enough.
I'll show you.
I'll show you kroner.
So you really want
to get up there?
That's why I'm here with him.
But you'll go even without him?
Damn right, I'll go without him.
Fine, he's all yours.
It ain't like you
had all your life
to get your shit together, Dad.
Kaapo?
Kaapo.
I'll try tell you everything.
Bro, I really don't care.
This changed so much.
Why did it change?
How would I know?
I'm from Finland.
Okay, I'm gonna get you in here.
Take you up.
And whoever's up there
will take care of you.
Hey, take it easy with him.
You coming in or not?
This is insane, Dad, fuck.
Hey, how long is it
at the top, Kaapo?
I'm not a fucking
Norwegian tour guide.
I should know.
But, we never made it.
Wait, we who?
Dude, please stop.
'Close Encounters' is
not my favorite movie.
-Hi.
-And there it is.
-Devin Robins.
-Would you stop?
Sorry, I don't speak Norwegian.
-What are you talking about?
-Would you shut up?
Sorry.
'Close Encounters'
is your favorite movie.
Mine is 'Dawn of the Dead'
and yours is 'Mad Max.'
That's the order
of things, right?
-It's not, it's not my...
-That's our lot in life.
It's not my favorite movie.
Well, what is it then?
-Well?
-'The Wizard of Oz.'
What? What are
you a five old girl?
Tell me, were those
scary flying monkeys real?
You don't have to
like it. I like it.
Yeah, maybe you shouldn't
have told us that.
What a world, what a world.
Look at that.
Whoa, oh that, looks safe.
-Look at that.
-Alright, come on.
Let's do this before our parents
start wondering where we are.
Syd, how much do you think
they know about the fire?
Who?
Our parents, dumb-ass.
How much sunlight
do you think we got?
Can we make it up
there and back in time?
Every time we bring up the
fire, you change the subject.
Doesn't matter. Just drop it.
Whatever, alright?
Whatever is right. I'm
not a fucking shrink.
Is it okay if we talk
about something else?
Remember when we went
to Space Mountain?
Yeah, but this is gonna be real.
Alright, come on. Let's
just do this already.
Hey, do you speak English?
You know the language.
You get English.
It depends.
You do?
He speaks English.
Could you take us up to the
top of the mountain, please?
Cafe up there burned
down a few years ago,
so go find a movie
on TV or something.
You missed all the cute
waitresses and pretty tourists,
but I'm married now,
so who gives a shit.
I give a shit.
They have big tits.
-Big juicy tits.
-Oh my God, oh.
For you, they had hot
chocolate and warm snacks.
Warm snatch. You
hear that, Devin?
He didn't say
that. He said snacks.
Have you ever
banged a hot tourist
-in the cable ground?
-Oh my God.
You don't have
to answer that, mister.
You do.
Every day.
Yeah, you Norwegians got
that Viking blood in you.
They let their sons freeze,
instead of crawling
into their mommy's beds.
I don't crawl
into my mommy's bed.
-He does, he does.
-Alright, stop.
We're wasting time.
Can you take us up there?
Shouldn't you be in school?
Are you boys playing hooky?
Me? I don't pay hookers.
But if you're asking
why we ain't in school,
ask fire starter here.
-Why don't you shut up?
-No.
Where are your parents?
My mom and his
dad are at the chateau.
Listen to this guy. Chateau.
They're at the sucky
lodge, boozing it up.
-Oh fuck. That's gnarly.
-Whoa.
How'd you do that?
Benefits of coal mining.
Come back tomorrow, okay?
What?
My wife's cooking
my favorite tonight,
so, homemade meatballs and the
best sauce you've ever tasted.
Are you kidding me?
Dude, take us up there.
I'm sorry, boys.
Jamie, Jamie Raft.
Øyvind Bjerck.
Øyvind Jerk, I love it.
-Bjerck.
-Jerk.
Syd, Syd Baker.
-Hi, Syd.
-Hi.
-Dude, what are you?
-What the?
-Charlie Chan.
-What the fuck?
What did I just watch?
Nice to see you,
Øyvind, Devin Robins.
Fantastic, okay.
-Are you kidding me?
-Enjoy.
We're never gonna
be in Norway again.
Never.
If you saw my wife, you
would understand.
Come on, guys,
we should go anyway.
-Oh God, come on.
-Such bullshit.
Okay, let me take
a picture of you
and you can bullshit
your friends
you went to the top, okay?
Come on, stand in front
of the gondola.
I don't bullshit though,
that's not...
-Fuck sakes.
-Oh, okay.
So with this camera.
Don't be funny.
Just stand in front of gondola.
Okay, what?
- The what-
- It's a cable,
it's a cable car.
Gondola.
-Gondwallah.
-Okay, smile.
You're at the top,
it's been fantastic.
One, two, three, cheese.
-Ah, ah.
-Oh.
-What are you doing?
-You're heavy.
The worst smile I've ever seen.
-You're fucking heavy.
-We're not happy.
-Here you are.
-You could have just taken
us up. It'd be way better.
I wish I could.
This country fucking sucks, man.
I tell you, I don't know
how The Clash managed
to play in Norway.
I was at that show.
Huh, whom? You?
Yeah, me.
-Oh yeah.
-No way.
You like The Clash?
-Fucking love The Clash.
-Yeah.
I've got the buttons
and everything.
Okay then, come on, guys.
Yes.
-You were actually there?
-Yeah.
That's so cool.
-I did it.
-I said don't touch it.
-That's his job.
-But I did it.
So now we can go, come on.
-Now we can get in.
-Oh yeah.
Come on, come on.
This is so cool.
Guys what do you
think he's saying?
-I don't know.
-Guys look.
This is CB radio.
Does it work?
Probably not.
Hey, don't touch that.
Is this even working?
Øyvind, um, we decided to
give you this picture.
-So, you can stand there.
-No we didn't.
Thank you, you can stand
there, let's get ready.
Come on.
You're the one missing
out on not having it.
This is so cool.
Bye, bye mister.
Does this thing go any faster?
Nope, it's not a roller coaster.
Um, my parents are probably...
If you could just
chill out. It's fine.
How is this thing moving?
I'm just a babysitter
for tourists like you.
Did you hear that?
He's got his hands free
to squeeze on big titties.
Look, ma, no hands.
Come on, guys.
Oh, come on.
Sorry Øyvind, my friends
are so immature.
That's alright, I like titties.
Oh, that's...
Can we go up there?
Roof?
-Yeah.
-Sure.
Yeah.
Yeah, you wanna
just stand on the...
- Yeah, yeah,
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Gonna surf on the wagon,
yeah, huh, huh, huh?
Of course not.
You'll die.
-Oh.
-But...
Please, we'll be really...
Lemme take a picture.
-Lemme take a picture.
-You wanna take a picture?
Yeah.
Okay. Try to take
a decent one at least.
You guys could look scared.
Doesn't look authentic.
Do you think we can
get a picture with you?
-Yeah.
-So we can
kind of prove that
we were in Norway?
-Sure, come on.
-Yeah.
-Okay, you're in the front.
-Smile.
Øyvind, smile.
You're ruining the picture.
Oh, the flash, man.
Hey, guys.
Ready for this?
♪ ...and battle come down
♪ London calling
to the underworld ♪
♪ Come out of the cupboard
-♪ Ya' boys and girls.
-Excuse me, that's mine.
I know.
We paid for
that, give it him back.
Can I please have that back?
This is illegal.
Give it him back.
Oh, hang on, oh, hang on.
♪ London calling, now
don't look at us ♪
♪ Phony Beatlemania has
bitten the dust ♪
♪ London calling, see
we ain't got no swing ♪
♪ Except for the ring of
that truncheon thing ♪
♪ The Ice Age is comin',
the sun's zoomin' in ♪
♪ Meltdown expected, the
wheat is growin' thin ♪
♪ Engines stop runnin',
but I have no fear ♪
♪ Cause London is drownin' and I
live by the river ♪
♪ London calling to
the imitation zone ♪
♪ Forget it, brother,
you can go it alone ♪
♪ London calling to
the zombies of death ♪
♪ Quit holdin' out and
draw another breath ♪
♪ London calling and I
don't wanna shout ♪
♪ But while we were talking,
I saw you noddin' out ♪
♪ London calling, see
we ain't got no highs ♪
♪ 'Cept for that one
with the yellowy eyes ♪
♪ The Ice Age is comin',
the sun's zoomin' in ♪
♪ Engines stop runnin',
the wheat is growin' thin ♪
♪ A nuclear error,
but I have no fear ♪
♪ 'Cause London is drowning,
I, I live by the river ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
You
okay? Are you okay?
Okay, what the
fuck just happened?
-What the fuck?
-You okay?
Oh.
-It's okay, it's okay.
-Øy.
-Øyvind.
-Relax, it's okay.
Was that meant to happen?
Hello, Andreas.
Hello, hello, lo, lo, lo.
Shut the fuck up,
you fucking idiot.
-Well?
-Øyvind, what was it?
No one home.
That's alright.
That's okay.
Hey, relax,
-relax, relax, relax.
-What do you mean?
Well?
What? No.
Hello, hello, lo, lo, lo.
-I swear to God, shut up.
-Shut the fuck up.
Oy, Øyvind,
you can't take us down?
It's okay.
Øyvind.
Move, move, move, move.
Okay, okay.
-Oh, come on.
-Øyvind.
Øyvind?
Oh my God.
Mister Øyvind!
Oh, what is that?
What is it?
Okay, what the fuck?
Someone tell me what
the fuck just happened.
Oh.
Oh, fuck, man.
Øyvind? Shit.
Is he dead?
Jesus, please don't be dead.
I don't hear nothing.
Oh.
Oh my.
What the fuck is that?
Is that heartburn?
Are you fucking nuts?
What kind of
heartburn does that?
Why are you doing that?
You sure you
know what you're doing?
I saw a guy on the subway
have a heart attack
and somebody started
pumping on his chest.
That's CPR.
I was supposed to learn that
in Boy Scouts, but I quit.
You guys said it was corny.
Anything?
He's dead?
Øyvind's dead.
You should have
done mouth to mouth, man.
No way.
Hey, hey.
What?
I don't, I don't
see any car lights.
Do you see any?
No.
If it was a blackout,
there should still
be car lights.
Yeah.
Jamie, do you see any lights?
Jamie?
You know I
only got one good eye.
What do you see, Syd?
That sound could have been
some kind of evacuation siren.
Evacuation for what?
I don't know.
Maybe an avalanche.
No, that's sound
came from up there.
It could have been bouncing off
the mountains from below.
What if it was some kind
of warning or something?
Are there missiles flying?
Russian nukes?
We're near Russia, right?
Right?
Is that what's happening?
What if World War 3 started
and we're up here
safe in the mountains?
What's that bomb called
that saves the building
but kills the people.
That's a neutron bomb.
-Yeah.
I don't know. Maybe.
I've never been up here before.
Devin, people know
we're up here, okay?
You guys' mom and dad, remember?
I can guarantee you there's
not a chance in hell
that they'd ever
leave us up here.
Help.
Anybody?
-His eyes are still open.
-We're in the cable car.
Jamie, close his eyes.
-Wait, why do I gotta do it?
-You already touched him.
Yeah, but I didn't
know he was dead yet.
-Help us.
-Ugh.
Help!
We're so screwed.
I don't even see any planes.
Can someone close
Mr. Øyvind's eyes, please?
Go on, Jamie.
You're always going on
about how tough you are.
It's your time to shine.
Unless that's bullshit too.
You guys are bunch of pussies.
Okay, Syd, you do one eye
and I'll do the other, okay?
No.
That's a good
idea and close his mouth.
Yeah, I'm not, I'm not
touching him, alright?
I'm not touching him.
He's taking up a lot of room.
And what if he starts to rot?
Why are you making
our situation worse?
Parents are coming.
I'm just saying, we might
have to get rid of Øyvind.
Have you guys lost your minds?
What if he's some
kind of evidence.
Evidence of what Devin?
We've done nothing wrong.
Evidence of whatever the
hell's going on up here,
like, like a clue.
Do you know what kind
of trouble we'd be in
if you shove a
Norwegian out of a door?
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
You heard this guy. Trouble.
You don't think this
is trouble already?
Guys, I just
thought of something.
I don't wanna jinx
us or anything,
but I'm gonna say
it anyway, okay?
What?
What if we were stuck
up here for a long time?
Can't believe this is happening.
And we have to eat him?
His meat ain't right.
I don't care if he's
cooked on the inside.
I am not eating Øyvind.
A nice guy, but he
didn't die right.
Hey, you know that,
the book 'Alive?'
They did it in
that book 'Alive.'
Okay, that's what really
happened in real life, Jamie.
Yeah, I know it really happened.
-We're just scaring ourselves.
-Okay.
They'll send another
cable car or helicopter.
We will just hop right into it.
And until then...
Use your bandana.
Put it, put it across
like both eyes.
Okay.
Have you finished?
Hold your horses.
-Oh, fuck.
-Hold on.
Devin, you can look now.
Well, what's the plan, guys?
What plans can we make?
We're sitting ducks up here.
Well, well, for
one, we're losing heat
and it's gonna get a
lot colder up here.
This whole trip's been a
bad idea since the start.
Holy shit.
-Guys, look what I found in here.
-What?
Whoa.
That's awesome.
Ah, hang them up here.
Maybe our parents will
see us up here with these.
You guys are lucky to
have a parent out here.
By the time we're
back on the ground,
my dad will have
heard about this.
But your brother will
see it on the news first.
Holy shit.
You guys'll be
brothers soon enough.
What? Why?
I'm right, right, Devin, right?
I don't know, maybe.
Maybe, what?
What are you talking about?
Are you serious?
What, you don't think your dad
likes Devin's mom that way?
What? No, I, you mean?
But that's Devin's mom.
We agreed, no, moms.
I hate to be the one
to break it to you,
but I don't think your
dad agreed to no moms.
Devin, look me in the eye.
Is your mom banging my dad?
Why'd you have to
say it like that?
Are they sharing a room?
They're not sharing a room.
They have separate rooms.
You don't want me
to be your brother?
No, no, no, I'm not saying that.
We're kinda like
brothers already.
You know, all of us, kind of,
but let's not jump the gun here.
We don't really know
what they're up to.
Uh, I know what they're up to.
Come on.
Give it a rest, okay?
What?
Don't fuck around, man.
He just breathed.
Get the fuck outta here.
I saw his headband suck
into his nostrils and mouth.
Oh my God.
Well, what do you see?
I don't see nothing.
Go closer.
No fucking way.
I can't, I can't.
-Stop, stop.
-What the fuck are you doing?
Get in you fucking idiot.
-Devin.
-Stop, stop, don't do it.
We're gonna handle
whatever happens together.
Get the fuck away from the door.
You're fucking nuts, man.
No, that's nuts.
You guys done fucking around?
-Yeah, we're done.
-We got a situation here.
Yeah, we're done, okay.
Speak for yourself.
Did he just move?
If he moved, this thing
can do a lot of damage.
Well, what do you think?
We have to have eyes
on him at all times.
Count me out.
Oh, this is so
fucking weird, man.
No, yeah, no shit, Sherlock.
Fuck.
Are you guys thinking
what I'm thinking?
Don't say it.
-How long does it take?
-Don't say it, dude.
-Until someone turns into...
-Don't say it.
A zombie?
Great.
There's no such
thing as zombies.
Well, if we're talking
'Night of The Living Dead'...
There's no such
thing as zombies.
We don't know that.
Syd, your dad said he saw
a ghost when he was a kid.
-Yeah.
-Ghosts aren't zombies.
It's still the unliving.
How long's he been dead?
We only just got up here.
Well, in that case, who bit him?
No, he didn't have to get bit.
In 'Night of The Living
Dead' it was because a satellite
-had way too much radiation.
-Look, look.
Swear to God, he breathed.
We're in Norway, they don't do
-zombie films here.
-Oh my God.
They only have Vikings and
good looking women, that's it.
Fuck me, man, look.
-What?
-He's breathing.
You fucking around?
No, I'm not fucking around.
Go look. Go look.
-What?
-Go fucking look.
-Take a...
-Get the fuck off, both of you.
-Take a closer look.
-Get the fuck off me, man.
I don't wanna go fucking closer.
He's literally a dead guy.
Go fucking closer.
It's just a draft,
Devin, you idiot.
-Oh.
-Jesus.
You and you zombies, Jamie.
Well, there is still time.
We could be up here for a while.
Someone put his bandana
back on his face over his chin.
Okay.
Okay, I think we can
relax for a minute.
And just like that you think,
you think everything's okay?
We, we still have a
dead body with us.
I'm too young for this shit.
We'll let the grown-ups
deal with that.
Stop saying grown-ups already.
You sound like a baby.
Oh, Devin, Syd's giving
me the crazy look.
We're gonna lose a shit load
of heat when I take a piss.
You're gonna need to
open both those doors
to get my big dick through.
You know what I'm saying?
Oh, fuck, fucking asshole,
look what you made me do.
Ah, you're
gonna smell like that,
what's his name in
the computer lab?
No, I'm not. Shut up.
That guy was, you know, twice
as clever as all of us.
At least Øyvind is on ice,
and he won't stink up the place.
Shut up.
Stop looking at him.
I'm not, I'm not looking at him.
I don't, I don't
wanna look at him.
It's not a movie, you guys.
We are just a
bunch of kids, okay?
We're gonna get
rescued. Stop it.
You, you just, you just
walked over a dead guy.
You can't do that.
And?
That has to be a no-no
in somebody's book.
A no-no and grown-ups,
God, I'm a fucking
babysitter out here.
Just walk back over him.
What? No fucking way.
I didn't even know
I stepped over him.
You'd do the same if
you walked under a ladder.
Come on. Just do it.
That's a load of shit, Syd.
Where'd you ever hear that?
My dad said it.
And if I remember
correctly, you believed him
when he said he saw
a ghost as a kid.
Yeah, Syd, your dad's a
hillbilly from the backwoods.
And your dad was probably
born in the back of a sweatshop.
No one gives a shit.
Walk backwards over him.
Devin, where was your dad born?
In a potato sack on a steamship?
You're not funny.
Oh and you don't think
me walking backward
over a dead guy is funny?
Why? Why do you
wanna jinx us, hmm?
Why do you wanna be a jerk?
-Just walk right over him.
-You don't think
we jinxed already?
What have we got so far, huh?
Let's think.
For one, we got a dead
guy, a nuclear holocaust,
and we're stuck up
here and gonna die
from starvation or a
cloud of radiation.
Radiation?
Yeah, you should be happy
we're gonna go out as skinheads.
Stop coming up with
ways for us to die.
Why don't you use your
squirrel brain
and help us get out of here?
How does that sound?
-Devin?
-What?
How high up do you think we are?
I don't know, 12 stories.
Oh, that's a lot of guts.
Oh, well, I could jump
that, I could jump at any day.
No, I'm not saying
you got guts or balls.
Devin, I was thinking
that's a lot of guts
we're gonna need to climb down.
What?
What are you talking about?
His guts, numbnuts.
We could pull out his guts
and shimmy on down out of here.
My God.
What did Mr. Perry say, Devin?
In biology, intestines
are how long?
He didn't say
there were 12 stories long.
If you think of something
better, let me know.
Maybe I will.
Why does none of
this shit make sense?
It's so, ugh, God.
We have to connect the dots.
We're in the wrong
place at the wrong time.
There's your dots.
Okay, which moron
thought it was a good idea
to light all the glow
sticks at once, huh?
Jamie, we have a
couple more, right?
I don't know, go check.
Well, do you mind going?
You guys are both useless.
Ugh.
Devin.
Whoa.
So, Syd, how, how
many more do you have?
I'll go to church every Sunday
if you get me out of
here in one piece.
Syd! Syd!
What are you gonna do?
Is that blood on the window?
Fucking, go on.
-Get close enough.
-Get off, get off me.
What the fuck?
What the fuck is going on?
Why were they doing that?
Birds don't do that.
Someone tell me
what just happened.
Hopefully, if anything.
Oh my God. I have
to get outta here.
If you guys wanna
get outta here.
So weird.
Weird? Fucked up, man.
Yeah, it's fucked up, alright?
Devin, what was that?
That was like the birds, right?
Oh my God.
Have you ever heard
of anything like that?
Is that normal?
Birds do that, right?
I dunno.
Well, they just did.
It's one thing
after a fucking another, man.
There has to be an explanation.
For, for that noise.
For shit exploding
around us, for that?
Devin, I really appreciate
your mom inviting me,
but fuck this shit, I am
never leaving home again.
Got that right.
Yeah, I'm with you on that one.
Fuck Norwegian pizza, man.
It's pretty bad.
Yeah, fuck Norwegian pizza.
I don't even care if we starve.
-Yeah, it's shit, shit yeah.
-Trash.
Yeah.
But I bet Øyvind
doesn't taste any better.
That's funny.
No, it's not.
I do feel pretty bad for Øyvind.
Oh my God.
I need that.
-Gimme that.
-It's mine.
-Get off.
-Get the fuck off.
-Let go.
-Gimme that.
-Get off, let go, mine.
You guys are disgusting.
Ah, it's so fucking cold.
Devin put his pants on.
No way.
You gotta wear something, man.
You're gonna freeze to death.
Hey, Dev.
Look, if, if, if,
if you, if you die,
and me and Jamie get
rescued, you know
how bad it's gonna
make us look, huh?
I don't care how it
makes you look like.
Devin, come on.
Just put his pants on.
Come on.
Put that on.
-Devin, put it on.
-I'm not putting it on.
Nice, gimme the money.
Hey, that's mine.
You don't need this.
You asshole.
Devin, come on. You
gotta wear the pants.
Put his pants on.
Oh geez.
Devin, make sure you don't
put your mouth on this part.
Mm.
It'll warm you up.
Yeah, for like two seconds.
Ugh.
Oh.
Good to the last drop.
Scotch.
Can I get a sip, please?
Please, Devin, just take a sip.
I'm okay. No thanks.
Devin, just have
a bit. Come on.
Lemme get a sip, please.
Just come on. Take a sip, man.
-I'm okay.
-Just give it.
Hey, douche bag.
Idiot.
-Oh.
-Devin, please.
Come on, man.
Look, maybe it'll help
you connect the dots.
My mom will have a drink
when she gets stuck writing.
She says it helps
clear the cobwebs.
But your mom's in
rehab in California.
I didn't say drink
the whole bottle.
He clearly doesn't want any.
Come on. I swear
to God, Devin.
You've got like two choices.
Either you take a sip,
or you put his pants on.
Those are from a dead body.
You want my pants?
You are not getting my pants.
Now put them on.
Mm, mm.
I'll take a, I'll take
a sip, I'll take a sip.
Take a sip.
There you go.
But, come on.
You don't do it like a shot of
cheap tequila like Syd.
It's Scotch.
You gotta sip it.
It's like swallowing Listerine.
But, you're warmed up, right?
What is this shit, Jamie,
why are you ignoring me?
Here.
-You idiot.
-Fuck you, Jamie.
Fuck you.
Stop doing that.
What do you think we got?
V.D. or something?
You know what?
What?
My mom would want me
to put on his pants.
See, that's using your noodle.
-You alright there?
-Ooh.
How about one of those smokes?
Sorry.
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Devin?
Come on. Lemme get a drag.
Dude.
We got a whole pack.
Smoke 'em if you got 'em.
Ah?
Deader than disco,
Devin, don't worry.
I was thinking.
For warmth?
Just to be on the safe
side so he doesn't come back.
They burn zombies.
Oh, for crying out loud.
You don't think we're gonna gag
on like burning flesh in here?
Like I said, if
you got an idea...
Huh?
Wicked. Gimme it.
Wicked.
Put that, put that away.
Let me see.
Wait a second. It's
probably worth something too.
Maybe he has a family
that might want it.
Yeah, fuck that, Devin.
I'm sorry. It's mine.
Are you just gonna let him
take your shit like that?
I'll trade him a pack of smokes.
What am I gonna do with
a pack of cigarettes?
Take up smoking. I don't know.
Just keep the knife already.
Sounds like a deal to me.
At, at least gimme the vest.
It's not a vest, it's a sweater.
I can smell his breath.
Yeah, one of his last.
Fish and cigarettes.
I'm never gonna
get used to this.
What? His dead
breath or the Scotch?
You are making me regret.
Oh my God, guys, guys.
-Holy shit.
-Whoa, God.
Freaking awesome, man.
This reminds me of
this book I read.
Devin, shush.
No one cares.
Who cares?
Oh my God.
Come on, man. Gimme
a hand. Gimme a hand.
Jump up and put your
foot through here.
Devin, your pants.
On three.
One.
Two, three, go.
-You okay?
-It's like
-lifting an elephant.
-Yeah, okay.
Shut up.
I'm not even kidding.
You weigh like a ton.
Shut up.
I got it. I got it.
Oh, sorry.
I was just joking.
Come on, let's go.
Just be safe dude.
Give it a push.
-It's frozen.
-Come on, just do it.
There you go.
Come on. Go, go, go, go.
Come on, guys.
You gotta see this.
Woo.
-Jamie, get up.
-What?
Get, get up.
Get up? Why?
Get up. Look.
What the fuck?
Devin?
Oh, what's happening?
Look, Devin, get up.
Look at his head.
His eyes have been smashed in.
-Oh no.
-Who did that?
I mean, who smashed his head in
it ain't like his head
just exploded.
It's like someone was
trying to kill a zombie,
but they didn't know
what they were doing.
They didn't finish the job?
Who? Us?
Come on, man.
Who did it?
I didn't, I didn't do it.
Well, I didn't do it.
Pretty sure that's not
like my kind of thing.
You, you brought up
this zombie thing first.
And Devin's a scaredy-cat.
Can't even look at him.
But he does sleepwalk.
You guys think I'm
some kind of zombie
sleepwalking zombie killer?
Where'd that come from?
Oh shit.
A candy bar.
Whose is this?
Who are you guys?
How, how, how can you eat that
when there's a smashed
head right in front of you?
How are we supposed
to trust each other
when we got head smashers
and food hoarders among us,
and nobody's 'fessing up?
I'm cool. You don't
have to worry about me.
Or Øyvind anymore.
One of you guys has
gotta a screw loose.
But that ain't saying much.
Could have been you.
If I did it, I
wouldn't have done it
with everyone sleeping.
Fuck, fuck yeah you would've.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Who did what or anything?
It doesn't matter anymore?
Yeah right.
Okay, whoever, whoever,
whoever did it, just say it.
It's okay. Just admit it.
I'm gonna sleep
with one eye open.
What are you doing?
We don't have any
more glow sticks.
I don't know about you, guys,
but I'm not gonna
freeze to death.
You gonna light a fire?
Yeah.
My head hurts.
Why does your head hurt?
Is it the Scotch?
Is it like a side effect?
Like one of those symptoms?
It's your first hangover.
How long is it gonna last?
We'll see.
Don't tell my mom
that I've been drinking.
You know what?
Let's get rid of old
Øyvind here.
Norwegian's ain't
sentimental anyway.
They're almost Germans.
Are they?
I say, I say fuck em.
Okay.
Fuck.
Except, except for Øyvind.
For leaving, leaving us
out in the cold
up here with a dead
fucking body, huh?
Bastard.
You know what?
We should sue him.
Your dad better sue
the shit out of them
when we get back down.
Yeah, he is gonna
sue the shit out of them.
Not cool.
So, we all agree
we're gonna do this?
Lemme get a sip first.
Really?
That a boy.
He was, Øyvind was going
home to his wife, right?
She's gotta be wondering
where he is, huh?
They gotta know
something's wrong up here.
How could she not call
the cops to come looking?
Because shit has hit the fan.
Somebody should say
something before we do this.
Wanna say something?
Oh God.
You think, is this his daughter?
Who, who knows?
Sorry, Øyvind.
Thank you so much for
trying to get us up
to the top of the mountains.
I'm sorry.
Anybody else wanna
say something?
Thanks for the Scotch.
And, and for your clothes.
He, he, he'd understand, right?
Somebody put his wallet
in his hand or something,
so they can identify the body.
Okay, guys, let's do this.
Oh.
Glad, glad I was with you guys
for the first time I
touched a dead body.
Why?
Do you plan on touching
more dead bodies?
Okay, on three, we'll
slide Øyvind out the door
and let him go, okay?
Uh huh.
One, two, three.
He's fucking heavy.
Fuck.
Oh.
Holy shit.
Here's...
Here's to Øyvind.
One hell of a cable car dude.
What day is it?
It's Sunday.
I think it's Sunday.
Sunday?
I shouldn't be up
here getting drunk.
On Sunday morning,
I'm at home, eating pancakes
and watching 'Bugs Bunny.'
Let me ask you something.
Why is he always
dressing up like a lady?
Who?
Bugs Bunny.
He's in disguise.
Then why is he always
kissing guys on the lips?
He's just messing with
people's heads, breaking balls.
No, you don't break balls
giving Elmer Fudd a boner.
Elmer is all goo-goo eyes.
Yeah, and Bugs is a rabbit.
Elmer's popping a
boner over a rabbit.
I'm just saying...
Sunday mornings are,
I just thought it can
never be a bad one.
You know, eating pancakes
and watching 'Bugs Bunny.'
Yeah, I hear you on that.
That sounds better than
anything in the world.
Without question.
But Bugs is half-a-fag.
No fucking...
Shit.
-What the fuck is that?
-Those are flares.
We're saved!
Devin!
Lemme see.
You're okay.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Open the doors. Open the doors.
Help us!
-Dad! Dad!
-Mom!
-Help! Up here! Help!
-Dad!
We're in the cable car, Mom!
Are you okay?
-Mom!
-Dad!
We're safe!
Mom!
Okay, shut up, shut up, shut up.
We'll get you
down. Don't worry.
-I love you, guys. Mwah.
-Ugh.
Mwah.
Oh shit.
How are you gonna get us down?
Don't worry, don't worry.
Hey.
Shut up.
When can you get us down?
-Daddy!
-Mom!
-What's that sound?
-Mom.
No!
Aargh!
Why'd they come alone?
I don't know!
Come on.
My mom.
Oh my God.
What am I gonna do
about my mother?
I don't know.
Don't fucking look at me.
Well, you set it.
That's total bullshit, Syd.
I was right there.
We were all there.
Well, who was it
that threw a lit box
of matches in the trash can?
You did.
Such bullshit.
Devin, did you really
think I'd burn it down?
Think I would burn
half a building?
The whole eighth floor caught
on fire because of you.
Me and Jamie are the
only ones who know.
I didn't do it.
Why are you talking
about this now?
We wouldn't even be here.
We're not supposed
to be in Norway.
We're supposed to be
in school in March.
Do you think our parents
wanted to come here?
We're, we're
here because of you.
They're dead because of you.
Is that what's wrong with you?
You don't know this?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
You should, you should
have got help.
My mom, she started to talk
to your dad about
getting you to see somebody.
After your mom died but,
your dad thinks there's
nothing wrong with you.
My dad?
He...
He wouldn't even listen to her.
My mom.
Okay, we need to get outta here.
Why couldn't you
just ask for help?
What help?
I got help.
Even Devin.
Even Devin got help.
What help?
We go to therapy.
Yeah, I know that.
We're going because
our parents got divorced.
My mom died.
We know your mother died.
Everybody knows
your mother died.
But can we mention her?
We gotta fucking tiptoe
around for how long?
What about my mother?
His father?
My mom wanted me and
Jamie to talk to you.
That's why she invited you.
She thought getting away
from everything would help.
Every time, and I mean, every
time we mention the fire,
you just zone out, man.
I knew we should have told
her you set the fire.
Now look at us.
We're not supposed to be here.
It doesn't matter anymore
who knows now.
We're stick up
here and we're gonna die.
There is nobody out
there to help us.
I'm sorry.
Just stop saying that.
I didn't kill your parents.
What?
I said...
I didn't kill your parents.
You wanna stab me?
Go right ahead.
I don't care anymore.
Stop making excuses.
Stop doing it.
Sorry.
Okay?
There's not much more I
can do, but apologize.
You better shut up already.
You're not crying
for our parents anyway.
Okay, can I take out the glass?
Okay, just,
just stay still, yeah.
Mm.
Sorry.
Ah.
I know, I know I can't
undo any, any of this.
Or fix it.
And if, if you want to throw
me out, go right ahead.
See if I care.
I know, I know nobody
gives a shit about
what I think anymore anyway.
People know we're out here.
Right?
Well, Øyvind was talking
to somebody out there
before we went,
before we went up.
They've not given up on us,
so we can't give up on them.
Alright?
Pete and Carol, they, they,
they, they, they had flares.
Must have got them from somebody
and they must have told them
why they needed them.
Don't look at them.
I'm not.
I can't, I can't...
Just wondering how
deep the snow is.
Go ahead. D.O.A,
dead on arrival.
People survive jumping off
the Golden Gate Bridge
every now and then.
It's not impossible.
That's water.
If the snow is
really soft right now,
then it'll be like a 20
foot deep pillow.
The snow could freeze
over. Be a sheet of ice.
Syd, why don't
you just go already?
Wait a minute, can we draw
straws or something?
I'm not drawing
no fucking straws.
Just jump, Syd.
It's the least you could do.
My dad and Devin's mom
died trying to save us.
Like Devin said, we're only
here because of you, so jump.
Do you want me to jump?
Fine, I'll jump.
I don't fucking care.
I don't fucking care at all.
We're all dead anyway.
We're all gonna die.
Then do it.
We gotta get the fuck
out of this fucking hell hole
of a fucking nightmare.
A-fucking-men.
Or we could all jump.
We'd have to do it now.
Once, twice, three shoot, right?
Right?
Yeah.
Okay.
First one down, don't bolt.
Guide the other two down and
we'll get outta this
shithole together, alright?
Okay.
Alright.
I'm evens.
Here we go.
Alright, ready?
Once, twice, three, shoot.
Oh, shit.
Hey, that's mine. Evens.
Once, twice, threes, shoot.
Fuck.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Read it and
weep, Jamie. I win.
Devin, you're up.
I'm changing.
I'm not odds anymore.
-You can't do that.
-It's alright. Take Evens.
Here we go.
Once, twice, three, shoot.
Yes, I've won.
Okay, okay. Again, again, again.
Once, twice, three, shoot.
Nice. Come on. Come on.
Here we go.
Once, twice, three, shoot.
Dude, what are you doing?
You won.
It's alright. I wanted
to go first anyway.
That was just a bad idea.
You don't have to do it.
My mom would want
me to be strong.
I'm ready.
Devin Knievel.
Yeah right.
Sounds pretty fucking cool, man.
Ready?
Yeah, okay.
Grab him, grab him, grab him.
I got him.
Pull him, pull him in,
pull him in.
Jamie, pull him in.
The door.
Devin?
He didn't bite his tongue.
-Okay, what then?
-I don't know.
I don't know,
but he's breathing.
Okay, what else?
Fuck, he's got a big ass lump.
Okay, what does that mean?
That can't be good, right?
A big lump is
better than a concussion.
Oh, shit, man.
You're not meant to sleep
with one of those, right?
Fuck.
-What are we gonna do?
-I don't know.
I'm gonna jump, I'm
gonna jump right now, okay?
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna go get help if
I survive the drop, okay?
He was really gonna do it.
It would've been suicide.
He didn't care if he died.
Or maybe he's just
crazy like you.
This fucker probably bashed
in Øyvind's head as well.
That would make us a couple
of crazy kids, wouldn't it?
Look who's back.
Hey, dude.
You have seen better days, huh?
What? What ride is this?
Oh, the belt is on too tight.
I can't, can't feel my legs.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna be sick.
Hey, hey.
Everything's cool, dude.
You're with your best buds.
Snow cones in the winter?
I don't get it.
Those birds.
Those birds. Why? Why
did those birds do that?
What, what about Øyvind?
What happened to Øyvind?
I remember now.
My brother had this book.
Is this the book you
were talking about?
Did I finish it?
What book?
Writer said...
in 1982,
all this,
it'll trigger.
It's 1982 now.
What, what's wrong?
Power lines,
Earth's magnetic field,
the Aurora Borealis
to Northern Lights
colored light show
in the night sky
it's caused when the
activity of our sun
creates dark sun spots
that shoot out gigantic
electrically charged waves
of particles from its corona,
geomagnetic storms
traveling through space,
a solar wind echoing
out into the universe.
But this time is different,
it's stronger, more intense.
It's rare.
A perfect solar storm of
radiation taking on all things
run by man's electricity,
even batteries.
It's the alignment of
planets this time,
Earth and the nine planets
all lined up,
all lined up on one
side of the sun.
The strength of their
gravitational pull on our sun
has caused this,
their alignment.
It's rare.
A rare grand alignment.
I ain't never heard of
anything like this before.
They can't. The planets
can't just stay still?
They gotta move.
Must have moved, right?
This can't be like forever?
They must have moved.
They've moved.
They moved.
It's rare.
Jamie...
I gotta tell you something.
Remember that day...
when I punched you in the face,
on the field trip in
front of the girls?
I don't know what
I was thinking.
I don't know why I
said your mother.
But I'm sorry.
Syd, when we get off this ride,
you gotta tell my mom,
you gotta tell her you
wanna get help, Syd.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. I'm gonna, I'm
gonna get help, okay?
I'm gonna do it.
Are you guys crying?
My eyes froze shut.
Wish I could see that.
Jamie made me...
fucking scared with his...
zombie talk.
Fuck zombies.
Fuck 'Dawn of the Dead.'
Made me bash
Mr. Øyvind's head in.
He ain't coming back.
I'm sorry, guys.
You're a sick puppy.
You know that, Devin?
A sick puppy with a potty mouth.
Hey, hey Devin.
You know what we
are, what this is?
You said it yourself.
I, I don't remember.
Come on.
You just said...
you just said it.
I don't remember anything.
Okay, I'll give you guys a hint.
We are...
a rare...
Grand...
alignment.
There you go.
That's what we are.
Right here, right now.
The three of us.
What a world.
I'm sorry you lost
your, your friends, Dad.
I didn't lose 'em.
Never let 'em go.
Does, does mom know all this?
No, not all of it.
I thought, I thought
she named me Devin.
I tried um, really hard,
to get this out of me.
I needed you here for this.
I don't want you to
feel like you can't
talk to me about
stuff, anything.
I was, I got scared for you
when your mother
and I separated.
I saw myself in you
when my mother died.
And I really fucked
up after she died.
And now I see you doing
the same thing.
Do you know what I mean?
But it wasn't your fault.
These people sacrificed so
much for me and then they died.
We were at the wrong place
at the wrong time, you know?
They died and I got stuck there.
We made it, right?
You and I made it up here.
Yeah, kicking and screaming.
But we made it.
It's not gonna
happen again, is it?
The planet alignment thing?
I don't know.
What happened to your dude?
Who fucking cares?
What a world, what a world.
♪ If you ever
♪ Want to come and find me
♪ I'll be midair
♪ If no one else is there
♪ Just wait, the door's ajar
♪ Welcome home again
♪ You left something behind
♪ I think it's yours
♪ Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm
♪ I'll fall at your feet
♪ And on the ladder on
♪ Look behind you
♪ I've always been around
♪ Midair, hold tight
♪ But God, you're not alone
♪ You're home, please stay
♪ Don't you run away
♪ Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm
♪ Midair, half there
♪ Oh with you don't you care
♪ Midair, nowhere
♪ Don't close your
eyes, not now ♪
♪ The light shines in them
♪ The last thing that I'll see
♪ Stay here midair
♪ Between your life and me
♪ Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm