You can't do that in here.
Okay.
Who the fuck are you two?
Us?
We're...
Morning, baby. Let me look at that.
- See you, sweetheart.
- Bye, Mom.
Sammy. Fruit, please.
- Okie dokie.
- Brady, eat the protein.
I am good.
Clean your plate, please.
Hey, that's Dad's.
- Is he even home?
- Bye, Lasagna.
Hey, cut him some slack, okay?
Always.
Hold up.
- I love you.
- Okay, I love you.
- Hey, babe.
- My friends are here.
Okay, I'll... have a nice...
Hey, hon. I slept in the basement
so I wouldn't wake you.
Okay, where's Brady?
I want to hear about the game.
Well...
the other team was kind of,
you know, physical.
- Yeah?
- So, he...
I'll let him tell you.
Very busy day.
I've got three showings
and one confirmed sale. And...
Brady stole your coffee. You're gonna
have to make some more.
- Well, we had--
- Hutch, you're bleeding.
Alright, we should--
Damn it.
Hey! Hey, buddy!
- Hey, man.
- Bye, Mom.
- Yeah.
Have a great day!
Bye!
- Hey, guys.
- Hi, Sammy.
- Hi. Love your shoes.
- Hey, you g--
Thank you.
Yeah, I got it from the mall.
Are you going anywhere
this summer break?
Yeah, I'm going bowling.
I'm going to the lake with my family.
Hutch?
What's up, hon?
You know...
summer break's
in just a few days, and--
We should do something. As a family.
Yeah. I'll... I'll make a plan.
Today. I'll make a plan,
and I'll tell you tonight at dinner.
I'll make lasagna.
- Sure, Hutch.
- No, I can do it. I...
I have... I have
one assignment today.
But then tonight, you'll see,
the whole thing playing out--
What's going on?
Never mind.
There you are.
Looks like your day went long.
It was a bit more, a big bit more
than the prep said it would be.
The data card.
It was a straightforward
snatch, Hutch.
It started as
a straightforward snatch.
You guys having fun
at the convention?
Asshole.
We're not here
for the fucking convention.
Where's the card?
Oh, my.
Fuck!
Please! Someone help us!
We're in the--
Operator will assist you shortly--
Right. Straightforward snatch.
Yeah. Until the Corsicans
showed up with Uzis.
Wait. No. They had MP7s.
- Corsicans, huh?
- With MP7s.
Well, we always suspected
there might be another
interested party in the mix.
Only one?
- Brazilians.
- Yeah.
With machetes.
The sharp kind.
- Oh, my.
- Yeah. Oh, my.
Well, I'd say it was worth it,
because this checks out.
Which brings you 800 grand closer.
And how much more do I owe?
Thirty million, give or take.
Your next mission.
I can't.
Hutch, I'm trying to help you
pay off a debt.
One we very graciously
paid on your behalf
when you burnt
all the Russian's stack of money.
At the rate you're going, you'll have
paid off the Obshak by spring.
Gonna take a v-va...
I'm gonna take a break.
Good luck.
What do I need luck for?
You? Take a break?
This job is in your nature,
and nature always wins.
Wherever you go...
there you are.
Wild times await.
This summer, drive to Plummerville
smack dab in the middle of America
and join me, Wild Bill
for summer fun!
With the majestic midway.
Hey!
And to top it off, America's first
and finest water park!
You kids having summer fun?
Sure are, Mr. Wild Bill!
Slides for miles and miles!
Because Plummerville is...
Summerville!
So, come on back
to Wild Bill's again and again!
Again and again.
Yeah.
That commercial is really old.
Are you sure it's still a place?
Yeah, it's all there. I-I checked.
It's the hotel and the water park
the duck boats and the midway.
What's a duck boat?
It's... it's like a bus that floats.
It's a military vehicle.
Grandpa will love it.
We're bringing Grandpa?
Yeah, of course.
You know what?
I volunteer to stay home.
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
Yeah, Brady, listen.
This is gonna be the most fun...
What happened to your eye?
Somebody fouled me at the game.
What game?
The one you missed.
You're right.
We do need to spend
more time together
- as a family.
- Yeah.
This is one of those places you went
when you were a kid.
Okay, but that makes it sound like
I went to a lot of places, okay?
Dad took us on one vacation.
One. To Plummerville.
Listen...
in life, when times get tough
you need to have happy memories
to carry you through it.
I just want to show you guys
the place that made me happiest.
You know, make some memories for you.
Would you let me do that, please?
Well, hello, Lasagna.
Okay.
- Alright, Hutch. Sure.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- What?
Come on, kids!
It can be an adventure.
An adventure?
- Yeah.
- That's it.
Grandpa!
Hey, Dad.
You gotta put out the cigar.
Secondhand smoke.
What?
No such thing.
Let's do this!
Hutch, start the car.
- Here?
- Yeah.
I love you more today than yesterday
But not as much as tomorrow
There's a raffle!
Oldest waterpark?
Is that something
we want to advertise?
Yeah, well, it's historic.
Kids, you're in here.
We're sharing a room.
And where's Grandpa sleeping?
He's next door.
Hutch, I think
the kids are too old to share.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
We can all sleep in the old lodge.
Nah. Not gonna happen.
Just me then.
Fine. You can have my room.
- Thank you.
- Great.
And, Sammy, you've got this
all to yourself.
The honeymoon suite.
Oh, yeah!
That's what I'm talking about!
Look at that, huh?
Take it in.
Yeah.
This is where business gets done.
You don't like it?
No, I'm... I'm taking it in.
I smell cigars.
But I'm happy that you're happy.
And that we're all together.
It's gonna be great.
Water park time.
- Yeah, water park time.
- Water park time.
It's paradise.
It's like the tropics
mixed with Europe.
- Hello?
- Closed. Sorry.
What?
There's an incident. Waterpark's
closed for the rest of the day.
- For how long?
- Twenty-four hours.
Here's a coupon for hot dogs.
Come again. Sorry.
Lame. I'm out of here, kids.
Checking out the old lodge.
Hot dogs.
- Number 52's up.
- Can I get some more ketchup?
Larry, Dad's bringing the food.
Yo, what's up, Hutch?
Hey, it's the great
Mansell's family vacation, boys.
Wait till you see the lodge.
You'll see mosquitoes
bigger than this hot dog.
Something wrong, pal?
You got a problem?
I'm sorry. I was just thinking.
You know, it's not polite
to eyeball the law.
Sorry, officer.
It's sheriff.
Did I do something wrong?
I don't know.
Did you?
Hutch?
Everything's good, hon.
Okay.
Mansell?
Yeah. That's me.
- Hot dogs are in.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Fantastic.
- Enjoy.
- Thanks.
- Hey.
Worth the wait, and look what we got.
Coupon for the arcade.
It's how they get ya.
- Can I see it?
- Alright.
All four food groups in one place.
Thanks, Mom.
Here you go. You bet.
I wanted to talk to you about
that shiner you got in the game.
I didn't get it in the game.
Sorry, what's that?
I said I didn't get it in the game.
But you got fouled though, right?
Dad, can you just stop? Can I just...
Okay? Can I just play the game?
It's not a big deal, alright?
- Come and see this!
- I won, so...
- Hutch!
- That doesn't make it...
- Yeah.
- Come!
- Play the winner.
- Okay. I'll be right there.
We... we will talk
about this more later, okay?
- For sure.
- Yeah.
He's so cute.
Howdy, girls and boys
it's sizzling here in Summerville's
ultimate arcade
the one-stop entertainment
center and fun for all.
Do you guys want some tickets?
Sure.
Thanks.
- I have a bunch.
- Hey, Brady.
Why'd you get them all away?
I have plenty, dude.
Come on.
Look at us.
Decompressing like pros.
Yeah. We're getting there.
- Is that a badger?
- Yep.
- That one.
- Alright.
- Hey.
- Thanks.
Nerd.
You getting some Nerds
with your tickets, nerd?
- What's up?
- Tell me you're sorry.
- For what?
- For hitting on my girl.
You're giving her tickets, man.
What if I tell you to fuck off?
That count?
You know who I am?
Last chance.
Cool. What, are you gonna cry?
What? You don't...
you don't want another shiner
on your... your pretty
city boy face, do ya?
Hey.
Hey! Hey!
Fucking touch my sister's--
Let him go!
What are you doing, you punk?
Coming into my house
starting a fight?
Settle the fuck down!
- Hey.
- Dad... Dad.
- This piece of shit--
- Get out of here right now!
- What happened?
- Hey, is that your kid?
- Yeah.
- Well, he's starting shit.
He's not starting anything.
I have cameras all over this place.
If you don't get
your family outta here
you and I are gonna have a problem.
- Yeah, we are gonna have--
- Hey!
We're leaving.
- You hear me?
- Okay. Okay.
- Alright. Let's go.
- Yeah.
- Listen to your wife, old man.
- Alright.
No, Mom. I didn't do shit.
This guy did all of it!
- Dude, how's your arm?
- My badger.
Leave it.
Ouch.
- Brady, hold up. Hold up, sweetie.
- No, I just wanna...
I just wanna go.
Brady.
- What?
- I left my phone.
I'll be right back.
No, Hutch. Hutch, no.
No... no.
- Well, look who decided--
- Oh, shit!
Hey! Trying to be a hero, big man?
Someone call the cops!
How's that feel?
- Huh?!
- Hutch!
- God!
- Dad!
Sir, sir, we were attacked.
And I don't understand
why we are here.
I don't understand why
those bullies are not here.
Are we being charged with anything?
Okay, is your son prone to violence?
Is my... are you kidding me?
Ma'am.
I'm just trying to gather
some information.
- Can you tell me exactly--
- Sir, if we're not being charged
I'd rather not answer
any more of your questions.
Having a lawyer is definitely...
I understand protecting
your sister, Brady.
It's instinctual.
But there are other ways
to handle things.
You serious?
You tell me to stay cool,
but then you go and lose your shit?
Which I-I thought
was awesome, by the way.
- You know, the way that you--
- No. No, it wasn't.
I'm just saying.
You have to be better
than your old man.
Whatever.
Okay.
Let's go.
Get up.
Not you. Just Dad.
Sit your ass down.
You know who I am?
No, but the way you're sitting
behind the sheriff's desk
I'm guessing you're somebody.
Damn right I am.
Name's Wyatt Martin.
I run this town.
Well, I'm Hutch--
I already know who you are.
You're the tourist
who fucked up my son.
- I didn't--
- Shut the fuck up.
Your son was the kid at the arcade--
Shut the fuck up.
Well, your son may have
had something to do--
Your son has got an attitude problem.
I'm pretty sure I'm staring at--
My daddy built this town.
And he had a rule.
Tourists get a free pass.
You know why, right?
Bread and butter and all that.
But for this...
- Your son, Brady, right?
- Yeah.
Your son, Brady, messed up
my son's pitching arm.
I get it.
Do you?
Yeah, I get it.
I'll make my son apologize.
But you should watch
the security cam footage
because one of those guys
smacked my daughter.
And I lost it.
What would you've done?
Walk him out.
Brady.
Come on.
So, that's it then? We can go?
Do yourself a favor.
Keep going.
Get the boys together.
Didn't Wyatt say to leave 'em alone?
I don't give a fuck what Wyatt says.
Get rid of them.
Can you not?
What the hell, Hutch?
- On our first day?
- I'm sorry.
You just had to bring
that other side of you?
Brady's already aggressive
and do you know why?
It's because of you.
Because he is watching you.
And what you do.
Look, I lost it.
Alright? It's over.
What's in the work bag?
What?
The black bag, Hutch?
- You've been trying to hide it.
- Listen...
- Okay, so what's in it?
- I'm not here for...
I made a promise to you.
- Yeah.
- And I meant what I said.
Yeah, I remember that promise.
Wine?
It's not just any wine.
It's from Puglia.
Where we met.
And the year.
I'm sorry.
Where did you find this?
- eBay.
- eBay?
Yeah.
Wait, so you ordered it?
It took, like, six weeks.
You planned for this.
I knew who you were
the moment I met you.
I knew you were dangerous.
You were covered in blood.
Good times.
Crap, Mom.
You've got an eye.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, this is not a fair fight.
This is not a fair fight.
I'm on her side.
Sammy? Where'd she go?
Sammy? Sammy, wait for me.
Dad! Guess where I am?
You got me.
I warned you,
this is a wonderland. Off we go.
Ready?
Super cute!
Grandpa doesn't know
what he's missing.
Duck boats are super fun.
They're trustworthy,
but they don't...
Four tickets for the...
That's... that's not a duck boat.
Yeah. You see
the big duck on the top?
No, I told my son,
a duck boat is a military vehicle.
More than... more than one conflict.
I'm gonna... okay, four tickets.
One kid.
Yeah, here, honey, hand these out.
Really heavy duty. Mil-spec.
Yeah.
Single-handedly caused
our loss at Nam.
Hey, only a few seats left, folks.
Come aboard.
Hope you don't mind getting wet.
Yes.
Thank you.
- Sweetie, why don't you sit down?
- That's good. Thanks.
Yeah, Dad's right.
It's like a bus that floats.
It is like a bus that floats.
Where is Dad?
What? You're not coming?
Hon, I had too many churros
with my macchiato.
I'll see you at the park.
What?
Have fun!
Bye, Macchiato.
Well, eat better!
Looks like it's end of the line for--
Alright, let's get
this party started.
- Vest!
- Grab off my arm.
- Vest?
- I'm good.
- Excuse us.
- There you go.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Just head on up to the front.
Yeah, headphones
should be on the bench.
Find a seat in the back.
Just get comfortable.
You can stand if you want,
just hold on really tight.
And we'll get going in a minute.
Sit. Sit down.
And we're sailing away.
Okay, so I'll be your guide today
as we cruise along
the great Plummerville lakes.
And, folks, if you...
What's up, guys?
More than you know.
You were told to leave.
So, what are you still doing
in town, old man?
I'm here with my family.
Making memories.
He's making memories, huh?
There's no need for this.
This is all a big misunderstanding.
I'm here on vac--
Be cool!
Come on!
What the...
- Hey!
- Use your words.
What am I paying you for?
Fuck! He's right there!
That's right. My favorite,
personally, is the Bugger Rounder.
And, speaking...
Now no one gets the pole!
But I got a fucking knife!
You're dead, motherfucker!
Although calm, these waters
are home to our native giant bass.
Cool it, man, cool it!
Talk to me, okay?
Think of the children!
What?
Fuck!
You motherfucker--
That's what I'm fucking
talking about!
You said he was just
a fucking tourist!
Well, that's all
Abel fucking told me!
You're gonna pay us a lot more
fucking money now, Dann.
I lost a tooth!
Fuck that!
No! Shit!
Tell your boss
I'm on fucking vacation!
We went to the beach,
now we're gonna get some ice cream.
- What flavors? Yeah?
- Yeah! I want ice cream!
I want chocolate ice cream.
We're gonna get
some chocolate ice cream.
Come on. Let's go this way. Yeah?
Okay. I'm gonna get strawberry
ice cream. Yeah, and vanilla.
Hey, Harry. That wasn't a trumpet.
You were just being serenaded
by a shamisen, my brother.
You just got back from Osaka, right?
Yeah, and I master shit quickly.
What's up?
Hey, you remember Plummerville?
One of the happiest weeks of my life.
Yeah, mine too.
Yeah, I remember...
I remember seeing
the other kids and their parents
and thinking we were just like them.
Anyway, I came back here and...
Plummerville just isn't
as friendly as I remember it to be.
It's an old trade route.
Used since the bootlegging days.
Why you think Dad took us there
for a one and only family vacation?
Are you saying he was on a mission?
You got it, Hutchy-boy.
Oh, yeah.
The cops over there
they're in cahoots
with the big syndicate.
Hey, be careful with that.
- It's not my money.
- I'm sorry, boss.
- I didn't mean it.
- Fucking moron.
And he would not want a guy
like you sniffing around, bro.
How's it going?
Holy shit, this is a big shipment.
What's in the blinkin' thing?
The shit that's gonna land Lendina
on INTERPOL's Top Ten.
This is great.
You want more guys here, just in case
there's any more trouble?
Hey, don't cause any trouble
and there won't be any trouble.
Remember who's boss here.
Got it.
I gotta get my son.
Watch this shit and be cool.
Want me to take that?
Thanks.
Do you think Dad is eventually going
to grace us with his presence?
Or...
Wild animals!
Don't go too near.
That's a wild wolf dog.
Gotta stay locked up, that one.
Well, Mom, you saved animals
back when you met Dad, right?
Among other things, but...
You know, if you gain their trust
and you show them that
the world is a safe place for them--
- World that is safe?
- Yeah.
What world is that?
Okay, let's go find Dad for dinner.
You caught a tourist, I heard.
Did they put up much of a fight?
What's th-- I can't hear you.
Hey, turn that off!
Shut it off!
What are you, new?!
What... what was that?
He broke my teeth, man.
What about your teeth?
He crushed 'em, okay?
He... he jus... he beat everybody.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Talking about the guy, okay?
I don't think he's just a tourist!
- Yes?
- I've got a problem.
Of your own making, I sense.
Plummerville. You heard of it?
It's a back road.
Drugs, guns, viruses and worse
come down from Canada
and go on to points unknown.
Alright. Well, where does
the buck stop here?
There are layers.
Possibly an individual,
a unique individual, called Lendina.
Lendina.
- Guy in the white?
- Yes, ma'am.
- No, no. No new dealer.
- This requires a woman's touch.
I'm winning. On a roll here.
Congratulations.
Let's see how your luck goes.
Beautiful. I split.
Sure.
- Hit me.
- How's your trip been going so far?
Shut up and deal.
Plummerville is critical
to Lendina's larger empire.
Oh, shit.
It happens.
A lone wolf.
Operates unburdened
by any constraints at all.
You piss off the Russians,
they come to your house with guns.
Lendina and her squad will slay
your family on the front lawn
and force you to watch
if you disrupt
their situations any further.
Yes!
Pay me!
You're a winner.
Ma'am, I swear I knew nothing.
What's happening?!
Nobody cheats in my casino!
You'll want to
de-escalate the situation.
I mean, do you got
any intel, an address
or anything?
I'll give you a lead.
But hear me on this.
You're on your own, Hutch.
Killer, I'm so sorry
that you had to see that.
My little baby should never see
those terrible, terrible people.
What about them back there?
Leave no witnesses. Burn it down.
You got it.
Let's go for a walk.
That was fast. Did it hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Maybe this is too soon.
Dad, really, I'm fine.
My arm's feeling good.
Hold on.
Max, I have to take this damn call.
Won't be long.
What?
Well, that's no way
to treat your business partner.
Ex-partner.
This is my last shipment.
- Goodness.
- My father's debt is all paid up.
I can count.
This, you know, pays off
the last of our debt.
By my calculations,
the debt will never be paid off.
No.
That's bullshit and you know it.
Ain't nothing funny
about what I said.
Your father died
because he was distracted.
Are you distracted?
I'm not my dad.
It's over.
Well then, we'll see.
Well...
Hello?
Hey, Max! Where are you going?
Sheriff.
You can just call me Abel.
I need to make sure Wyatt
hasn't forgotten who he works for.
Take something that really
matters to him.
Got it.
Mom, it's your turn.
- Hey, Mom.
- Yes?
Is Dad in trouble again?
Why? Do you know something?
No, that's why... no.
I'm sure he'll be--
No, honey. Let me.
Hamburgers and s'mores
for dinner tonight!
- So nutritious.
- Yay!
Your dad's running late.
But come with me.
I promise you it's the way to go.
Sammy, come on. Help me pack up.
- You... you talked to Hutch?
- Talk later.
- Gotta move.
- Okay.
Walk in real smooth.
Keep everything room temp.
Yeah.
No escalating.
De-escalate.
Lead by example.
Hey, fellas. What a mix-up.
It's a big shipment,
but I guarantee you
we can do more next time.
Except those paintings are a bitch.
But you gotta see what's in here.
Here is the special thing
the boss lady asked for.
Wyatt's spoiled son.
Now, I want you to tell the boss
that I said it was a pleasure
to be of service. Okay?
You understand?
Or do I need to get
a fucking translator?
I need to get a fucking translator.
Hey, fellas.
What the fuck!
How did you get in here?
The door.
Is that gasoline?
You're quick.
Now, listen, I could torch this money
and it'd go up in a flash
and whatever's in those barrels
would go boom
and most of you wouldn't
make it out of here.
And those who do
will have to answer to Lendina.
I'm guessing this is all hers.
So then, what the fuck do you want?
Okay, well...
I want a break.
A break?
I just want a fucking break.
So, if I walk out of here,
you leave me and my family alone.
Because that's all I want.
To de-escalate this.
Are you fucking kidding me?
From the moment you've shown up
you've put my men in the fucking ER.
There's no way
you were just some family man.
De-escalate? Fuck you!
Plummerville was A-OK
before you showed up.
Wherever I go...
I could so easily kill you right now.
But...
You're lucky.
You catch me on a good day.
Go.
Get the fuck out of here.
Go before I change my mind.
Will you fucking pick him up?!
Jesus Christ!
Help, please!
Help me!
You're on my last fucking nerve!
I told you to get the fuck out--
Who the fuck is this guy?!
No... no!
Please, wait! Wait!
Okay, let's go.
Stop, motherfucker!
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
How much do we lose?
Everything. The cash, the chemicals.
The bio-case.
- No.
- All of it.
Wiped out all our men
and got away with Wyatt's son.
Who is this zealot?
Nothing about him is turning up.
There is one oddity.
He had a family with him.
My valuable shipment
was blown up by a man
who's a tourist
on a fucking family vacation?
Does nobody
play by the rules anymore?!
Jesus fucking Christ!
I don't know who the fuck you are
but you crossed the line, asshole.
Sheriff.
What do you know about this threat?
I don't know, okay?
But I sent you the pictures.
And they haven't checked
out of the hotel.
You might want to bring
some others, alright?
How... how many of your
I guess, soldiers can you bring
with you? Because he's--
Shut the fuck up. I'm on my way.
This guy's an idiot.
- Hey, son.
- Look who finally shows up.
Hey, Dad. Everybody good?
Everybody's doing great.
Your son swings an axe like a pro.
Dad.
- Sammy.
- Where were you?
Hey, Brady, that's Max.
I brought him here, so be cool.
We good?
Yeah.
Let's go outside.
How'd you get that shiner,
country boy? Kidding.
Are you stayin' for the night?
I would... I would love to stay
but I still got
some heavy lifting to do.
Oh, yeah. You're right about that.
Let's go, Sammy.
Come on.
You can light the fire.
Arm's length, Hutch.
You were supposed
to keep danger at arm's length!
I didn't mean to...
Hutch, you promised me.
You promised.
You broke your promise.
I don't have...
I don't have control over this.
I'm just realizing that
you should get away...
from me.
Becca.
Becca, I'm not asking.
You don't tell me what to do.
You were a lot of things.
But most of all, you're a dad.
And you're my guy.
So, go fix that shit.
Come on, Sean.
Answer your damn phone.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
You.
What the hell are you
still doing to my town?
Well, I could use your help.
No, no, no. Be cool.
I've got your son.
- He's okay.
- You mess with my son?
You're a dead man!
No, you don't understand.
He's totally safe, with some people--
What the fuck do you mean by safe?
From Lendina!
We want the same things.
You burned all of it?
Yep.
You burned the money?
And whatever was
in those chemical barrels
they... they exploded.
You burned all of it?
I-I saved your son.
Thanks.
She's pure fucking evil, man.
She killed my dad.
Used Abel to take my son.
Backstabbing son of a bitch.
This empire that
I inherited from my dad
came with a lot of debts.
Wild Bill.
He was a lot of fun,
but the man liked the bad odds.
And I'm still paying
for his mistakes.
Lendina has run this town
for two fucking generations.
I will not let my son
be forced into this.
I know what you mean.
So, what... what would she do
if she found out that
you burned her stash?
You burned it.
Okay, what would she do?
Okay, how... how do I put this?
She's eradicated
entire bloodlines for less.
She's absolutely bat shit crazy.
Vicious.
Where is she right now?
She's definitely on her way here.
Ma'am, it's time.
Hit it, motherfuckers!
Let's move!
My dad planned to fight Lendina.
She got to him first.
I'm not sure
if any of it still works.
I wouldn't.
Now we lead her to the most
dangerous place in Plummerville.
- Closed for repairs.
- Hey, we just got here.
I'm so sorry, folks,
but it's gotta be made safe.
- Here you go, you got free churros.
- Your website didn't say anything--
You're gonna get a free refund.
Let's go, let's go, now!
Must be hard
to say goodbye to this place, huh?
You know, when my dad
brought us here--
You kidding me? It's a curse.
Water park leaks like a motherfucker.
The funhouse is nothing
but headaches.
No kid wants exactly
what their dad built.
Really?
It's actually good to hear.
Who the fuck is that?
Harry?
You know, this place is much smaller
than I remember, man.
Oh, man!
This is my brother, Harry.
Wyatt Martin.
- Good to meet you.
- What are you doing here?
I sensed you was
having an existential crisis.
Okay, I want to talk to you.
Hey.
Yeah, good boy.
Yeah, go on, go on, go!
You know, Pops, remember that
you left us alone in that lodge
for two nights straight by ourselves.
And all we had to eat
was hot dogs and s'mores.
That's probably why I'm a vegan.
Well, you guys were safe.
Mostly.
Did you ever worry about us, though?
I mean, like,
about who we'd become.
You mean, like,
how you worry about Brady?
Yeah, I want him to be--
A better man than you.
- Yeah.
- And he will be.
Believe it or not
you guys are improvements on me.
Hey, listen.
- You know where you're headed?
- I got it.
Okay, you need any help up there?
Yeah, I got something else in mind.
Time's up!
They're in the water park.
Fun.
- What's that?
- Some sort of cabin.
We think his family is there.
Take a team and go there.
And Kartoush...
- Yes?
- Scorched earth.
No prisoners.
Bend it open
and put chocolate inside?
Okay, let's do that.
You know what you're doing?
- Yes, I do.
- Nice, capture.
- No, I can't...
- On the offense. Just jump here.
Kids?
I'm gonna go for a walk.
- Have fun.
- What?
You got this, Brady?
What if I just move mine?
Yeah.
- Be safe.
- That's a good one.
Okay, tie game?
- Yep.
- No, it's fine.
- It's a tie game.
- Okay, so...
Liking the new look.
Really suits you, Abel.
You kidnapping puto.
Cute.
You really lit a fuse
when you did that.
No.
I think you did that.
The moment you underestimated me.
See, I've been pushed around
for long enough.
So, from now on
I'm the fucking man.
And this is my fucking town.
So, give me your guns
walk in front of me, back to the car
and maybe I'll get you out of this.
Maybe.
What if we say no?
All hell breaks loose.
- Yeah, we'll take that.
- Yeah, we'll take that. Yeah.
What an ass pain he is.
- Take him out.
- Copy that.
Move in!
Move! Move! Move!
Move! Move!
Go! Go! Go!
Fuck him up!
What the fuck is this?
Oh, god!
Let's go!
Oh, shit!
Open fire!
Move.
Hey, fellas!
What the fuck?
You can't hide!
There he is! Ball pit!
Go, go!
Shoot!
Fuck him up!
Shit!
Hey, Wyatt. Meet me at the pool.
I'm on my way.
Come on, boys. Let's move!
Watch your six!
Hey, good boy.
Yeah, I owe you one.
Go. Run!
Get over there! Go!
Fucking-A!
I've got you now, motherfucker!
You're gonna die, old man!
You motherfucker.
Got eyes!
Huh? What the fuck?
- Hey, Hutch!
- Dad, cover me!
Dad!
Fuck you!
- There he is!
- Still not dead.
- Take him out!
- We got him!
Dad!
Whoever's in there, never leaves.
The Mansell family directives,
Eighth Principles:
in darkness, let fear
enhance your strength.
What the fuck?
Turn challenge into opportunity.
The fifth principle.
Hey. Hey, man. Don't do this.
I'm just doing my job, kid.
Max!
Protect Sammy!
Last man to challenge me
I took his head.
Peek-a-boo.
Don't bring the machete
to a fucking katana duel.
That's principle number one.
Please, don't kill me.
What's up, nephew?
Your father would be
proud of you, Brady.
- Wyatt.
- Hey.
I got shot in the fucking leg.
Fuck.
Alright. Just hold that on there.
Thanks.
- Alright. Loaded. Ready to Rock.
- Okay.
I'm gonna check on my dad.
Alright.
Dad!
Lendina?
Who sent ya?
Nobody.
I'm here with my family,
making memories.
What are you doing here?
I'm here for you.
You know, I like
this little empire of mine.
Operative or a family man,
it doesn't fucking matter.
Because what I don't like
is people who try to fuck up
my peace of mind.
But, you know, I'm just like that.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Mr. Making Memories.
What happened to
Mai Tais on the beach?
You just go
and leave a trail of destruction
everywhere you go.
Do you know how important
this town is for my business?
What the fuck are you thinking?
FBI, park ranger. Fuck.
You are a nobody.
And now, you're gonna
lose everything.
And do you wanna know why, buddy?
Because you fucked
with the wrong bitch.
Take him out. I'm bored with him.
No!
Motherfucker.
(Spanish) Damn it.
Lay down, fuck face.
You think you can get away with this?
You need a lesson, asshole.
Fuck your memories. Fuck your family.
And most of all, fuck you.
Die, fucker.
Fuck.
Who are you?
I'm his better half.
Becca!
Kill her.
Don't fuck with a mama bear.
Hutch!
You heard the boss. Kill her.
Fire in the fucking hole!
Crazy gringos!
Are they gonna be okay?
Yeah. Just another Mansells vacation.
We're not gonna ask again.
Who are you guys?
Us? We're...
We're married.
Yeah. We're married.
Yeah.
...Hutch and Rebecca Mansell...
Sir, I cannot do that.
There are bodies all over.
This is like a war zone. I...
I don't give a fuck...
Yes.
Yes, sir. I hear you.
Loud and clear. Sir, yes.
You're free to go.
Get the keys for the cuffs.
Hutch, after this vacation...
Yeah?
We need a vacation.
We did it!
We went to Plummerville.
And we came back in one piece.
Yes! Yes!
- Almost.
Now listen. One thing
that'll help us never forget that.
So, let's hear it for Sammy.
What... what was the idea
with this one?
Max and Wyatt!
We should call them some time.
Honey, I think
we cost them enough trouble.
I can't wait
for the next summer break.
You'll come with us, right, Grandpa?
- You got it, Sammy.
- I miss that ball pit.
Hey, look at that.
I don't even remember that.
- Did you take that?
- Yeah.
That's really good.
You could be a pro photographer.
Yeah, I know. I'm shocked.