A FIREBREAK IS A STRIP OF LAND
CLEARED OF TREES IN A FOREST…
OR ANYTHING, OR ANYONE,
THAT CAN STOP A WILDFIRE FROM SPREADING.
Hey! What's up?
- Can you hear me?
- Sounds familiar.
- A trip?
- I'll check my calendar.
- I changed it to Monday.
- I'll see if I can fit it in.
- I didn't go.
- I'll just leave!
FIREBREAK
- We're here. Come on.
- Let's go.
Dani, help your mom.
- Give me a hand, kids.
- You got everything, Lide?
- Here.
- My suitcase.
- Morning, Mara.
- Hi.
I took photos earlier,
so I won't get in your way.
- Okay.
- The furniture's great.
We could ask for 20 grand more.
Yeah, sure. Sounds good.
Here are your keys.
I'll pick them up when you're done.
- I'm Luis.
- Thanks.
- Mara's brother-in-law.
- Nice to meet you.
Don't worry. It'll sell fast.
It's a beautiful house.
Okay. All set.
- Race you!
- All right. I'm thirsty.
We need to pack.
You do it. It's your stuff.
I don't know how to use this.
We'll have one box for donations
and one for trash.
"Donations." Right.
- Don't throw the ball.
- Copycat!
If you don't want to play--
- I do.
- Then go play.
Dani, come help.
Mom, when are we going
for a walk in the woods?
Later. We have to clean up
and eat lunch first.
- Okay?
- All right. Promise?
Sure. Go on.
Dani, play with your cousin.
- Want them?
- Yeah, they belonged to my parents.
- My brother loved this one.
- Come on.
Mara, this is like new.
- You're not keeping it?
- No. I'm not a vest person.
You or Luis can have it.
Just keep it out of my sight.
You must've lost it.
You're it!
- Mara's going to regret this.
- You know how I feel about it.
We can't pretend he never existed.
Selling the house, tossing his clothes…
I mean, he was your brother.
She needs to face her grief,
not run from it.
I think that's exactly
what we're all trying to do here.
Aunt Mara!
- Check it out!
- Dani.
Then you look, Mom!
Delicious. I was starving.
Why are you selling this place? I love it.
- I wouldn't sell it.
- I love it too.
But this is where Dad died.
Lide.
That's not why we're selling it.
Lide, look at me.
We're selling it because
we're buying a beautiful place.
Really nice. By the beach.
- Next to ours.
- Exactly.
So we can spend our vacations together.
- Sounds nice.
- We've talked about this.
- But I like the woods.
- We'll come visit.
- Right, to pick mushrooms.
- Yeah.
If they're smooth and white
on the outside…
Those are edible.
Some are red with white spots. Those are…
Is that the neighbor?
- Those don't grow here.
- Hi, Mara.
Hi, Santiago.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Come in.
- Can I?
- Of course.
- Hello.
- Come sit.
- I'm good.
- Hi.
- I just ate, and I've got work to do.
The whole family's here.
- My brother-in-law, Luis.
- Hi.
- Gustavo's brother.
- We've met.
You haven't met his wife, Elena.
- Not in person.
- And Dani.
- Hi.
- My nephew.
- And Lide.
- Lide.
I brought something for Lide.
Can I give it to her?
- It's a butterfly.
- Of course. Go head.
Hi, Lide. I brought you something.
- It's from the forest.
- Right.
- What do you say, Lide?
- Thank you.
- It's nothing.
- So…
- I saw you packing up.
Right. We're selling the house.
We're leaving. Today's our last day.
- Right.
- So…
If you need help or anything…
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- Thanks. Really.
- Have a good one.
- All right, take care.
- You too.
- Bye, Santiago.
- Bye.
- Later.
See you.
He seems nice, huh?
Yeah.
We're not close,
but Gustavo hung out with him.
He saw us hauling boxes all morning.
- And now he offers to help?
- Luis…
When we drive off he'll be like,
"Need a hand, man?
Here I am, smelling like incense."
Is it snowing?
The wildfire has now burned
over 2,500 acres,
and firefighters are working
to contain it.
The prolonged, intense drought…
That's a lot of acres.
…has sped up how fast
the fire is spreading.
Unless the wind changes direction,
the fire is expected to be contained
by nightfall.
There is also hope that the firebreak,
created in late summer,
will keep the flames from spreading…
Firebreaks don't work.
That's all for now.
Now, over to our correspondent…
Let's pack up and go.
- Firebreaks don't work.
- But, Mom.
- We're not staying overnight, right?
- No.
- Dani and I will take the workshop.
- Are you sure?
- You take the bedrooms.
- No need to rush, but…
- It'll be fine.
- We'll go.
- We'll head out.
- Right.
I won't seal all the boxes.
- Let's go.
- We can come back another day.
- Why'd Uncle Gustavo carve so many bears?
- He really liked them.
Your uncle loved the mountains.
We used to come here all the time.
He was really sad when they disappeared.
Come on. We'll take these with us
and wrap them up later.
- Maybe this is fine, though.
- Dad.
- What?
- This is where he died?
That's right.
He wanted to spend his final hours here.
That's why we're here, just you and me.
So Aunt Mara doesn't have to be. Come on.
You take this one.
I'll wrap these up later.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
Yep? Okay.
We can toss this. Don't we have a bag?
- With more.
- No.
That's the last of it.
Let's throw this out.
This too.
Lide, do you have my Rubik's cube?
No. I wouldn't give it to you anyway.
- Let me see that.
- No. It's mine.
- I found it.
- Everything's yours.
- No.
- You always get your way.
- Where's my Rubik's cube?
- No idea.
You said you wouldn't give it back.
- Did not.
- Did too.
- Let me see.
- I said no!
- I found it!
- Let me see!
- You're so annoying!
- Then leave.
- This is my house.
- Not anymore, Lide.
Keep your binoculars.
I'm donating most of this.
Grab anything you want.
Mom, look what I found.
I'll fill my canteen, and we can head out.
We can't, honey. There's a fire.
We need to leave.
- We were supposed to say goodbye.
- We can't, sweetie.
- It's really dangerous.
- You said we could.
I know, but there's a fire.
Will the hut burn down?
It won't. The fire's far away.
But we need to pack up and go.
- Come on.
- I don't care about the fire.
We were supposed to go to the woods
and say goodbye together.
I know, but there's a fire.
- We were supposed to do it together!
- That's enough.
We were supposed to say goodbye together!
- There's a fire. Stop being ridiculous!
- I don't care!
I don't care if you don't care.
Go pack up your things.
- You liar!
- Go pack up your things!
- No!
- I'm not telling you again.
Go!
Don't throw things!
- Should I go talk to her?
- No.
She's making this so hard for me.
- Mara…
- What?
What is it?
These too?
STORAGE
You were together your whole lives.
Exactly.
And he still chose
not to fight until the end.
Not even for us.
- I'll do the kitchen.
- Yeah? Then I'll…
Dani, come help us.
Dani is a big help.
- Time to go.
- Is that everything?
- The car's loaded.
- All right.
You ready, Dani?
Dani, where's your cousin?
No idea.
- So that's it?
- Yeah, all set.
Lide, sweetie, we're leaving.
Lide.
Did I leave my jacket in there?
Not sure. Maybe in the bedroom?
- Dani, buckle up.
- That's Lide's seat.
I can't find Lide.
Dani, where's your cousin?
- No idea. She's around.
- Where?
How should I know?
- Luis…
- Coming.
Let me.
Lide?
She's not in there.
I bet she went to the hut.
- She's not in there?
- She's in the hut.
I told her not to go, but she still…
- I'll go get her.
- I'll come too.
- Call if she comes back.
- Okay.
Come on. Let's wait inside.
- Santi.
- Yeah?
- Have you seen Lide?
- Yeah.
- Where?
- In the hut. Just now.
- I knew it.
- You know there's a fire, right?
- Yeah, thanks.
- Yep.
No worries.
Lide.
Lide!
Mara, what's wrong?
Lide's not in the hut.
That's weird. She was just here.
- You sure?
- Yeah, just a minute ago.
- Inside?
- Yeah, right there.
Luis, call Elena.
Ask if Lide's at the house.
Yeah?
- Hey, hon. Is she with you?
- No.
- She's not here.
Lide!
Where is she, Luis?
- If she's not in the hut, where is she?
- No idea.
Lide!
Everything looks the same out here.
Luis, can you call Elena?
Maybe she got turned around.
No, she's not here.
Probably got lost in the woods.
- Lide, please, honey!
- I can't hear you. Can you hear me?
Lide!
Baby, please don't do this.
Don't do this to me.
Afternoon.
- Hello.
- Good afternoon.
Hello. I'm Sergeant Revuelta,
head of the Missing Persons Unit.
- Corporal Baranda.
- I'm her mother.
- I'm her husband's brother.
- And I'm his wife.
Right. So your daughter is 8?
Almost 9.
When did you notice she was missing?
- Just after lunch.
- Yeah.
What time?
- Around 3:00.
- Excuse me. Santiago!
- Can you come here?
- What was she wearing?
- For just a minute.
- A white top.
Yeah, a light blue jacket.
This is our neighbor.
Hi. Good afternoon.
He was the last person to see her
in a hut she'd built with her dad.
Is her father here?
No. My brother passed away.
I'm sorry.
You were the last person to see her?
- Yes.
- Did you talk to her?
- I did.
- About what?
- Nothing important.
- Nothing important?
Did you notice any strange behavior?
Was she anxious?
I did find it strange at first.
Because of the fire.
But she seemed calm,
and we talked for a bit.
I figured she could find her own way back,
and I left.
You didn't think it was odd
she was alone in the woods?
- No.
- What were you doing at the hut?
I work for the Department of Environment.
- I'm in charge of the firebreak.
- Sorry.
- Right.
- I also--
Sorry. This is Lide.
She's about four feet tall.
Has bangs, 8 years old…
Do you have a piece of her clothing?
An item for the search dogs?
- Sure.
- I'll go get it, okay? Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- It's okay.
- Get her pajamas.
- All right.
- Unwashed, please.
Her pajamas, Elena.
We're expediting our procedures
due to the fire in the area.
- Right.
- Yes.
Units are on the way.
We'll join the search.
She likely got turned around,
but she's probably close.
- Thank you.
- We've activated our evacuation protocol.
We need you
to leave this property and go home.
Sure. As soon as my daughter is found,
we'll go.
The fire is getting closer.
It's dangerous.
That's why I can't leave without her--
- We will keep you updated.
- Sir--
But we need you to evacuate
as soon as possible.
Excuse me, I--
The roads will be closed
within the next few hours.
I'm not evacuating
without my 8-year-old daughter.
Ma'am, I understand your distress--
- No, you don't.
- I do.
You don't understand.
I can't leave
without my 8-year-old daughter.
- It's an order.
- All right. Let's--
We have to follow protocol.
Given the circumstances--
- We'll leave.
- What's your--
- Sgt. Revuelta.
- Revuelta.
- I'm sorry. Don't worry.
- You'll keep looking for her?
- Evacuate the area.
- Yes.
- Understood?
- Got it.
We'll do everything we can
to find your daughter.
It's "Lide." You got that?
- Lide.
- We know.
Anything I can do?
You also need to evacuate.
You know the area and the protocol.
- Right.
- Someone will call you.
Don't worry. She's just anxious.
All right. Thank you.
Okay. Thanks.
Dani, go to Lide's room.
I'll be right there.
Don't worry.
I'm not leaving.
I don't care what they say.
I'm staying. You three go.
Luis, there's a fire.
Elena, it's dangerous.
It's far away.
We can stay a little longer.
It's okay. Really.
- Elena, Luis, there's a fire.
- No.
- It's okay.
- No. Mara.
She'll show up. They'll find her.
- Of course.
- It's fine.
- You three go.
- No.
They ordered us to--
- We're staying.
- Yeah.
We can't come back otherwise.
- They're closing the roads.
- Really?
The fire's still far away. We're staying.
- We're staying.
- Yeah. With you.
- Elena, are you sure?
- We're staying.
- We're not leaving you.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- We'll stick together.
Come on! Go!
Watch the line!
- More pressure!
- Come on!
Her name is Lide.
She's about four feet tall.
Group One, you're with Revuelta.
Group Two, with Castro. Three, with me.
Portillo, Group Four. Let's go!
- Move!
- Let's go!
Lide!
Dani.
I want to go look for her too.
We can't, son.
That's a job for the police.
We have to stay here.
- Lide will find her way back.
- Are you sure?
Yeah.
I am. Just have faith.
Lide!
Check that area over there.
Around the hut.
Section one, clear.
Lide, honey!
Lide!
There's too much smoke. The wind shifted.
There!
There's so much smoke.
Smoke isn't fire.
I'm keeping an eye on the fire.
Look, it's really far away.
They'll find Lide,
and we'll be home before you know it.
- Lide!
- Let's go!
Section one, clear. Moving west.
- Visibility's terrible.
- Come on!
The dogs can't keep going.
We're waiting on HQ!
We'll keep you updated, okay?
I shouldn't have yelled at her.
I hate this house.
I hate this stupid forest.
It wants to take everything from me. Why?
That night Gus spent
in the woods alone changed him.
He was never the same. He…
- He gave up.
- No, Mara.
- There was a treatment.
- No.
There was a treatment.
But he didn't even try.
It was a trial.
He didn't want to be a guinea pig.
That's your opinion.
- And it was his.
- Honey.
Damn it.
If he were here,
he'd know exactly what to do.
Hello?
- Wha--
- Is it the police?
Excuse-- Sorry. I can't hear you.
What was that?
No.
- What's up?
- Here.
- What's wrong?
- Hello?
Sorry, can you repeat that?
What did you say?
That's ridiculous.
Okay.
- What is it?
- The conditions got worse.
The wind changed direction,
so they're calling off the search.
When conditions improve,
they'll head back out.
That's it? That's all they said?
They said we have to leave now.
That's what they're saying.
We're going to look for her.
If they won't, we will.
- Right.
- We'll find her.
Right. I'm going to look for my daughter.
Luis… it's dangerous.
I'm keeping an eye on the fire.
If it gets bad,
I'll come get you two, okay?
- I should take Dani.
- No, honey…
You'd leave us without a car.
And if Lide shows up,
there'd be no one here waiting for her.
Stay. If it gets bad,
I'll come back for you both.
- Fine.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Don't worry.
Luis, I'll go get Santi's car.
I'll ask if we can borrow it.
Elena, call me if she comes back.
- I will.
- Thank you.
- When Lide's back, we all leave.
- Okay.
Santi?
Santiago?
- Yeah?
- Santiago?
- What's up?
- It's Mara.
- Excuse me.
- Hi.
Listen, the police called off the search.
I just heard it on the radio.
Can we borrow your car
to look for her in the woods?
- Ours isn't--
- Of course.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
I'll come with you.
- You don't have to.
- No, I'm coming.
- The more, the better.
- Let's go.
Wait.
This one…
- Santiago?
- Yeah?
Mind if I check your place?
- That's a bit…
- I just thought maybe…
Maybe she's hiding in there, you know?
And not in the woods…
I would've seen her.
Maybe you missed her.
I'd feel better
if I could just take a quick look.
- She was upset with me--
- Yeah, sure.
- Go ahead.
- Thank you.
- I'm sorry.
- Come in.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
It's fine.
Anyway, this is the living room.
- Sorry. I…
- No, it's okay.
- If you don't mind checking…
- Sure.
- Sorry, I just…
- Let's see.
I'm sorry.
- That's the bathroom.
- May I?
Yeah, sure. Go ahead.
Here's the radio for…
- I was listening to…
- Right.
Can I check in there?
I'd rather you didn't.
Why? It'll only take a second.
She's definitely not in there.
This is part of my…
No, I'd rather you didn't. Not in there.
What's this?
That's…
- Mushrooms, it's--
- Drugs?
No, psilocybin. Psilocybin.
- It's more like… medicine.
- For what?
Stuff conventional medicine can't treat.
I use it to make…
It helps a lot.
Why are you still here?
I don't know.
I've got nowhere else to go.
I'm sure Lide's in the woods.
Luis.
I think the firebreak will work.
What's wrong?
What is it?
- Something's off.
- What?
- He…
- What's wrong?
- Something's not right. Luis!
- Why wouldn't he let me in?
- Where?
There's a room he wouldn't let us check.
And he was nervous. You could tell.
- It's just weird.
- Think about it.
He saw Lide, there's a fire,
and he didn't bring her home?
Maybe he didn't know about the fire.
- No.
- Okay, let's think.
- I'm calling the police.
- There's no signal.
No internet either.
- Is it just your phone?
- No, there's no signal.
- And yours?
- Since when?
Like five minutes ago.
Let's go back to his place
and get him to let us in.
Why won't it go through?
- It's not working.
- What's he up to? Is he leaving?
He's leaving.
- Santiago!
- Keep trying, okay?
I will, but we're cut off.
- Santi!
- Yeah?
Wait. Santi.
- Wait up.
- Yeah.
- Where are you going?
- Well, I'm…
- Huh?
- To get Lide.
Do you know where she is?
I'm guessing she's in the woods.
Get in if you want. Let's--
- We're coming.
- Sure.
- She's probably in the woods.
- We're coming with you.
Come on, Mara. Get in.
- Are there still bears?
- Excuse me?
- Are there bears in the woods?
- No, that map's old.
No bears.
- Ah, wait.
- What is it?
It's getting dark.
You'll need flashlights.
- I'll be right back.
- I'm coming.
No, you stay.
The key.
Stay calm.
Isn't this Lide's bracelet?
See? That was quick.
It's really important. If it gets dark…
One for you, Luis.
One for you, Mara.
Finding her will only get harder.
- We're wasting time--
- Wait. Turn it off.
- Why?
- Turn off the engine.
Turn it off.
Sorry?
Give me the keys.
What's wrong?
What's this? "Isolated area," "safe area"…
What's this map for?
They're notes for…
Remember what I said earlier
about psilocybin?
Besides my job
with the Department of Environment,
I also do rituals in secluded areas.
Santiago, where's my daughter?
- It was in here.
- Right.
She gave it to me earlier at the hut.
No. That's a lie.
She never takes it off.
Never. I gave it to her.
- There's no way she gave it to you.
- God.
I want to check your place again.
Give me the keys.
- Hey!
- Give me your house keys!
Give them to her.
- Hand them over!
- Do it.
- I will.
- Let her check. Do it.
To hell with the keys!
- Lide!
- Mara!
- Don't come any closer.
- Please.
Open up! Lide!
Stay right there. Give me the keys.
- Lide!
- Luis…
Lide!
The keys. Now.
No! Stop!
- Just let her check.
- Lide!
Come on, Luis.
No funny stuff!
I'm watching you.
Mara!
Open the door, Santiago!
Mara.
- Do what she says.
- Right.
- Open it!
- Lide's not in here.
- Open the door, Santiago.
- Lide's in the woods.
- Do what she says. Open it.
- Okay, I'll--
- Open the fucking door!
- Okay.
- Do what she says.
- I'll open it.
What is this?
What's all this?
- Your daughter isn't here.
- What…
What the…?
What's all this? Who are you?
It's…
What is it?
- What's all this shit?
- It's…
Where's Lide?
What's in there? What's that room?
Look, it's my meditation space.
- No.
- Lide!
This damn door.
Open this one too.
Now, Santiago!
Do what she says.
- Please.
- Fine.
- Open it.
- Fine. There.
Go in.
Go ahead.
See?
She's not here. Like I told you.
- Where's my daughter?
- She's not here.
I didn't do anything to her, Mara.
She got lost in the woods.
- I called the police.
- Good, Mara!
Because I didn't touch her.
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
I don't know, Mara.
In the woods or…
Please tell me where she is.
I don't know.
- Mara.
- I'm begging you. Please.
- Mara, listen.
- No. Where is she?
- I didn't do anything.
- Don't touch her.
No, don't you touch her.
- Don't.
- Okay.
Where's my niece?
You had her bracelet.
You left her alone in the woods.
During a fire. Are we the bad guys here?
- I'm sorry.
- Where is she?
- What's this?
- Huh?
Huh?
- That's for my rituals.
- What rituals?
My rituals. If you'd just listen--
- I don't believe you.
- Let me speak. Luis. Mara.
You're not leaving.
Stop!
- Grab him!
- Luis!
We're not stopping
until you tell us where she is.
Luis, tie him up.
I didn't do anything!
- Come here.
- Please, Luis!
You left a kid out there in the woods?
You just walked away?
Now you expect me
to believe your "ritual" bullshit?
- Here.
- Luis!
You think I won't? Where's my niece?
Get up.
Now you're gonna talk.
Tie him to the chair.
- Can you…?
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
- Please.
Mara, I don't know.
Where'd you last see her?
- At the hut.
- Then why isn't she there?
- Because she got lost.
- Lies. She wouldn't.
She's been coming here her whole life.
She wouldn't.
Where's my daughter?
Luis…
Please. Do something. Make him talk.
What is all this?
What is this?
What's all this for?
What the hell is this?
Talk!
- Where's my daughter?
- I said I don't know.
Where's my niece? You saw her at the hut.
You kept her bracelet.
What did you do to her? Where is she?
Where is she?!
Talk! I'll make you talk.
Where is she?
- Luis.
- Where's my niece? Where?
Why did you leave an 8-year-old
alone in the woods during a wildfire?
Talk!
Luis!
What are we doing?
- What?
- What are we doing?
Getting him to tell us where Lide is.
No, we need to call the police.
Fuck. It's not working.
- What?
- There's no signal.
Mine isn't working either. Wait.
I'll grab his phone.
Luis.
Don't move.
The PIN.
- What's the PIN?
- I'm not telling you.
There's a fire.
Stop screwing around and give me the PIN.
What's the damn PIN?!
The PIN, you son of a bitch!
You gonna tell me or not?
What's the PIN?
- One…
- One, nine, eight…
Nine, eight, eight?
Mara!
No. Stop.
What?
I wasn't hurting him.
I swear. Mara.
I won't hurt him. It's just to scare him
into telling us where Lide is.
This asshole's lying.
- I'll stop if you want.
- Yes.
I'll stop if you want.
- I'll stop, okay?
I'll stop.
Stop.
We need to talk to the police.
There's no signal here either.
The radio.
- The radio.
Right.
- What?
- It won't work.
- It's not working?
- I can't use it.
Here. The battery's down here.
- Hello?
- Hello! Wait.
Can anyone hear me? Hello? Please.
Yes, I'm--
Hello, we're in the woods.
In the ranger's house.
Can anyone hear me?
It's dying. Low battery.
- Do you copy?
- Hello?
I'm the missing girl's mother.
We need the police. Please!
Hello?
Luis.
What if he did something to her?
What if he did something?
If I lose her, I'll die.
That's not going to happen.
It won't.
We'll search every room.
Every corner. Every closet.
Let's look. We'll find her.
- We'll find her.
- Right. Okay.
We need clues.
- Right.
- There has to be something.
Something that leads us to her.
There has to be something.
PITS AS SACRED SPACES
MESSAGES
SPRING
THAT WAS AMAZING.
NEVER BEEN SO SCARED AND FELT
SUCH A RUSH AT THE SAME TIME.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING RID OF ME.
EVERYONE WILL FIND OUT,
AND YOU'LL GO TO PRISON.
PHOTOS
Mara.
Can you listen, please?
Why are you suspicious of me?
What is it?
The shovel?
Your daughter was alone in the woods.
- I was--
- Shut up.
And about the bracelet, Mara…
- It was on the ground.
- Mara!
Mara.
Don't let him go.
Check the rope.
You're not listening.
- Shut up.
- You're not listening.
Watch him. I'll check outside.
You didn't let me explain.
Where's my daughter?
I don't know.
She can't just disappear.
Listen, I…
I was in the car,
and I saw Lide in the hut, okay?
At first, I tried to get her
to come home with me.
But she seemed fine,
like she needed to be alone because…
So I left. And I'm really sorry.
She's been alone for a long time now.
She's probably terrified.
I'm sorry, Mara. I'm truly sorry.
I should've insisted and brought her back.
That's where I messed up. But that's it.
I didn't do anything--
I don't believe a word you say.
I thought she'd be okay.
Where's my daughter?
I swear, I don't know. I'm so sorry, Mara.
Where… is my daughter?
In the woods.
- Where is my daughter? Again.
- In the woods.
- Where is my daughter?
- In the--
Again! Where is my daughter?
Where is my daughter?
- Where?
- In the forest-
Tell me! You should've brought her back!
If she's hurt, I'll kill you. I swear.
I could kill you right now.
Forgive me.
Luis?
What are you doing?
Look.
- Look.
- What is it?
- It's his phone.
- What?
This bastard.
- I know what you're going through.
- You can't.
I know how you're feeling. I really do.
Don't talk to me like that. Who are you?
Stop it!
I would never hurt a child.
I'd never lay a finger on a child. Never.
Here. Record it.
You have to come here already.
I haven't seen you all weekend!
I want to be in it too.
Come on. Let me.
I also want you here.
We miss you so much, baby.
- All right?
- Tell me, will I see her again?
Just tell me if I'll see her again.
I get that all of this
makes you suspicious of me.
This is just a big misunderstanding.
The map, the psilocybin.
Yes, this is what I do. I help people.
I do rituals with psilocybin
to help people
leave their old life behind.
To connect to something new.
To stop being afraid of death.
THE USE OF PSILOCYBIN IN TERMINAL ILLNESS
REDUCING ANXIETY AND DEPRESSION
IN TERMINAL PATIENTS
That night Gustavo spent in the woods…
He didn't want me there.
You were with him, weren't you?
- Yes.
- Weren't you?
What did you do to him?
Nothing bad.
You should've seen him.
- What?
- It was what he wanted.
He found peace, Mara.
He found peace.
Bastard.
He found peace, Mara.
No.
Elena…
Mara…
No, let me.
- Please.
- No.
Let me do it.
- Let me.
- Mara!
- Mara.
- No!
No! Please! Let me!
I'll do it.
No.
- No, please!
- Let me do it!
No…
It's not her.
You son of a bitch!
This piece of shit is messing with us!
Luis.
Where's the neighbor?
Inside.
- Tied up.
- What?
Hi, Jorge.
Look, I just dug the pit
for your rebirth ritual.
I've got a few,
but I dug this one far from the house.
I think the energy's perfect for you, and…
Yeah. I'll show you.
Anyway, see you.
Hi, Lide.
Are you okay?
There's smoke. There's a fire nearby.
Can you smell it?
- Are you out here by yourself?
- Yes.
Why are you all alone?
I was leaving some of my dad's things.
Want to see?
- What is it?
- Pictures.
They're beautiful.
My mom wanted to throw them away.
I knew him.
Really?
I tried to help him when he was sick.
- To cure him?
- To stop him being afraid.
Afraid?
Of what?
Of being away from you two.
Mom said
Dad didn't want to get better.
- I heard her tell my aunt.
- He did want to.
He couldn't, Lide.
- He couldn't.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- I think so too.
Your mom will understand someday.
She just…
She needs more time.
What's this bracelet?
Is it yours?
Yeah, but I don't want it anymore.
My mom gave it to me.
- What should we do?
- You can have it.
- No, it's--
- It's yours.
- You keep it.
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
- Look.
- You won't tell anyone?
- Of course not.
I'll say I lost it.
Or that a bear stole it.
You promise?
Promise.
Want me to drive you home?
- No.
- No?
I want to say goodbye to the hut.
You'll head home
as soon as you're done here?
- Okay.
- Promise?
Do this.
All right.
Bye, Lide.
Bye.
No…
That's not okay.
You've lost your minds.
He's lying.
He's lying to us.
What if you're wrong?
- No.
- Yes.
We need to make him tell us where Lide is.
- No, honey.
- Yes.
We need to leave, okay?
Call the police and get out of here.
Hey, Dani.
Dani.
Can you untie me, please?
Let's go look for your cousin together.
Please. Untie me.
Dani…
Your…
Your father and…
and your… your aunt and your mom
will go to jail if you don't untie me.
- They did this to you?
- Yes.
Yes, but they're confused.
They've got the wrong…
They've got the wrong person.
They think I'm someone else.
Someone different.
But… I didn't do anything wrong.
Then why didn't you tell them?
I tried, but your father won't…
He won't listen.
He just yells.
Honestly, I'm scared.
This is all my fault.
I told Lide she was annoying, so she left.
It's not your fault.
Look, untie me,
and we'll go… find your cousin together.
I know this forest
like the back of my hand.
Please, Dani.
We have to go.
- No.
- Yes.
We need to push him
until he tells the truth.
"Push him"?
What if he's telling the truth?
Maybe you two are wrong.
He was with Gus that night in the woods.
- What?
- Santi was there.
- With my brother?
- Luis…
My brother?
Luis…
Dani, let's figure this out.
Just you and me.
Thank you, Dani.
- Call the police. Take Dani.
- No.
- I'll keep going.
- No. Please.
- Take Dani.
- No. Come with us!
Come with us! There's a fire!
Thank you.
Dani!
Dani, where are you? Dani!
Thank you.
Open up!
Open this damn door!
The kid's with me! Open up!
- Open it!
- What?
Mara, let me out!
- Dani?
- Open the door!
- He was getting away.
- What?
I'll make him talk.
We have to pressure him.
- Open up!
- Make him talk.
Open this fucking door! Luis!
You're not coming out!
I'll keep pushing until he talks.
He will. You'll see.
Dad!
- Son?
- Luis, the kid's here!
- Dani?
- Open the door!
What? Dani…
Why's my son in there? Dani!
I've got your son!
- Why's Dani in there?
- Santi.
- Dani!
- Dad, stop yelling.
- What?
- Stop yelling, he says!
Why are you in there?
Dani! Son! Are you okay?
I'm in here, Dad.
Stay calm. Stay calm, son.
Stay away from him.
- Give me the keys.
- No.
- What?
- I have your son, Luis. Open up.
- Give me the key.
- He won't hurt him.
Luis!
Give me the key.
No!
I need to know where she is.
You locked my son
in there with that bastard.
- Give them to me.
- He won't hurt him.
I need him to tell me
where my daughter is!
- Are you insane?
- Open up, or I'll hurt him!
Open up!
I'm opening the door!
If you hurt my son, I swear I'll kill you.
- Luis, look.
- Listen. Don't hurt him.
Take me. Leave him.
- No.
- Take me.
Luis, look.
Look.
Move back. I'm coming out with the boy.
Don't drag him into this.
Everyone stay calm.
- Dani, son.
- Hey!
- Son.
- Don't come any closer!
- Come here.
- Stay back!
- I'm sorry, Dad.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay, buddy.
I'm so sorry.
I'll kill this bastard.
- Don't hurt me.
- Luis.
- Don't hurt him.
- Don't come any closer.
- He's a kid!
- Don't follow me!
- Calm down.
- Dani.
- Get in.
- Stand over there.
- Okay. Here.
- Dani, it's okay.
- Stay calm.
- That's it.
- He didn't do anything.
- He's just a kid.
- Please.
Let him go!
Stay back!
You stay inside!
- Stay inside!
- Let him go.
Dani, baby. I'm sorry.
It's okay, son.
- Dani.
- We'll stay here. Let him go.
- Let him go.
- Luis, stay there.
Don't hurt him.
Listen to me.
I need the car keys.
Give me the keys.
Don't. He'll take him.
- Santiago, please…
- Give me the keys!
I don't have them!
- Fuck!
- I don't know where I put them.
Please.
Let him go. He didn't do anything.
- Let him go!
Let him go. Now!
- No!
Come out, and I'll hurt him!
- Okay.
- Mara, stay by the door!
Fuck!
Stay back! Luis!
We'll stay here! Just don't take him!
Calm down. Don't hurt him.
- Don't hurt him!
- The keys are in the car.
- What?
- The keys.
He's taking him in his van.
- Mom!
- No!
- No, Dani!
- Quiet!
- Dani!
- Stay there!
- I'll claw your eyes out.
- Get in. I'm sorry.
Please, Santi. Don't take him.
He's taking him!
- Buckle up.
- No!
- Hey! No!
- Stop!
- Dani!
- Mom!
- No! Dani!
Santi!
- Dani!
- You bastard!
Dani!
Mom!
Okay, Dani. Get out.
Run back to them!
Okay? Get out of the car.
Get out, Dani!
Dani, get out!
Get out!
- You piece of shit!
- No!
Stop!
Stop, Luis, stop! Stop!
Santi, no!
Santi, stop! Luis!
Please stop!
Stop! Santi, enough!
Leave him alone!
No!
It's okay. You all right?
Luis!
I'm sorry, Luis. I'm sorry.
No…
Stop! Luis! No! What are you doing?
- No!
- What were you gonna do to my son?
No!
- Luis!
- Where's my niece?
I know where Lide is!
- I know where Lide is!
- Stop.
He knows where she is.
- I'll tell you.
- Where is she?
- Where is she? Tell me.
- I'll tell the police.
- What?
- Absolutely not.
No, tell me. Where is she?
- I'll only talk to the police.
- Tell me!
- Tell me where!
- In the woods.
- In the woods?
- Alive?
- Yes.
- She's alive, Elena.
- She's alive.
She's okay. Take me to her.
Come on, please!
Get up. Let's go!
- Which way?
- This way.
Straight?
This way?
Take Dani.
If we're not back in two hours,
call the police.
- We'll come back in his car, okay?
- Okay.
Here.
Which way?
- Which way?
- Straight ahead.
Say it.
We did what we had to do.
Shut up!
- I'm terrified of you, Luis.
- Of me?
We're going to find Lide, okay?
- Where is she?
- Right here! We're so close!
- He's taking us toward the fire.
- Stop!
- Where's my daughter?
- Please, listen to me.
- What?
I'm sorry you're hurting.
I'm so sorry, but I…
What?
I'm sorry.
- Luis!
- He got away!
Stop! No!
I can't see him!
Where'd he go?
- Mara!
- Luis!
Mara!
Luis!
Help!
Lide.
Lide!
Keep shouting!
Over here!
I'm here!
Lide, yell!
I'm in a hole.
I'm down here!
Lide.
I'm down here.
Lide!
Lide, look at me.
- It's Santi. Look.
- I'm stuck. I can't move.
- Let me see.
- Help!
Give me your hand.
Come on! Give me your hand!
That's it. Stretch. Grab my hand!
- Pull!
- Give me your hand.
I can't reach. Push it away.
- The dirt…
- I can't!
Come on! I'll reach you!
- Yes, you can!
I can't reach!
Come on!
Wait.
- I'll get a stick.
- No!
- I'll be right back, okay?
- Please come back!
- Lide, hang on.
- I can't.
Now!
That's it. You can do it. Pull hard.
Okay. Come on.
I've got you.
That's it.
Lide.
Lide?
Can you hear me?
No!
- No!
- Mara, no!
- Mom?
- Honey.
Are you okay?
- Mom.
- Are you okay?
- Mom!
- What? What is it?
- I didn't know where you were.
- Mom!
I'm sorry.
My leg really hurts!
It's okay, baby.
You're okay now.
Here. Cover your face. Can you do that?
Okay? Like this?
Come on. Let's go.
We're almost there.
What about Santi?
Did he hurt you?
I fell.
I fell… into a hole.
There was so much dirt.
I couldn't get out.
What?
I was chased by a bear.
- And I fell.
- What?
I couldn't find the house.
Lide…
He…
He pushed you into that pit, didn't he?
- Huh?
- No.
Santiago. Yes, he did.
- He saved me.
- He pushed you.
He saved me.
Wha--
He didn't push you?
No.
- You fell by yourself?
- Yes.
Lide, I need you to tell me
if Santi hurt you.
- Did he do anything to you?
- No.
All right.
Mara!
Luis.
- Luis.
- Lide!
Lide!
- Is she okay?
- She's okay.
- Honey, are you okay?
- Yes.
Are you alright, sweetheart?
Where was she?
- She fell.
- Where?
In a pit. But she's okay.
- A pit?
- Yeah.
Is she hurt? She's hurt.
She thought she saw a bear,
and she fell in.
Was it Santi?
No, she just fell. She needs to go
to the hospital, but she's okay.
- I'm cold.
- Let's get out of here.
- Right.
- She needs a doctor.
- Let's get out of here.
- It's okay.
- Let's follow the firebreak home.
- Let's go.
We're here now.
- The keys?
- I've got them.
- See if it's open.
- It is.
It's over, baby.
There.
- Get some water.
- Right.
- And blankets.
- Coming.
Honey.
It's okay. Does your leg hurt?
- Not as much now.
- No?
Does your head hurt?
Anything else hurt?
- No?
- I'm cold.
Your uncle's bringing blankets.
I love you.
- I love you.
- Me too.
I love you.
Now, sweetie…
Your uncle's taking you
to the hospital right away.
The doctor will check you out.
Everything will be okay.
He'll take care of you.
Mara?
I'm thirsty.
Right, honey.
There.
Hey, wait. Slow down, honey.
Easy.
That's it. Where did your mom go?
Where's Mom?
She left.
- Which way?
- Straight ahead.
Into the woods?
- Yes.
- Yes?
Mara!
Lide.
Lide, hey.
Lide, don't fall asleep, sweetie.
Look at me, Lide.
Stay here.
Lide. Wake up.
EMERGENCY
Where's Mara?
Are you family?
No. I found him on the road.
Can you hear me? Do you understand?
Why were you on the road?
- What happened?
- She got lost in the woods.
She breathed in smoke.
- Can you hear me?
- She fell in a pit.
- She hasn't had water.
- Can you hear me? Look at me.
- She's responsive.
- She hit her head here.
We need an X-ray of her arm.
- When did you find her?
- About an hour ago.
- How old is she?
- Eight years old.
- What do we have?
- Smoke inhalation.
I'll get Dr. Bautista.
Check her heart rate, pulse, and BP.
You can't come in, sir. We'll update you.
Can you hear me?
What's your name?
- Santiago.
- Santiago, why were you on the road?
What happened? Prep trauma bay four.
Pupils, normal.
- Any severe pain?
- Everywhere.
- Everywhere?
- Yeah.
- We'll start an IV, okay?
- Okay.
- I'm dizzy.
- We'll lay you down.
Oxygen, please.
- Weight?
- Forty-two pounds.
- What's her name?
- Lide.
- Lide, can you open your eyes?
- She's weak. Inhaled a lot of smoke.
Pulse ox 95. Close the curtains.
Shut the door too, please.
Honey, we found Lide.
We're at the hospital.
I'll text you the address.
I'd like you to come here.
- Good evening.
- Hello. How are you?
- Did you call?
- Yes, that was us.
- Which way?
- The observation area.
Follow me.
Santiago.
Call Radiology. Set up a CT scan.
Excuse me.
- Come in.
- Can you give us a moment?
- Go ahead.
- Thank you.
I don't know… I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
I'm so sorry.
How are you feeling, Santiago?
Whatever happened, you're safe now.
Okay. Can you tell us
how you got those cuts on your face?
It wasn't…
I'm sorry. I don't…
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It was a bear.
A bear?
Yes.
Yes, I was attacked.
By a bear in the woods.
I guess she must've been…
protecting her cubs.
Or she thought she was.
She couldn't be reasoned with.
- Mr. Serrano.
- How's my niece?
Don't worry. Come with me.
- Come in.
- Is she okay?
She's sedated, but stable.
I guess you won't be
pressing charges, then.
No.
Can you imagine a bear in jail?
Lide, honey. How are you?
Her leg needs time to heal,
and she hit her head, but she's okay.
How are you?
Fine.
I'm sorry I was mean earlier.
It's okay. I'm sorry too.
You can't be here, ma'am.
It's dangerous. Come on.
Can you hear me?
- Where's my daughter?
- Are you the missing girl's mom?
We've been notified she's at the hospital.
Can you make sure
my house doesn't burn down?
Don't worry. The fire's under control.
Come on. Let's go!
I brought this flower for Lide.
It's a fire lily.
It only grows after a fire,
out of the ashes.
I thought she might want to have it.
Anyway…
Santiago…
Yeah?
I'm sure she'll love it.
Thank you.
FIREBREAK
Subtitle translation by: Marta Aulet