By locking horns with Dhanraj
you have endangered your life.
Scoundrel.
"My dream girl,
when will you come?"
Move. Move. Move.
"My dream girl,
when will you come?"
Wild people.
You disturbed me
while | was singing.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
When | leave from home, my
wife helps me sit on the cycle.
My man at the field
helps me get down.
| fell down. Who will help me?
| will help you.
- Why?
Tell me. Why is everyone running?
Hello, village head.
- Hello, village head.
Hello.
Sir, everybody is
saying | Killed my wife.
| swear on God. | didn't Kill her.
| didn't Kill her.
Is there any
eye-witness of the murder?
Sir, | am the eye-witness.
Sir, husband and
wife were quarreling.
He beat her very badly.
Poor woman fell on
the ground in pain.
| saw it.
Sir, | saw Rajpal taking
her to the north direction..
..and hanging her.
No. Sir, it is a lie.
It is a lie, sir.
My lord, they are
concocting a story.
Is there no one to
challenge their lie?
Rajpal, in a case
testimony is of utmost importance.
There are two eye-witnesses.
After committing murder when you
were fleeing, they caught you.
It confirms our suspicion on you.
The village council
finds you guilty..
..and hands you over to the police.
Banwari, take Rajpal to
Rampura police station.
This is the reward
for your service to me.
After ruining a poor man's life,
they are feigning innocence. Look.
They did such a derogatory deed.
And confidently gave false
testimony in the village council.
If Suraj had not come on time..
..an innocent man
would have been hanged.
Fine. | don't say
whether they are guilty or not.
But are you the village head?
Is there a council
to deliver justice?
Are there police?
Your son became a goon.
He barged into their
house and bashed them badly.
Is this justice?
If they had suffered
serious injuries..
..who would have been responsible?
If everyone does as they please..
..how will there be
peace in the village?
What will happen if
everyone resorts to violence?
My son was wrong to barge into
their house and thrash them.
Calling it a mistake is not enough.
He will have to
apologize to everyone.
| apologize for my son's mistake.
| will ensure that it
doesn't happen again.
Hand both of them to the police.
Release Rajpal and bring him to me.
Did you see, dear?
What your brother is doing!
In so many years | never
apologized to anyone in the village.
Your brother is the new age don.
| used to always
think that negotiation..
..bribery and
differentiation are enough.
People say | always give sermon
to others but not to my family.
Nobody can dare raise
his head in front of me.
If you interfere in
other people's affairs..
..will we be able to
live in this village?
If you knew the culprit,
why didn't you tell me?
Or else you should
have told the police.
Tell me.
Are you an incarnation
of God who has come..
..to liberate
sinners from their sins?
Sita.
Father is very angry. Bring a
glass of buttermilk. - Okay.
Your father and | have
returned from the council.
For me..
What is this? You are
acting like a child.
What is this?
You will have to take
permission to relieve yourself.
| asked for a glass of buttermilk.
Father, buttermilk.
There is another policy
besides negotiation..
..bribery and differentiation,
isn't there? - Penalty.
Besides negotiation, bribery and..
.differentiation there is
penalty too. You forgot.
An innocent man is being
punished on false charges.
You are telling me
to watch it silently.
| follow penalty.
Righteousness woke up to
eradicate unrighteousness.
You were telling me
to apologize. Why?
Had your son not done this,
an innocent man..
..would have been punished.
Why should | apologize for that?
If your son does a
good deed, praise him.
Don't get angry needlessly.
Who said | am wrong?
People who give false testimony,
rape hapless women..
..and commit murder.
If | am defamed for
punishing such wicked people..
...| accept defamation.
If India's brave revolutionaries
had not shed blood..
..we wouldn't have
called them martyrs.
Why did you call me an
incarnation of God..
..who punishes sinners?
You must have noticed. When
mother cooks in the kitchen..
..children help her a bit.
The same way God also
needs such kind of help.
She is young. Forget it.
Drink it. Father, let
anything happen in the village.
Why should we quarrel?
Drink buttermilk.
Don't talk like a
naxalite in front of me.
Your speeches won't
work in front of me.
Do whatever you want.
Can't you stop fighting
and live harmoniously?
Dissection heals incurable wounds.
Sweet talks can't heal it, father.
Suraj, what is your
goal in life? Tell me.
| have no goal or destination.
Destinations are
formed automatically.
| can't live under the
burden of somebody's favor.
It is difficult for a
culprit to escape from my grasp.
Yes. Every youth talks like that.
It's rubbish.
If you live here, you
will always quarrel.
Go and live in Meerut.
You know | didn't
come here willingly.
You called me repeatedly.
That is why | came.
Now, you are telling me
to leave. So | am going.
Brother.
What is this?
You didn't come for five years
saying you are busy studying.
You came recently and
you are returning so soon.
Don't stop me.
My train will arrive at the station.
| will board the train.
And reach Meerut.
Got it?
Take this, dear. Give it
at the workshop. - Okay.
Suraj has come. He has come.
Tonight, we will have a feast.
He has come. He has come.
He has come.
How is everyone?
How are you, Paro?
- Fine.
Where is your father?
- He is there.
Is everything fine at home?
The entire locality was
silent in your absence.
Now, we will have fun.
Come on. Let's have a party.
What is this?
A bag. Remove it.
Where are Bali and Ramu?
Suraj, a lady came at
midnight to repair her car.
We took pity on her
and fixed her car.
She left without paying money.
Both have gone to recover the money.
Did they misbehave with the lady?
- No.
How did she leave
without paying money?
She was a strange lady.
Suraj.
- Suraj.
When did you come?
- What happened to you?
It's the game of destiny.
We went to recover
money from that lady.
We went there. She
had big Alsatian dogs.
They came running to hug us.
They clawed us.
That lady didn't stop them?
No. She told them to attack us.
If she had only attacked us,
we would have understood.
But she was standing
in her balcony proudly..
..and combing her hair.
And she said,
"Don't let them escape.”
She made the dogs run after us.
Who is that lady
who didn't pay money?
Her name is Veena.
She studies in G.V Lady college.
Her car number is TMS 6006.
Hi.
- Hi.
Good morning. - Who are you?
Why are you sitting in the car?
| am a mechanic. | am
taking the car to the workshop.
Madam had told me. Give this to her.
Your name?
- Paratha.
Paratha?
-Yes.
| gave the correct address.
She will surely come.
Four girls are coming in a cab.
Mister. Mister.
This is my car.
Beautiful.
- What?
| said it's a beautiful car.
Why did you bring my car here?
For repairing.
- Who said my car has broken down?
You didn't pay money for
reparation. So | brought it here.
Whom are you threatening?
Look, mister. | will tell the
police to put you in the lockup.
Got it?
- Great! What times are these!
The guilty rebukes the innocent.
Look there. Look there.
Look. See their plight.
They will bite me.
What happened to them?
They are dear to me.
Very dear to me.
My friends since the past 20 years.
They have been living with
me for the past 25 years.
The doctor gave them 56 injections.
Their survival seems unlikely.
Their survival
really seems unlikely?
Really. These innocent boys
will die within four to five days.
And you will be put behind bars.
Should | pity them
or should | pity you?
Veena, listen to me.
- What happened?
He is giving threat of
the police. Shall we leave?
Staying here is
like inviting trouble.
| don't know what
will happen. Let's go.
Wait. | will handle everything.
What trouble is this?
| didn't unleash my
dogs on them deliberately.
Unknowingly the
dogs got angry. And..
They are the apple of my eyes.
They are very precious.
Take this. A pearl ring.
- It's real?
It's worth Rs.7000.
Give me the car.
Take it.
Good evening, ma'am.
- Good evening.
Really.
She has come.
Hello.
- Hello.
How did he come here?
- Is something fishy?
| also think so.
Excuse me.
- Yes, please.
I am Vishnu.
- So what?
Pleased to meet you.
-1 am not pleased.
Shut up. Why have you come here?
To create a scene?
Get up.
What scene?
Who let them in?
Manager.
It was silly of us to
call you here. - Shut up.
Why? | will beat you with
my slippers. Understood?
Don't get angry.
- Look at this.
What is this?
Ma'am, you see..
- What you see?
Why did you allow them in
when they are not wearing suits?
I am sorry, ma'am.
- Nothing doing.
Throw these beggars
out within five minutes.
Otherwise you will be dismissed.
Understand?
Yes, ma'am.
- What yes madam? Go and do it.
Very good. Very good. Well done.
This is exactly how these
beggars should be treated.
Music is very interesting now.
- Yes. So?
| feel like dancing.
- So dance.
If you don't mind.
-1 do mind. Please go away.
You see..
- Okay. Okay.
We are going. Don't worry.
Everybody wears suit in this hotel.
Right?
-Yes.
Any other condition?
- No.
Who is this egoistic girl?
The only daughter of
the owner of the hotel.
That's why.
Manager, if we don't have a suit..
..should we come here naked?
- No.
But the dog has come naked.
Although there is a 'Pets are not
allowed' board outside the hotel.
| told you. She is the only
daughter of the hotel owner.
Are you the only
sycophant of the only daughter?
What is this?
It is that egoistic girl's dog?
- How did it come here?
She must be eating.
So she left her dog.
Shall we do our job? Son.
- Uncle.
What is this?
- Green chili.
What will happen if you eat it?
- Burning sensation.
What if the dog eats it?
- Havoc.
Let's wreck havoc.
Come. Come. Open your mouth.
| told you. Now see.
The grass is always
greener on the other side.
What is this?
Oh, God. Julie.
What is all this?
Is this a hotel or what?
Sorry, ma'am.
What is all this?
-lam sorry.
Excuse me. Julie. Julie.
Julie. Julie.
Julie. Julie. Julie.
Do you have any sense?
You ate chili and created havoc?
The dog also did the same.
His owner is rich.
You are a mechanic.
It can do whatever it wants.
"I gave my heart."
"I got pain in return."
Let's go.
Today, we are having a gala time.
There is a glow on your face.
We have nothing to
do with this nonsense.
If you open your mouth, we
will be exposed. Eat quietly.
The trouble is coming.
Show some style. Keep
your leg on the table.
Take this comb.
- Yes. Comb your hair.
You have only a few strands left.
Keep it down. Keep it down.
Hi. Veena.
-Yes.
Look there.
- What?
The same illiterate.
Oh, my God. Manager.
Yes, ma'am.
- Why did you let these apes in?
Manager.
- Excuse me, ma'am.
Yes, sir.
As you said, we are
wearing a suit and shoes.
And we have money too.
If you say anything, | will
explode the hotel in a minute.
Yes, manager. Isn't there another
nice hotel in this locality?
Mr. Manager.
- Yes, sir.
Everything should be
decent in this hotel.
First shave your beard.
Manager, one more thing.
What chicken is this?
Did you chop the
head while it was bowed?
Ma'am. As per the rules
| can't throw them out.
They seem to be goons.
Ms. Veena. If you say, |
will throw these goons out.
It's none of your business.
She is dancing merrily. Shall
| also show her dance steps?
Yes. Go ahead.
"Not just my heart, but
my life is also yours."
"What charm is this?"
"You have Killer eyes."
"Not just my heart, but
my life is also yours."
"I am an urchin."
"I enticed him."
"How?"
"l am trying."
"I am an urchin."
16 years old."
"Come into my arms."
"How to trust?"
"This bird will fly away tomorrow."
"My heart beats fast."
"My heart says so."
"Disco."
"The lady."
"I will teach you
the disco of love."
"Dance."
"Sing."
"Let your beloved
dwell in your heart."
"Not just my heart, but
my life is also yours."
"What charm is this?"
"You have Killer eyes."
"Not just my heart, but
my life is also yours."
"You have a beautiful face.”
"Admirers miss you."
"Beloved, give me
a hug for my sake."
"I will fulfill the
vows for seven lifetimes."”
"0 gregarious.
-Yes"
"0 crazy man.
"0 gregarious. O crazy man."
"It's my charm."
"Enticing and luring."
"It's not your cup of tea."
"Don't cast the
spell of love on me."
"Forget talks of love."
"Fear this flame."
"You might get charred.”
"Don't come in front of me."
"Don't commit suicide.”
"Not just my heart, but
my life is also yours."
"What charm is this?"
"You have Killer eyes."
"Not just my heart, but
my life is also yours."
Ravi, move. A car is coming. Move.
Catch him. Catch him. Catch him.
Come out.
If anything happens to the boy,
you will be sent to prison.
No. Forgive me.
| will give you money.
How much money will you give?
Take Rs.500. Let me go.
- Get lost.
What is this?
Why did you break the glass?
Leave. Leave.
Who are you? What nonsense is this?
Who are you?
Sorry.
Hello. Police station.
Oh, God. What has happened!
What has happened! My son.
Sinner.
You killed my son.
May you rot! You Killed my son.
My son.
For whom will | live?
Raju.
Take this money for the final rites.
| lost my son.
You are Suraj Prakash?
Come to the police station. Come.
Inspector, | want to bail him out.
You will have to fill the
bail form in the police station.
Come, mister.
Suraj, you were in the lockup?
We are leaving. Thanks.
Bye. Come on.
We came in her car.
She is a nice girl.
She signed the bail form.
We behaved very badly with her.
We even took her ring.
| don't know what
nonsense | spoke the other day.
Shall we go together?
But we will have to sit closely.
People will misunderstand.
Your ring.
Had it been an ordinary ring,
| would have worn it.
But as far as | know, it's
a precious ring. Expensive.
Only rich people can wear it.
Ordinary people
like me can't wear it.
Take this. Wear it.
| don't want this.
Look, Veena.
-Yes.
We will get married.
After our marriage our
elders will send us to a room.
Let's see what we
will do in private.
What?
-Yes.
Veena, you are immature.
You don't Know anything.
| am also young. |
don't know anything.
We will only stare at each other.
Let's practice that drama here.
No. We will practice it there.
It is difficult to
practice after marriage.
No. We will practice it there.
Yes. That is what | was saying.
Say it again.
- We will practice it here.
What? Being husband and wife?
-Yes.
What? - Yes. Fine. | am going to
office. - Will you come for lunch?
Lunch.
| will return from
office exactly at 7 o'clock.
We will practice what we
will do at night. Okay?
Yes. Only acting. No practical.
| am going to office.
- 1 will cook.
Bye.
- Bye.
Yes. | have returned from office.
What?
- What?
Look, Veena.
If you call me disrespectfully
after marriage, | will get angry.
Sorry. Sorry. | am sorry. Sorry.
What happened? Tell me.
You also called me disrespectfully.
No, Veena. Our marriage
won't work. | am going.
No. Our marriage will work.
Acting is not working.
Fine. You can call me anyhow.
- Look, Veena.
After our marriage you won't
call me disrespectfully. - Okay.
| won't call you disrespectfully.
- Okay.
Fine?
Why did you lift your leg?
Remove my shoes.
If you make faces,
we won't get married.
Okay. | won't make faces.
- Okay.
| think the shoe has got stuck.
You act well.
No.
- What happened?
| have sprained my back.
What happened? |
thought you are joking.
Here?
-Yes.
What do | do?
Is it paining? Shall
| call the doctor?
Call him quickly.
Fine. Lie down there.
1 will call him.
Did you see? We had to pay
a heavy price for our joke.
Oh, God.
- Carefully. Carefully.
| told you not to do it.
You didn't listen to me.
| thought you are Kidding.
Where? Here?
- Yes. That's it.
Press with your feet.
- Not with my feet.
| am dying, Veena.
Now?
Higher. Higher.
Higher?
- Higher.
"Your beauty is like
a blossoming bud."
"My beautiful companion."
"Your beauty is like
a blossoming bud."
"My beautiful companion."
"You dwell in my heart."
"I am your companion."
“Life is beautiful.”
"You are a young, handsome man."
"0 beloved, my companion."
"You dwell in my heart."
"I am your companion."
“Life is beautiful.”
“In my dreams."
"I have always found you, beloved."
"Your face.”
"Is like lotus in a pond."
"Ask me."
"This tumult in my heart."
"It is love. Love."
"Life.
-Is yours."
"O my beloved."
"Love manifests."”
"Is it a shower of nectar?"
“In your love."
"I have heard
melody in my heartbeat."
"In your tresses."
"The world is entangled."
"Don't tease me. Don't tease me."
"World.
- Golden fairies.”
"Do one thing."
"You are a young, handsome man."
"0 beloved, my companion."
"You dwell in my heart."
"I am your companion."
You know everything.
Still, you are planning to marry me.
Why? You didn't find any other girl?
Veena.
Father, a true man is the one who
helps troubled, helpless people..
..and who loves
principles more than money.
He knows | love him.
Still, he wants to marry me.
He is a characterless man.
Shut up.
If my daughter roams
around with an unknown man..
..without her father's permission,
will | earn good name?
Your image won't be tarnished,
father.
Suraj is not less
than us in any aspect..
..be it wisdom, money or virtue.
Find out everything about him.
Later decision whether it's
good for me to meet him or not.
Don't believe this useless
man and get angry needlessly.
Veena, you are my only daughter.
Otherwise..
Haste won't help us.
It seems to be a deep love.
| want to tackle it my own way.
Mister, what
insolence is this? Leave me.
| say leave me.
Suraj.
Leave me. Leave.
Leave my hand.
You know me, don't you?
No. | have only seen you.
I am Vishnu.
| am Suraj.
What happened?
- Call a doctor first.
Doctor, come quickly.
The doctor is coming.
What happened?
She fainted on seeing a murder.
Murder.
Sir, Suraj didn't take
Veena's name in the court.
The prosecution lawyer didn't
ask him the reason of murder?
Suraj said, "When |
have confessed my crime.."
".what is the need to argue?"
Tomorrow the court will
surely deliver its verdict.
Sir, | know the verdict.
Suraj will surely be hanged.
No.
It is injustice. |
won't accept the decision.
Father, he committed
murder to save my honor.
It is our duty to
save him from the noose.
Please, father. | beg you.
Save him anyhow.
Save him.
What's the matter?
The lawyer was saying tomorrow..
..you will get death penalty.
We came to give you this good news.
Suraj, in the court you
said you committed the murder.
But why didn't you
state the reason?
Had it been good?
If I had said I murdered
Vishnu to save Veena from him..
...| would have been acquitted.
Would the prosecution
lawyer have kept quiet?
In which condition did | find Veena?
Was she raped?
Is there any witness?
He would have gone into
the depth of the matter..
..and made Veena a rape victim.
What would have happened to Veena?
Look. I am happy that I saved Veena.
But | don't want her to be
slandered because of me.
Don't tell anyone.
Destiny is irrevocable.
It's difficult to erase it.
All of you leave.
Raj Shekhar, |
have heard a bad news.
About Vishnu's murder.
The murderer is Suraj, a
goon in the nearby village.
Yes. Exactly.
He committed the murder.
He didn't tell the court the
reason for committing murder.
Don't look at me like that.
| found out the truth from the
watchman of Vishnu's guesthouse.
You have silenced him.
Why will | do that?
You have done it.
That's why | am saying.
Your daughter is
of marriageable age.
You did this so that
she is not slandered.
| don't want it.
But as long as we are friends,
don't worry at all.
Thanks. You came at the right time.
Under section 378 and 302..
..the court gives death
penalty to the culprit.
Father.
Oh, God. | have got rid of Suraj.
Once | get my daughter
married to a decent man..
.1 will heave a sigh of relief.
Suraj's father or his relative can
save him from the death penalty.
How?
By appealing in the high
court and reopening the case.
The government won't
reject the appeal.
If they reopen the case
and find real witnesses..
..the verdict will
be overruled easily.
But you won't let that happen.
- Why?
Why?
What will | gain?
After hearing the
contentions and the testimonies..
..it has been proved
that the culprit..
..didn't commit the
murder deliberately.
So the court
overrules the death penalty..
..and sentences him to
five years of imprisonment.
Doctor. Father.
Father.
Brother's death
penalty has been overruled.
But he has been sentenced to
five years of imprisonment.
It was possible due to Dhanraj.
The court has
reduced the sentence, dear.
But my name has been tarnished.
Will | be able to walk on the
street with my head held high?
Passerby will point fingers at me..
..and call me a
murderer's father, dear.
Veena.
You must have thought
| got death penalty.
How will | come back?
If you Kill me, there
won't be anyone to save you.
You like to save me, don't you?
Had it not been true, why
would | have agreed to marry?
To save you from death
penalty | promised to marry him.
If | had been hanged, |
would have died only once.
Now, it is difficult for me to
either forget you or remember you.
Why did you Kill me like this?
Why did you Kill
me like this, Veena?
Had you died in an
accident or due to an illness..
...| would have lived
my life like a widow.
Not as somebody's wife.
Fine. You saved me.
You married for me.
| have come back for you.
Break your
marriage and come with me.
We will spend our lives somewhere.
| removed the noose from your neck..
..and adorned it around mine.
This body belongs to somebody else.
But my soul still belongs to you.
Wait.
It's the custom to see
the guest to the door.
| feel as if | am
sending you for a battle.
Remember.
Wherever you go, as a
milestone my chaste soul..
..will congratulate you,
encourage you and guide you.
But my body
belongs to somebody else.
While biding you
farewell | didn't want to cry.
But | couldn't control myself.
Forgive me.
| knew you will come to meet me
on being released from prison.
If we had met in the village,
| would have been slandered.
He wouldn't have liked it.
It is difficult to please everyone.
That's why | was
waiting for you here.
My duty is over.
| am closing the door.
As well as my heart.
Good luck.
- What happened?
What is this? Suraj
is going to the bar.
Suraj has returned. Bring a garland.
Put it around his neck.
Come. Come. Come.
Suraj has returned.
Suraj.
- Yes. Sura;j.
The people of the locality are
coming to honor you with a garland.
What have you done to yourself?
Garland.
Me?
- Then what me?
Get lost. Get lost. Get lost.
Is he talking or pelting stones?
He is inebriated.
- He would never drink.
"Love is a joke."
"Don't ever fall in love.”
"This suffocating
life is very painful."
"If your beloved betrays you."
"There is liquor."
"It won't turn its back on you."
"I have become the new age don."
"Look, | have
become a drunkard too."
"I have become the new age don."
"Drink and be merry."
"I have no concern with the world."
"What intoxication is this!"
"Such thrill in a sip."
"I have become the new age don."
"My beloved made me a drunkard."
"First you embrace your
lover and then reject him."
"Great is the custom of love."
"Who is yours and who isn't?"
"Only God knows that."
"First you embrace your
lover and then reject him."
"Great is the custom of love."
"Who is yours and who isn't?"
"Only God knows that."
"Give Him this message."
"I have nothing left."
"1 am destined for
suffering and pain."
"And to sigh."
"The wound inflicted
on my heart is deep.”
"Nobody cares for me."
"I have become the new age don."
"My beloved made me a drunkard."
"Drink and be merry."
"I have no concern with the world."
"What intoxication is this!"
"Such thrill in a sip."
"Lovers are not fortunate.”
"If the world is my enemy."
"I am also not afraid."
"I wasn't a drunkard."
"Listen, people.”
"1 was forced to drink."
"Friends, forgive me."
"Now, | share a bond with liquor."
"My heart rejoices in loneliness."
"I have become the new age don."
"My beloved made me a drunkard."
"Drink and be merry."
"I have no concern with the world."
"What intoxication is this!"
"Such thrill in a sip."
"I have become the new age don."
"My beloved made me a drunkard."
Jai Prakash won't live for long.
He might die anytime.
The doctor has clearly said so.
Uncle, this is the best chance.
Now, we will have to influence
the affluent people of the village.
If we seize Rajoli and
the surrounded areas..
.1 will be the
permanent owner of this place.
There is a person in that village.
A spy. Yes.
- Call him.
Start the work today itself.
Father.
Brother. Brother.
Brother.
He died saying you will surely come.
Sir, hello.
- Hello. Hello.
He.. He is one of the
candidates contesting for the post..
..of the village head
after Jai Prakash's death.
Doesn't he have a
strong personality?
My name is Banwari. Hello.
Banwari. Look.
Since generations
Jai Prakash's family..
..and my family have been enemies.
After his death we should
forget this quarrel and unite.
Khata told me everything.
- Okay.
But | have a request.
-Yes.
You will have to make
someone the head of Rajoli village.
| will make you the village head.
But here..
- 1 will do your bidding.
Everybody will imitate you.
You fool. Why did you sneeze?
Put your thumbprint.
Why are you putting your
thumbprint on a blank paper?
We are mortgaging
our lands to Dhanraj.
Did you give them money?
| have a tender heart.
| couldn't see the
villagers' woes. So | helped them.
Why did you have to sell
your flourishing fields..
..and leave the village?
Earlier your father used to lend
money without charging interest.
He would even give
us manure for free.
But when you went to prison,
his heart broke.
He would only lie on the bed.
Banwari, this is how
you have helped them.
As a proof that our
villagers are honest..
..and to recover
the borrowed money..
..I have made this arrangement.
Why didn't you help them get a
loan from the government committee?
There are many such
committees in the village.
Not just that. Dhanraj has
a good influence over them.
But why did he lend
money to our villagers?
To seize our small farms.
And later, he wishes to
control the entire village.
What is the total amount?
It's a large sum.
Look, manager. Repay the loan
that our villagers have taken.
The money..
Nobody from our village
will sign these papers.
Khata.
Khata, come.
What is this? - Shall we
take the other signatures?
Where did Kalu, Moti, Ramu..
..all those who work
in our village go?
They had taken a loan from Dhanraj.
They couldn't repay the loan.
So they are working for Dhanraj.
As slaves?
-Yes.
Come on. Work quickly. Why
are you staring at my face?
Look, Suraj is coming.
Suraj? Why is he coming here?
Hello.
- Hello.
My villagers, come here.
Why did you come? Why did you come?
Why are you calling them?
| will buy them and
sell them to your master.
Are you joking?
Rs.10000.
Make the receipt.
Come on, everyone.
- Come on. Come on.
Suraj has come. Suraj has come.
Look.
Henceforth all workers from my
village will work in my farms.
Not as unpaid workers.
Everybody will work together.
The profit will be equally
divided amongst everyone.
| will have a share.
Long live Suraj Prakash,
the new age don!
the don of our village!
Long live Suraj Prakash,
Stop. - Long live Suraj Prakash,
the don of poor people! - Stop.
You spend half your life
shouting slogans for others.
What did those
people who became rich..
..because of you do for you?
They sold their motherland.
And became homeless.
You worship your motherland.
You don't need to work for anyone.
One man gives a lecture.
And lakhs of people listen to him.
That era is gone.
Lakhs of people
should toil together.
The day someone comes to guide
them and value their worth..
..that day our country will prosper.
Henceforth | don't want to
hear slogans in this village.
He brainwashed them
and became their leader.
He doesn't even
want to hear slogans.
He is luring
people with sweet talks.
He talks about our wellbeing.
Shut up.
-Yes.
Will you spoil my
eardrums by yelling?
Put cotton in your ears.
Take this.
- Rummy show.
Oh, no. What is this?
He always wins.
Why do we play?
We should give him
money without playing.
Don't play.
Come on.
- Brother has come.
Listen, village head.
-Yes.
| need your cronies' help.
What do you want to do?
Tell me. We will do it.
We don't want a share.
- We want wages.
For our hard work.
For their every atrocity.
- We have an answer.
| had not imagined all
of you will demand this.
Is there anything lacking? Tell me.
1 will try to fulfill it.
Why are you talking to us?
Talk to our leader.
Surely.
This is the rule.
Who is your leader?
Chaudhary Shankarlal.
- Chaudhary Shankarlal.
We will surely take it.
- Our right.
Come.
Sit.
| am the leader.
Chaudhary Shankarlal.
You are the contractor.
You are the accountant.
When you quarrel, you
remember the village head.
No. My father was looking
after the farms since a long time.
Now, | look after it.
- Since the time you have come..
.. the workers have got spoilt.
Did it happen because of me?
Of course.
Why did you call the
workers from other villagers?
| thought they would like ..
.. to lead a comfortable
life in their village.
Who are you to decide this?
Nobody else took the initiative.
So | took it.
What did | do wrong?
Small farmers had taken
a loan from Mr. Dhanraj.
There had made an agreement.
Who are you to cancel it?
It is my habit to fight
injustice and to stop it.
Oh ho.
You will take law in your hands.
What if they can't repay the loan?
You will take law in your hand.
Isn't this your plan?
| have understood your plan.
| see. So you have understood.
How did it begin?
Is this quarrel against me or them?
Yes. We will have to pay
the workers double wages.
And two days off in a week.
How will they feed
themselves for two days?
Don't worry about that.
Since generations my workers
have been working in your farms.
You will have to transfer
the farms in their names.
Why? Dhanraj will take mortgaged
farms by giving them a loan?
Don't argue with me.
Do as | say.
Don't interfere when the
farms will be transferred..
..in Mr. Dhanraj's name.
If you want, you can
take your money back.
What if | don't want that?
What else? The quarrel will
intensify. Blood will be shed.
And then wails.
Today, | came to
meet you respectfully.
But now, | accept your challenge.
| won't let the workers
get trapped in your ruse.
Is it a challenge?
- Yes. It's a challenge.
See you.
Suraj, what is this?
You went to the village.
And never returned.
| have settled down in
the village permanently.
Look, bring all unemployed
students who study with us.
| want to talk to them. Later,
you will also have to come with me.
What is this? How will |
find all unemployed students?
Why did all of you come here?
To lock horns with me?
No. When educated
city-bred are toiling..
..should we sit at home?
Madhavi, what is the matter?
Nowadays your sister is
not to be seen at night.
Where is she?
- Why are you asking me repeatedly?
Because | don't want
her to fall for a goon.
If you are so concerned about her..
..why don't you find a
decent boy and get her married?
Who will conduct his son's
marriage into your family?
Do one thing.
| have kept you as my mistress.
| will gladly keep your
sister as my mistress.
It's a sin to be born as a woman.
On top of that a ‘Devdasi"
{A woman married to a deity).
Destiny.
- Slowly. Slowly. Slowly.
This terrifying place is
very eerie. Let's leave.
Why? What is here?
Nothing. Ghosts and spirits
haunt this place at night.
| love ghosts and spirits.
If they come, | will talk to them.
You can go.
- You will talk to ghosts? How?
| spoke to you. Is it
difficult to talk to ghosts?
My wife also says the same thing.
| was saying because..
- | said leave.
Why are you wandering here?
Why are you afraid?
| wished her well.
And she is driving me
crazy with her wails.
You are Dholakia Baldeva,
aren't you?
I was. Now, I am Madhavi's uncle.
She is my sister's daughter.
Who is Madhavi?
Madhavi is the ‘Devdasi'
who danced in our temple.
She is her younger sister.
Her name is Vidya.
Why is she wandering alone at night?
She has lost her sense.
Landlord Sevaklal wants
to give her a grand car..
..and a bungalow
surrounded by a garden.
But she is crying inconsolably.
We are low-caste people.
How can we lead a
dignified life? Tell me.
You beat me. Why do beat me?
Get in. - Open. Open.
Open. Open the door. Open.
Where are you going quietly?
Come to my house.
You are afraid because | am drunk?
Don't be afraid. Come.
Sita. Sit here.
No. Wait. Sita.
Sita.
It is you? How did you come here?
Did you come to meet brother?
| saw your dance.
You dance very well.
He is my brother.
Hello.
Brother, she is a great dancer.
Her name is Vidya.
Is that so?
No, brother. | have
told you so many times.
Don't drink.
Don't scold. Don't scold.
Listen to me.
She is an orphan girl.
She will stay here.
You don't mind, do you?
Why will you mind?
Don't worry.
God is there. Stay here.
He will handle everything.
Stop.
Stop. Come here. Come here.
| was waiting for your return.
Once you live in a bungalow,
you will forget your old lover.
Come. Come with me quietly.
Otherwise..
| will hand you over to the police.
Who is it?
You are amazing!
You dare to threaten
a girl in my village?
Landlord Sevaklal said
he will pay me Rs.10000.
You brought her along with
you without paying money.
Is it fair?
Get lost.
If you want to feed yourself, toil.
Don't sell helpless people and
earn money by dishonest means.
If you come here again,
| won't spare you.
Are the servants dead?
Why did you venture out
of the house? Come on.
What nonsense is he talking?
Educated people have come.
Should we become cowards?
- No.
| don't know what
spell Suraj has cast.
All women in the
village say he is good.
Every woman likes Suraj a lot.
Village head.
-Yes.
| don't know what
solution you have thought..
..and what you will do.
Drive away the
educated boys immediately.
Come on. Come on. Run quickly.
Hurry up.
They ran away. They ran away.
They ran away. They
ran away. They ran away.
Eunuch, you cling to me. Stay away.
They ran away.
Is she your wife?
- My wife died two years ago.
Do the villagers know?
Is this something to
shout from the rooftop?
If it becomes common knowledge..
..my image will be tarnished.
If you swear not to tell
anyone about our plan.. - Yes.
It will always remain a secret.
- Okay.
Understood?
-Yes.
Or not?
Come. Come. When did you come?
Just now.
Village head, sit there.
He said this chair is yours.
Bring another chair.
- Right away.
What happened? - Last night
| had a fight with a bull.
Did it beat you badly?
Beware of bulls.
| was careful. But
it got infuriated.
Sit.
- Okay.
Where will you hide your hand?
That's why | was at home.
How much money did Dhanraj
give you for this unfair strike?
At present he has
given me only Rs.15000.
He will pay me more.
If | want to end the
strike immediately..
..what will | have to give you?
Whatever you wish.
| will have to give something?
-Yes.
It's not compulsory.
Give whatever you want.
Otherwise forget it.
Village head.
-Yes.
If | give money,
will you end the strike?
That's why | have
started the strike.
Don't you feel you
are betraying him?
What is this?
His demands will never end.
My needs will be fulfilled
only when his are not fulfilled.
Give me.
| will give whatever |
have to give. - Okay.
In front of a witness.
Shall I bring a witness?
No. Your admirers are here.
Who?
- Come, brothers.
Disloyal village head.
You want to ruin us and become rich.
We spared your life.
That's why laborers have
to fight amongst themselves.
You should be hacked to death.
-Yes.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
Give my dhoti back.
Forgive us. He had brainwashed us.
It's better late than never.
-Yes.
Come on. Get out.
The one who is coming?
-Yes.
God bless you, dear.
- Hello.
Hello.
| was waiting for you.
You?
- | live in Jai Prakash's house.
Junior master wears..
He watches it all
the time and drinks.
| wanted to know why he does that.
His sister told me you
saved him from death penalty.
So | wanted to meet you.
| found out you come
here every Friday.
So | came to meet you.
Your name?
- Vidya.
Junior sir has
helped the village a lot.
You saved him.
The entire village
is indebted to you.
You adore him.
Why don't you make
him give up drinking?
Nobody in the village has the
guts to talk in front of him.
If you explain to him once,
he will give up drinking.
If that happens, |
will be really pleased.
Look, sister. God
hears everybody's prayer.
Pray devoutly. Your
wish will be fulfilled.
| am leaving.
Uncle.
Who is it? Get lost.
- Get lost.
Sir, hello.
Why have such
affluent people come here?
Uncle, Come here.
-Yes.
| don't know how you will do it.
Kidnap Vidya from Suraj's house.
- What are you saying?
Otherwise it will be difficult
for you to live in this village.
Don't forget that.
You can't judge a
person's character by his caste.
Lotus grows in muddy water.
We don't throw it away.
We offer it to God.
What's the meaning of
caste discrimination?
There is a difference
between words and action.
Do you know what is
written on our village walls?
What is written?
| feel ashamed to tell you.
You tell him.
You have kept a girl in your house.
People have criticized it.
It's written, "Suraj has kept a
whore in his house as his wife."
"He gives summons in the village."
"And he has kept a
whore in his house."
Brother.
With God as the witness
| accept her as my wife.
If you want to wipe the
tears of 'Devdasi' women..
..who become
victims of wealthy men..
..marry them and give
them respect in the society.
Don't sell them as dancers.
Did you see him marry her?
- Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
| spend money and he marries her.
If sir asks me, what will | say?
Say she got married.
- Shut up.
Ma'am.
Shall we go?
- After some time.
| was waiting for you.
Come with me.
I--
Got married?
| was waiting to congratulate you.
How was your nuptial night?
Next year you will have
either a girl or a boy.
Pray for that.
Did | say something wrong?
Don't misunderstand me.
He didn't marry me
because he loves me.
He married me
because he took pity on me.
And to fulfill the
duty of a true man.
| thought the man who
gives sermons to the world..
..will be happy because of you.
His heart..
Vidya, will you say this on Friday,
standing in the temple?
Not at all.
Because of that your life..
Initially | also
thought the same thing.
But | don't want to incur the
sin of another life being ruined.
Next Friday please send him.
Lord, fulfill everybody's wish.
Keep this in the car.
Seeing your black clothes
and beard, | understood.
Your plight is such because of me.
| am responsible for this.
Sita's trial by fire
in the Ashok garden.
| was wondering what punishment..
..you will get for meeting me.
Why only Sita?
What Mandodari must
have gone through?
Don't ruin your life for me.
If you give 1% of the
love that you gave me..
..to Vidya, who
considers you her life..
..she will
sacrifice her life for you.
Calling her your
wife is not enough.
She needs love as well.
Look, Veena. I am a man. Not a
corpse that I will forget my past.
| didn't come here
to give you a lecture.
| have come to tell you the
difference between lie and truth.
Vidya had faith that | will
make you give up drinking.
She came to me
thinking | will persuade you.
She fulfilled her duty.
You loved me before you married her.
You don't know what
endeavors she has done..
..so that you give up drinking.
After her marriage |
came to congratulate her.
She smiled and said,
"He married me."
"He put the
Mangalsutra around my neck."
She told me lovingly, "I
have borrowed this Mangalsutra."
Listen to me.
A woman wants only love.
You didn't realize how
much your wife loves you.
| regret that.
If possible, listen to me.
Live with her lovingly.
This is what | pray for.
Why did you meet him?
You would tell me you are
going to the temple to worship.
You love him so much?
| swear on you.
| met him without your
permission for the first time.
Don't misunderstand me.
Disloyal woman.
'You don't know what
endeavors she has done..'
'..so that you give up drinking.'
Vidya..
..I have hurt your feelings.
Forgive me.
| didn't take pity
on you and marry you.
"Your melody is on my breaths."
| got you. What else do | want?"
"Beloved, you are my worship."
"Beloved, | have
forgone my anklets."
"Your melody is on my breaths."
| got you. What else do | want?"
"Beloved, you are my worship."
"Beloved, | have
forgone my anklets."
“In my breaths."
“In my arms."
"In the spring."
"1 capture the image of
my beloved in my eyes."
"From my eyes to my heart."
"1 capture the image of
my beloved in my eyes."
"From my eyes to my heart."
"You have loved me."
"And expressed your love."
"We shouldn't ever separate."
"Your melody is on my breaths."
| got you. What else do | want?"
"Beloved, you are my worship."
"Beloved, | have
forgone my anklets."
"Tell the spring my
beloved is my ornament."
"Wherever he goes, | have
to adorn myself with him."
"Tell the spring my
beloved is my ornament."
"Wherever he goes, | have
to adorn myself with him."
"Bed of flowers is my life."
"You are my lamp."
"I am your flame."
"Our heart is a temple.”
"Your melody is on my breaths."
| got you. What else do | want?"
"Beloved, you are my worship."
"Beloved, | have
forgone my anklets."
“In my breaths."
“In my arms."
"In the spring."
Sir. Sir, stop the car.
- Why?
Look there.
- What happened?
Come.
- Come. - Let's go and see.
Come. Come.
- Look there.
Stop.
You can't run even
for a short distance.
You started panting.
We are meeting and talking
as our college is going on.
After finishing our studies?
We will get married.
- Will we be able to marry?
We will surely get married.
| get scared when
| think of brother.
Initially you were afraid
to laugh in front of me.
Later, you were afraid to talk.
Later, to meet me.
Now, you are afraid of marriage.
Shall | ask you something?
After marriage what
will you be afraid of?
Enough. It's time for my bus.
If | miss the last bus, |
will have to go walking.
Why don't you do one thing?
- What?
Stay in the hostel with me.
Rubbish.
Sitaram.
-Yes.
The girl who loves my brother,
she is Suraj's sister, isn't she?
Yes, sir.
Catch her. Catch her.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
What are you looking at?
Tattoo her hand.
Her hand?
- Yes. Quickly.
Do it quickly. Hurry up.
| will just do it.
You are crying because | saved you?
Why do you want to die?
Where is Dhanraj?
Will you tell me or not?
Suraj. Suraj.
Why are you beating them?
You tattooed her hand.
You should be punished.
But | have decided to
make you my relative.
Had it not been so, |
would have buried you alive..
..for what you did to my sister.
Dhanraj, listen to me carefully.
My sister is going to marry
your brother within three days.
You decide whether you
will conduct their marriage..
..or whether | conduct it.
If you created hurdle in the
marriage, | will Kill your brother.
Three days. It is Suraj's decision.
What are you doing?
- Leave me.
Seeing your old lover, you felt
love for him. Don't be stubborn.
You might have to regret it.
- Shut up.
Call my brother from the
hostel immediately. Go.
Brother. Stop.
Forgive me.
| will never meet him again.
Had | known this would happen..
...| would have never loved him.
Nobody ate dinner?
Serve dinner for everyone.
Where is she?
Come. Let's have dinner. Come on.
Eat.
How long have you known him?
Six to seven months.
Did you know?
He is also like his brother?
Answer me.
- No. He is decent.
You loved him in spite of knowing..
..that our families are
enemies since generations.
Will you be able to lead a
happy life in that house..
..after marrying him?
She loved him
because of this belief.
Shut up. | asked you.
You will marry him.
Brother.
Vidya. - Yes. - Guests are coming
for the marriage. Bring Sita.
Okay.
Come. Come. Come.
Come. Come.
- Hello. Hello.
Come. Come. Come.
Come.
- Come. Come.
Sit. Sit.
- Come.
Sit.
Suraj, don't think I came here
because I got scared of your threat.
| didn't expect you to come
to my house to see my sister.
That's why | threatened you.
You are young. You get angry soon.
Come, sister. Greet your relative.
My brother has chosen a great woman.
Suraj, forget our enmity.
We are converting our
enmity into a relation.
Old foes became relatives.
How did water and fire unite?
It happened.
Come in.
You must be amazed why |
conducted the marriage in haste.
In our country bride's
family has to bow their head..
..in front of groom's family.
Henceforth Suraj will do my bidding.
He will have to.
You are somewhat beautiful.
Have you gone on
your mother or father?
| am drawing water with toil.
Don't you feel
ashamed to watch quietly?
Why should | feel ashamed?
Draw water.
Your job is to draw water,
cook food, wash vessel.
And at night..
It's been six to seven
months since we got married.
And you have still not conceived.
Shameless.
Come. Come.
Come.
Come. Come. Come. You came suddenly.
| need your help.
Strange! How is sister Sita?
| didn't have a sister.
She has fulfilled that void.
That's great.
- That's fine.
Why do you always
wear black clothes?
Sir, my villagers are
leading a dark life.
| will wear colorful clothes
once their lives become lively.
Oh.
- Come. Come. Come.
At the time of election | invited
your father home and asked for..
..the vote of your village and
the neighboring 50000 votes.
| didn't get a single vote.
Now, we are relatives.
| have come to you with
great faith to ask for votes.
Try to understand.
After the marriage..
..both the villages
have become relatives.
Dhanraj will win the election.
Yes. There is a difference
between marriage and election.
When my father never let
him win the elections..
..how can his son break the norm?
| came here rightfully.
And you are refusing me.
B.A.C.K. Back.
C.U.T. Cut.
Back cut.
- Hey, you.
| was practicing. Forgive me.
Sit.
Suraj, | have a control
over the people. - Control.
What if it's proven wrong?
Enmity between relatives.
Relations are maintained
at home. Not in politics.
Do you want to stand against me?
No. | want to elect a
deserving candidate.
Suraj. You called me home
and you are humiliating me.
| didn't call you.
You are my relative.
So | welcome you warmly.
| didn't come here for welcoming.
| didn't form a bond with
you to mortgage the village.
You know with whom you are
locking horns, don't you?
This time | will print
such posters of yours..
..that people will
spit on your face.
Sure?
- Completely.
Man proposes and Suraj disposes.
Hello.
- Hello.
My name is Gangaram.
| am standing in the
election against Dhanraj.
My party has given me a ticket.
Come, Mr. Gangaram.
Pleased to meet you.
Bali, take the jeep home.
It's a serious matter.
Let's talk.
You know Dhanraj is a dangerous man.
| know | might lose my life if |
stand against him in the elections.
He can do anything
to save his position.
He has money. He has power.
But | have only my hands.
To serve humankind.
| love people.
| have mustered courage
on hearing their pleas.
"What does the beating drum says?"
"What is it complaining?"
"The world of heart
is very beautiful."
"Nobody knows the
truth behind voting."
"It's not good to
give vote for money."
"Don't sell your conscience."
"It's not good to
give vote for money."
"Don't sell your conscience."
"What does the beating drum says?"
"Don't say we were exploited."”
"Nobody serves the public."
"This chance comes
once is a lifetime.”
"Don't lose the chance.”
"Take the right decision."
"Vote for the poor. It's
the need of the hour."
"Think well and cast your vote."
"Yes. Yes. Yes."
"What does the beating drum says?"
"What is it complaining?"
"The world of heart
is very beautiful."
"Nobody knows the
truth behind voting."
"There should be food to eat.”
"And clothes to wear."
"A small hut with a cot.”
"There should be food to eat.”
"And clothes to wear."
"A small hut with a cot.”
"We don't need money."
"We are rich by heart."
"Money makes you corrupt.”
"You get whatever
you are destined for."
"But beware of thieves."
"You get whatever
you are destined for."
"But beware of thieves."
"Support me."
"And unite."
“Drum.”
"What does the beating drum says?"
"What is it complaining?"
"The world of heart
is very beautiful."
"Nobody knows the
truth behind voting."
"It's not good to
give vote for money."
"Don't sell your conscience."
“Say it."
No!
What injustice is this?
Don't beat her.
Brother.
Sita. Sita.
- Brother.
What happened, sister?
Brother. Mr. Dhanraj's
people threw her here.
Sita.
Stop.
Don't go.
Leave me.
Listen.
If you go there now, have you
thought what will happen? Tell me.
People can't see a
helpless animal being beaten.
Sita is not an orphan.
That is what | am saying.
She can become
orphan if you do haste.
Sita won't become an orphan.
| will ruin that
scoundrel's village.
| will destroy it.
You will tarnish Sita's image.
Shall | say something else?
You will make her a widow?
Will that be fine?
Listen.
After your decision,
this won't stop.
Go. Take your revenge.
Brute.
Wicked man.
Brute. Brute. Brute.
Brute.
Brother.
Why did they send you here?
Have they sent you to your
brother's house forever?
Dhanraj has sent this
letter with your sister.
Read it out.
"Suraj, is your sister's life dear..
..or the villagers'
life dear to you."
"It's time to decide.”
"This time there was a lot of
corruption in the election.”
"That's why | am filing a
case to cancel the election.”
"At the hearing you will
have to testify in my favor."
"The election will be held again."
"You won't lock horns with me."
"If you do that, your
sister's life will become hell."
You will blame me?
No. It's not right to put your
family at stake to save your honor.
It's a crime to
beat a hapless woman.
Beating your brother's wife
is not a decent thing to do.
It is better that you forget the
mistake that you did in your haste..
..Apologize to Suraj
and bring Sita home.
Today, you have made
me realize my mistake.
| should apologize to
Suraj and bring Sita back.
| think it is best.
Will you go or shall | go?
Brother, your
decision has made me happy.
| was sure you will listen to me.
| am so reputed.
And you want to tarnish my image.
If you utter another word..
- Sir.
Sir.
- What happened?
Two men and a eunuch
have come to meet you.
All three of you are
Suraj's friends, right?
Yes, sir. We have
come here as Hanuman.
As messengers?
Hanuman had brought a ring.
We have brought
this letter. Take it.
Balram.
- Yes, sir.
Look after the guests.
- Okay, sir.
Are we guests for two to three days?
Shut up, eunuch. Come on.
Read it.
Read it quickly.
-Yes.
"Dhanraj, | have not
decided to serve people.."
"..to hear false praises like you."
"For the wellbeing
of Rajoli's workers.."
"..if Sita leads a
miserable life, | don't mind."
"You can't do anything worse."
"But to save people from
a greedy man like you.."
.1 will lock horns
with you all my life."
Shut up.
Why are you beating me?
| was reading out whatever he wrote.
Why did you come here?
To see whether
Dhanraj is alive or dead?
That insolent fellow
made an ordinary man win..
..just to humiliate me.
Don't you feel ashamed?
Go and die somewhere.
We won't rest in peace
until we don't take revenge.
| will take revenge.
| will burn Rajoli the way |
am burning with rage right now.
1 will Kill all
those who helped him.
Only after | kill Suraj,
who snatched my post..
..will anything be
cooked in my house.
And | will rest in peace.
Tell me. What do we have to do?
A fair is going to be held in
their village's Goddess Kali temple.
Suraj will surely come
to worship Goddess Kali.
There will be havoc.
In that havoc Banwari along
with his cronies will shoot Suraj.
There won't be any witness.
| was waiting since a long time.
It's not good for us to meet.
| couldn't send the
message through someone.
That's why | came.
He plans to wreak
havoc in the village.
| suspected this.
He will kill you during the riot.
Beatings will happen suddenly.
As far as possible, stay
away from the quarrel.
You have come to tell me this.
Shall | believe you?
He has gone crazy
because of his defeat.
| don't know what he will do
in his desire for revenge.
| am afraid..
..his life might be in danger.
| can't even dream of
seeing you as a widow.
| am not afraid for myself.
| am afraid for my unborn child.
| don't want people
to taunt him saying..
..he caused his father's death.
Congratulations.
Sita?
Let your husband's anger abate.
| will meet him and take a decision.
You know it's a sin not to
control your desires, don't you?
It's written in the Vedas.
But the man who has come here..
..people's favorite
leader Suraj Prakash..
..Vedas, religion or
justice nothing will stop him.
Earlier they would
meet outside the village.
Now, they are
meeting in the village.
Tomorrow they might
meet in the house.
Why? They might even
meet in my bedroom.
Don't say anything to him.
He is hapless people's God.
Helpless people's friend.
Farmers' well-wisher.
Rajoli's don.
He has the right to do anything.
Listen. What are you saying?
Shut up, shameless woman.
If you love him, why don't
you elope with him? - Dhanraj.
It's not a decent thing to humiliate
your wife in front of everyone.
She is my wife. And your mistress.
You..
Leave him. Leave him.
Go away.
It's an old proverb
that wife doesn't cross..
..the line drawn by her husband.
But he is a man who
listens to his lover.
Why are you talking like that?
| came here to beg for your life.
You are Kalyug's Savitri and
he is Yamraj (Lord of death).
You have come to
save my life from him.
Whom are you fooling?
Dhanraj, if you want to take
revenge from me, go ahead.
Don't blame an innocent woman.
| don't have the strength
to take revenge from you.
You are people's God.
If | speak against
you in front of them..
..they will hack me to death.
If this had happened in
my honorable village..
..people would have
chopped you into pieces..
..and thrown your
bits to dogs. But here..
..people are watching the spectacle.
If | seek justice, people will say..
"It is not our man's fault.
Your wife is at fault.”
Our village also has some rules.
We are not like those who
silently watch the spectacle..
..if a man casts lustful eyes
on a woman from another village.
We will pelt stones at him
and break his hands and feet.
Leave him. Leave him.
Don't beat him. Don't
beat him. Don't beat him.
- Beat me.
Shameless.
You are saving him in front of me.
Dhanraj.
She is pregnant.
Don't beat her brutally.
Who knows whether
it's my child or his?
Dhanraj.
Veena.
No. Don't touch me.
Listen.
- Veena. Veena.
Veena.
Forgive me.
Due to my ego | got
separated from all my loved ones.
After hearing my husband
say that my character is bad..
..instead of living..
..it is better that | die.
Veena. Veena.
Look.
Forget old enmity.
And bring Sita home. Yes.
Forget your differences.
And lead a happy life.
Wherever you go..
..as a milestone..
..my chaste soul..
"This life is perishable."
"Those who are born, they die."