Tubi. Tubi.
Helen?
Erik?
Is it normal... to be scared?
Yes, of course.
This is the beginning of a new
phase of your life, Cassandra.
It's okay to be scared.
I'm excited too.
You know, I'm just... I'm nervous.
I don't know.
You know, returning to a previously
unhealthy environment
prior to your hospitalization,
in this case, your home of residence,
can be daunting for anyone.
A level of trepidation is to be expected.
But if you feel like your surroundings
are becoming a little too much for you,
then I'm only a phone call away.
Okay. Thank you, Dr. Smith.
Oh, I also have some good news.
We were able to find
you possible employment
if you're interested.
Oh, I...
You don't have to take this one,
but as you know, you have to
have some form of employment.
No, no, no. No. I don't
mean that I'm not...
that I don't want the opportunity.
I... it's just I haven't... I-I don't...
I haven't had a job.
I don't know. I haven't had an interview.
-I don't know. -I know. I know.
Don't be nervous.
These folks at the hotel are great.
They offer on the job training,
so there's no experience required.
I think this is going to be
the perfect starting point.
Here, the manager's expecting you to call.
Okay.
- Thank you. - Uh-hmm.
Thank you for this.
Okay, let's see what else?
Oh, yes. So I'm gonna be scheduling you
one time a week for the next six months.
It's either gonna be in my downtown office
or in at your home.
This is the standard procedure
to monitor how well you're adjusting.
After that, if you like, we
can trim down the sessions
to twice a month.
What if you don't think
that I'm re-acclimating well
to my environment?
- Will I... - Be re-admitted?
Yes.
I'm gonna tell you the truth.
It's possible,
but that would have to
be the very last resort.
Honestly, I don't want
you to worry about that.
Just put that out of your mind.
As long as we stay on top of your sessions
and your medication,
you're going to be just fine.
Speaking of, here's your prescription
and your medication.
Uh-hmm.
You must take this.
Okay.
-Okay. -And I guess that's it, Cass.
Do you have any questions for me?
Um, no, no, no.
I guess not. Thank you.
You know, when I think
back on our sessions,
you used to frequently bring up fairytales,
how they inspired you when you were little.
No.
I don't believe in fairytales
anymore, Dr. Smith.
I've... I'm all grown up now.
Actually, I was gonna say,
it isn't such a bad thing
believing in fairytales.
In our own way, I think we should all have
a small belief in fairytales
or the pursuit of our own
individual happy ending,
whatever that might be.
So I don't want you giving up
on your fairytale, Cassandra.
I want you to live your
life vigorously in its pursuit.
- Okay. Thank you, Dr. Smith. - Uh-hmm.
Um, can I use your phone to call?
Go right ahead.
I don't... I don't have a phone yet.
Cassandra?
Hi. Yeah. Uh...
Andrew, but just call me A.J.
-Okay. -Come in.
-Thank you. -Yeah. Welcome home.
Your mom is gonna be so happy to see you.
-Yeah. -And your ride over was okay?
- It was. - Yeah?
Yeah. And, uh, thank you for everything
you've been doing for my mom.
Of course. I live right
down the street, so...
-Oh. -...it's no problem.
You know, you look exactly
how I imagined you would.
I've only seen old pictures
from when you were a kid,
so I wasn't too sure, you know?
-Here's your house key.
-Oh, thank you for this.
So you won't have to go around knocking.
-Thank you. Where is she?
-Your mom's asleep.
She's in here if you
wanna take a peek at her.
Okay.
I, um, I have an interview
that I have to go to, so...
-Okay. Cool. Good luck. -Yeah.
I'll put your stuff in
your room for you, okay?
- Thank you. - Okay.
-Hi. To management? -Yes, ma'am.
-This way. -Oh, okay. Thank you.
Oh.
-I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
-Yeah. I'm sorry.
That was totally my fault.
Uh, no, you look a little lost.
Uh, can I help you with anything?
You look like you have your hands full.
Uh, I can make room.
I'm just looking for Helen.
I think she's the manager.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Uh, her office is right
down there on the left,
right at the end there.
Thank you.
Have a nice one.
I like your cologne, by the way.
Oh, thank you.
-Cassandra? -Oh.
Yes, Helen Troy.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's been a bit of a bad
house in here today.
No worries.
I was just admiring your pictures.
Um, you have a very beautiful family.
Those were taken years ago.
Our daughter is much
older now, but thank you.
So this will be your first
job in a few years, correct?
Yes. Uh-hmm.
Well, I, um, uh, haven't
actually had a job.
Hey. No judgments here.
We hire all types. Housekeeping is easy.
So as long as you're here
on time, a good worker,
and can fold, we don't
care about your past.
The job starts at 16.50 an hour.
Dr. Smith highly recommended you.
She said that you were great
with the hospital staff there.
Yeah, I did volunteer, um,
for some janitorial duties.
-Okay. -Few days a week
just to, you know, help pass the time.
Perfect. You seem like our ideal candidate.
So when can you start?
Immediately.
Perfect.
So let me look at our schedule,
see what we have here.
Are you able to work night
shifts, 6:00 PM to 2:00 AM?
It's a lot slower paced.
Skeleton crew. Just to get you started.
Well, that's fine. What
does that entail exactly?
Mainly turnaround services.
So light to moderate housekeeping
per guest's request,
along with food and drink delivery.
Are you able to handle that?
Yeah. Absolutely. Yes.
Okay. Perfect.
Now, I run a tight ship,
but I'm fair and I'm pretty good at my job,
if I say so myself.
We're the top five on "The
Forbes Travel Guide" by AAA
for the past three years to prove it.
So I have high standards,
but I take care of my people.
We're all like family around here.
You'll see.
I'm happy to be a part of it.
Okay. Great.
So we'll go ahead and start you tomorrow.
You can see Crystal at the front desk.
She'll give you your paperwork
and your temporary ID.
Okay.
- All right. -Thank you.
- Thank you. -Okay.
All right. I'm all done, so I'mma head out.
You're leaving now?
Yeah.
But it's such a blessing
that you'll be here
to help with your mother.
Yeah. But what if, while you're gone,
I can't take care of her properly?
-I forget. I... -You got this.
- You will do just fine. - Uh-hmm.
It's really not as bad as it may sound.
I'll walk you through our routine,
and whatever your work schedule is,
we'll work around it, okay?
-Uh-hmm. Okay. -All right.
So, you have a list of her meds, right?
I do, yeah.
Okay. All right. Now, where are my keys?
Right there. Keys.
- Thank you. -You're welcome.
Oh, don't forget her 8:00 PM dosage.
That's the one that helps her sleep.
Without those, she will
have night terrors, okay?
Yeah. 8:00 PM, night terrors.
- Okay. I got it. - Okay.
And if you need me, call me.
I'll come right over two minutes away.
- Okay. -All right?
-Thank you. -All right.
-I'll see you tomorrow evening.
-See you tomorrow.
Oh, my gosh.
Mija, you're home.
Mom, I didn't know that you were here.
How could I sleep?
The way you and A.J. were carrying on.
The house echoes, remember?
I remember.
I'm sorry.
Your burns, they look good.
They heal.
Yeah.
Come, give your mom a hug.
I haven't seen you for
10 months of Sundays.
-Yeah. It's been a while. -Uh-hmm.
I could have visited you, but, you know,
I have problems of my own.
I understand, mom.
Did A.J. tell you everything
that needs to be done here?
I believe so, yeah.
Hey, Mom.
What happened to all the pictures of Dad?
Mom?
I wish I had done all that.
Cassandra, where is she at?
-She's in the elevator hall... -Okay.
Like...
Cassandra?
-Oh, hey. -Hey, girl.
-I'm Paris. -Hi.
Call me Big P.
Okay. Yes, girl.
So, listen, I think you're coming with me.
-Uh-hmm. -I'mma show you everything
that's going on around here, okay?
-Okay. -You good?
-Yeah. -But in the meantime,
if there's anything you
need to know, I'm your girl.
I got all the tea.
What... what's tea?
Girl, like, what's going on around here?
-Like, gossip? -Yes.
-Oh. -Don't you want it?
-Yeah. Like what?
-Yeah, you look kinda nosy.
Anyways, so look, it's this, um, cook.
His name is Edwardo.
And girl, he think he Pablo
Escobar or somebody.
He do got the best
weed in the city, though,
like, no cap.
-You smoke? -No, I don't.
-You do percs? -No. Nothing.
Edibles?
-Nothing. -Oh, okay.
You're one of them kinda girls.
Okay.
All right.
-You good? -Yeah, I'm good.
All right. This job is not that bad, okay?
Especially the night shift.
-Super easy. -Uh-hmm.
Just remember one rule, mind your business.
Okay.
Girl, these guests around here,
they be doing the most.
Okay.
So whatever you see,
you ain't really see it.
I didn't see it. Okay. Got it. I got it.
-Mind your business. -Okay.
You look like you might be a little nosy.
-Okay. -Yeah.
I think you're good.
You see a lady named
Silvia with a black eye girl,
it's probably 'cause her
husband beat her up again.
-Huh? -Yeah.
Girl, I'm talking about putting
all on her.
-Yes. -That's terrible.
You good? -Yeah. No, no. No, I am good.
-Those drinks look good. -Yeah.
-What up, E? -What up?
These for Naudi?
-Oh, you already know they are. -Okay.
That girl love her martinis.
For sure.
-Cassandra, right? -That's me.
Uh, I didn't get to formally
introduce myself to you.
-I am Erik. -Nice to meet you, Erik.
So how are you enjoying
your first day at work?
I'm sure the gossip queen
here blabbing your ears off.
Whatever.
No, she's been great, actually.
We've been having a good time.
See? I've been great. Unlike
these watered down drinks
-you over here serving.
-Ooh. That's what we doing?
All right. Okay. Now, you remember that
at the end of the night
when it's time to tip you out.
-Whatever, nigga. -Yeah. All right.
Okay.
Come on, girl.
You planning on sleeping all day?
-Mommy? -Get up, damn it!
I'm sorry. Sorry.
You need to make me breakfast!
-Come on! Get up! -I forgot. I'm sorry.
- Chingada madre, huevona. -
¿Que Barbara?
Just what the hell do
you think you're doing?
Mommy! No! No, no, mommy, please.
Look at me. Look at me!
We have a deal, didn't we?
-Didn't we? -Yes.
I took you from the hospital
so you can stay here,
so you can help A.J. to look after me!
Okay. Okay.
-We have an agreement! -Yeah.
That's why they release you.
So you don't need to
take these pills anymore.
Okay, mommy. I'm sorry.
And that's the way you pay me
-for taking you out of there. -No.
You're not doing part of your job, girl?
Don't you think I can't call them?
-No, no, no, Mommy. Please.
-I can call them!
-No, no! Please! -Yes! So they can come
and pick you up and take you there again?
No, no, no. No, mommy, please.
So goddamn you're right.
What it's gonna take, huh?
Make my damn breakfast
and take it to my room!
And, you know, the pills,
you can take some of mine.
I have plenty on my medicine cabinet.
Mommy?
Thank you.
Mija, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for before.
I understand. Here.
Okay.
I know it's your favorite.
This is my favorite piece in the hotel.
It's the... it's the different
shades of red for me.
Are you partial to the color red?
Yeah. I love it.
Reminds me of a nice Pinot Noir,
John Coltrane playing in the back.
Hey. Let me help you up.
I didn't know the bar
was still open this late.
Uh, maybe it is.
Maybe it isn't.
And it's not what we agreed on, Helen.
I don't care, Erik? - At all!
What do you want me to do?
Call them back and tell
them that I can't come?
It's the board of directors luncheon.
I don't care. You know,
do whatever you want.
-Do whatever you wanna do.
-I run a business.
Erik. Erik! - Do whatever you want.
I don't care!
I run a business.
I'm sorry.
No. I'm sorry. I didn't see you.
-Uh, you okay? -Yeah.
All right.
Helen? - What?
You wanted to see me?
Cassandra. Yes. Um,
we're slightly overstaffed,
so I need to cut hours where I can.
So I'm gonna need you to
clock out a few hours early today,
say about midnight?
Okay.
Will do.
Oh, my God.
Cassandra, right?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
What? You scared of grown people toys?
No. No, no, no. I'm so sorry. I...
It's totally fine.
It's only natural to wonder
why I have so many.
-Yeah. -I'm Naudia,
but everyone calls me Naudi.
- Yes. Um, they told me. - Right.
Paris must have told you about me.
Well, then I guess you
know what it is that I do.
Yes.
But I... Don't worry. I don't judge.
I'm just here to clean your room.
Oh, good to know.
Yeah.
Uh, I really love... I
really like your name.
Oh, thank you. It's double meaning.
-Yeah, okay. -Yeah.
Wait.
So which one do you think?
-Oh, that's... -Girl, white or black?
You know what? The
girls look amazing in both,
but the white shows more booty.
So white it is.
Uh-hmm. Yeah.
You know?
You know what? This
would look great on you.
You know, I really should get going.
Okay. Yup. Hold on.
Oh, my God.
What?
-Here. -What is that?
Don't worry.
It's brand new.
Hasn't been used.
Oh, I can't. I...
No. You can.
And you will.
Consider it, uh, a gift
for tidying up the room.
No. No. I mean... I don't...
I don't... I really... I'm sorry.
Girl, what? No. Listen.
Before we truly learn to enjoy sex,
we first have to learn
to be with ourselves.
Trust me on this, honey. Okay?
Now take it and then go.
-Okay. -My client is on the way.
Where am I supposed to put this?
Tuck it in. Get familiar with it.
Okay.
-Here. Go. -Okay. Thank you.
No problem.
Get off of me!
Get off of... get off of me!
Get off of me! -
-Hey, are you okay? -Yeah.
-Are you all right? You sure?
-Yeah. I'm okay.
All right. I got you.
You sure you don't need medical assistance?
Uh-uh. No. I'm fine, really.
- Thank you. - Okay.
Well, then you're good to go.
If you start feeling headaches or anything,
-please find the nearest ER.
-Yeah. I will.
Thank you.
Guess you really don't
like hospitals, do you?
No.
My mother always said they're just good
for creating repeat
customers, and I believe her.
Ain't that the truth.
Well, the cops are taking this guy to jail.
They say he might be
the same one responsible
for a few attacks in the area, so...
- Yeah. - Uh-hmm.
-Here you go, ma'am. -Thank you so much.
-All right. Is she good to go? -Yes, sir.
Someone will be in contact
with you in a few days.
Try and feel better, ma'am
and make sure you buy this man a beer.
- He's a real hero. - Yeah.
I'm a hard liquor man myself.
Uh, can I give you a lift?
Sure.
Let me take this right here.
So you live with your mom?
Uh, yeah.
I recently decided to
move back in with her.
Um, her doctor called me and told me
that her health was declining.
Oh, uh, sorry to hear that.
Uh, how long has she been
dealing with, uh, health issues?
Wow, um, 20 years?
That's how long ago my father passed away.
What happened?
House fire.
It, uh, it happened suddenly in the night
and, um, it was just a
gas leak or something.
I just remember my mother waking me up
in the middle of the night
to get me out of the house.
She tried to go back in to save my father,
but it was too late, so.
Wow. Um, Cass, I'm, uh, I'm sorry.
Just something really
heavy fell on top of her
and pinned her to the ground.
And by the time the firefighters got there,
they were able to save her,
but they weren't able
to get my dad out safely.
So she's suffered a
pretty bad spinal injury.
So she's, um, she hasn't really
recovered from it, you know?
Man, I'm really sorry that happened.
Um, how old were you?
I was just a teenager.
Yeah.
Just had your whole
life turned upside down.
You were just trying to be a kid.
I'm sure that was tough.
Is that why this happened?
Oh, um, yeah.
I guess. Yeah.
I was just a kid, you know,
with all these things happening.
My mother just changed, you know?
Yeah.
I just felt... I felt so lonely.
And I just thought that this
was the answer, you know?
I get it.
You know, I was, uh, deployed in the army,
um, and I was on a
tactical convoy mission, uh,
right outside of, uh, the city of Mosul.
I'm in the back of the Humvee
laughing it up with my boys.
Within a span of four minutes,
I was the only one left alive in my unit.
I guess they called it survivor's remorse.
So between that and a little bit of PTSD,
I was in a bad way.
So about a year and a half later,
I end up in front of my
house with a bottle of gin
and a barrel of a nine-millimeter
in my mouth.
What stopped you?
This is it?
Yeah.
Yeah. This is it.
Honestly, um, it was my daughter's voice.
And I know that sounds crazy
because she was only five months old.
And I... and I could
swear I heard her voice
telling me to stop.
And the voice I heard
then is her voice now.
I'm sorry. I was...
I didn't think I would ever
tell anybody that story.
I... I'm sorry.
Well, she's really lucky.
How old is she now?
She's seven. This is her.
Sweet, right?
She's so pretty.
She's adorable.
Yeah.
She's my everything.
That's why I do everything for her.
Yup.
I'm gonna have a bar one day
and I'm gonna name it after her.
Wow. It would...
it would be really nice
to see you owning a bar.
Maybe it'll even give you
some space from Helen.
Whoa. What made you say that?
I'm sorry. I don't...
you guys just don't seem
like you're that close.
Damn. Is it... was that obvious?
Like, for real?
I... well, we, everyone
at the hotel have...
we've all seen you guys fighting outside.
Yeah. Right.
Well, um, I... she...
look, that's a story for another time.
Okay? Anyway, I am... um,
this is what I'm working towards.
And Helen, you know,
she's doing her own thing.
You know, just climbing
the corporate ladder.
Maybe you should... you
should take a few days off.
No, no, no. No, that's not necessary.
Are you sure? Because I can talk to Helen,
especially after what
you've been through tonight.
No. No. I don't need
any time off from work.
I don't need any time away.
I really enjoy working at the hotel.
It's freeing. You know?
Okay.
Well, okay.
Well, how about, um, you
can take my phone number
and give me a call if you need anything.
Oh, I don't... I don't have a phone.
Oh, okay.
Wow, that could be a problem.
Um, well, how about just get some rest?
Thank you for being my hero tonight.
Okay.
Um, I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow.
-Bye. -Bye.
Where the hell were you?
Oh.
Mommy, uh...
a man attacked me on the way home
from work last night.
- Did he... - No, no.
My coworker Erik stepped
in before it can get that far.
Good for you.
Don't forget to make my breakfast.
Helen?
Cassandra. Yes. Come on in.
You wanted to see me?
Have a seat. Erik told me
what happened last night.
I'm so glad that you're okay.
Yeah. Yes. I'm fine. Yeah.
He suggested that I give you some time off.
Oh, no, no. I told him
that wouldn't be necessary.
I can work.
-Really, I'm fine. -I figured that.
So...
he took you home after?
Well, after everything
that happened with the
police and everything,
I really didn't feel
comfortable riding the bus,
and he offered to take me. So...
He's a gentleman like that.
Well, I just wanted to
check on you before I left.
Again, I am so glad that you're okay.
I'm fine, Helen. Thank you.
Good.
Well, you can go ahead
and get back to work.
Thank you.
-Hey. -Hey.
Um, I'm about to close up in a few.
So once you're done delivering this...
why don't you meet me by the pool?
For what?
All right. I have something for you.
-Okay. See you there. -See you there.
All right, make sure.
So pretty out here.
Come up here sometimes just to...
get away from all the BS down there.
You know, no...
cameras watching you everywhere you go.
No radios.
-No Helen? -Ooh.
I'm sorry.
No. No, no, you're right. No Helen.
I swear, that woman,
she drives me insane.
-Is this for me? Okay. -Yeah.
I'm sorry about that.
Oh, I, uh...
got this for you on my way here today.
What am I supposed to do with this?
What are you talking about?
-Wow. Okay.
-That right there, you take that
and you light somebody's ass up with.
You hear me? You just
spray them in the eye with that,
and you zap them in the balls with that.
-This is like self-defense 101. -Thank you.
And you use that for any and all bus rides,
or at least until you get a car.
-Bus rides, car, got it. -Yeah.
Thank you for these.
You just can't stop being a hero, can you?
Oh, oh. Matter of fact, I've
got something else for you.
-A book? -Yeah.
It's one of those self-help
inspirational joints.
It helped me make it
through some dark times.
Erik, I can't take this from you.
No, no, no. Please. I want you to... no.
I want you to take it.
I mean, besides, I've
read it a million times
and I should've had it memorized by now.
And it really
showed me how to look at things
in a positive light.
And I hope it does the same for you.
I don't know what to say.
You don't have to say anything.
Pain recognizes pain.
That's from the book.
See, we can't stop pain from happening,
but it is on us
to give it meaning and purpose.
Is now a good time for that story?
What are you talking about?
The why you're not happy with Helen story.
Um...
All right. You gotta keep
this between you and I.
Of course.
All right.
So, um, legally, we are...
we're married,
but we've been separated for about a year.
I'm living in the basement right now.
-It's a little cold down there. -Yeah.
Uh, and about a year ago...
Helen had an affair with a bigwig
at a hotel conference.
I wanted a divorce.
She refused to give it to me.
Why, if she's the one who had the affair?
I don't know. She
said, "Oh, it's a mistake.
We can get past this."
Helen is about control, you know?
And we planned to come here
to build our own thing together,
but somewhere along the way,
she just got greedy.
Okay. So if you're always working,
she's always working,
she's greedy, all that stuff,
who's taking care of Phoebe?
Helen's even crazier a mother.
But I will say she loves Phoebe,
so it keeps Phoebe away
from Helen and my
daily drama.
-Daily drama? -Yes. Uh-hmm.
Hmm.
Why don't you just leave her?
Because...
she holds all the cards.
She's got the good job,
makes all the money,
great benefits, the whole nine.
She's always threatening
with custody battle.
And I know I couldn't take being away...
a day, not a week, not a month
being away from my baby girl.
I couldn't deal with that.
She can't do that. That's illegal.
You don't understand.
The woman Helen is now
is not the woman I married.
Well, at least I thought it was
and she did a good job at hiding it.
Either way,
the only thing Helen cares about more
than our daughter is control.
And she'll do whatever it takes to get it.
So you're just stuck?
Maybe until Phoebe is old enough,
then I can explain my side of the story.
Yeah. I mean, until we get there then,
then I'll be free.
I know how that feels.
Being held...
captive and hostage by somebody
who once said they loved you.
You know, the powerlessness that you feel
when you realize that you're their puppet
and they can pull those
strings at any moment.
It's painful.
- Yeah. -
Oh, somebody's got a phone now.
Whoa.
I gotta go back to work.
Oh. See, now you gotta
learn how it works around here.
You gotta check out
where all the cameras are
so when folks are on break,
you can get away when you wanna get away.
-I'm working on it. -All right.
All right. Are you coming?
No. I would, um...
sit here for a little while longer.
-The moon's right there. -Yeah. Beautiful.
Thank you for everything.
Anytime, love.
Thanks.
I forgot my Mace.
What?
Hey. Are you okay? -
- Oh, you're drunk. -
- Okay. Come on. -Just do me a favor.
- Take me to one of the... - Okay.
- Empty rooms. - One... okay.
I'm sorry to... Okay. Okay.
Wait, wait. Are we
supposed to get into the pool?
- No. No pool. -
-Okay. I have my trunks.
-You're not swimming.
Are you okay? -Oh, boy. Yeah.
-Oh. -Oh...
-Let's get you to a bed. -Oh, that's...
-Okay. It's a bed.
-perfect. This is fluffy.
-Yes. Yes. Get in there. -Oh, God.
Oh, oh, come.
-Oh, my God. -I'm sorry.
-I'm so sorry. No, no, no. -No, no, no.
-You don't have to go. No.
-No. I really... please.
-You... stay... no. -I'm so sorry. No.
-Come... -Please get some rest.
-You can... -I'm sorry.
You can just come here.
It's okay. We can just...
Um, listen. I'm so sorry.
I know I owe you an apology for last night.
- No. - No, no.
Listen, you were drunk and I...
-No, listen. -I'm so sorry.
Listen, the only thing I'm sorry about
is we didn't get to finish what we started.
Um, I always say there's no better time
like the present.
Um...
Shh.
Oh, shit.
Girl, I'm telling you, one day,
Helen is gonna mess with the wrong one.
What happened?
Girl, she tried to go
off on me for being late.
And I'm like...
she's always late.
I've been in there doing
the most, doing everything.
She don't appreciate
nothin'. I'm sick of it.
Why are you letting her stress you out?
Oh, my goodness.
Just go home and relax
and I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
Wait, what you mean? I
thought I was taking you home.
Paris, I need to get used
to taking the bus again.
And there's no better
time like the present.
-What? Are you sure? -Yeah. Uh, it's fine.
Are you sure? -I'm positive. Thank you.
All right. Well, let me know
when you make it home, okay?
-I will. Bye. Thank you.
-Bye, girl. All right.
Wait!
Fuck.
♪ One heart, one love ♪
- Hi. - Get in.
♪ We rise, we shine, one love ♪
-I just missed the bus.
-I know. Get in. I got you.
♪ The voice and mine
let the world feel it ♪
-Thank you. -You're welcome.
You just happen to be
driving by the bus stop.
-I mean, this is what I do. -Huh.
Put your seatbelts on.
We're safe drivers here.
-Okay. Good to go? -All right.
-Thank you. -All right.
Listen.
What we did earlier...
Yeah? -
Don't get me wrong, okay? It was amazing.
But I think that it needs
to be a one-time thing.
-Okay. -That's it, okay?
I mean, I don't know
what you want me to say.
We both have so much going on.
You know, me with my
mom and you with your wife.
Yeah. Yeah, you hit the nail on the head.
-That's true. Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
-Right? Okay.
So I think that we should stop this
before we get started.
You agree?
Sure.
You don't look like you agree.
I do. I...
I'm all for it if that's what you want.
Ooh. Where are you going?
Erik, my... you just...
Erik, you missed my... that was my street.
Just relax. I got you.
We just talked about this.
- I know. -What are you doing?
Just relax. Just relax.
It'll be all good.
In the Bible, do you know why
the forbidden fruit was so tempting?
- Because it was forbidden. - No.
It was because taking a bite of the fruit
gave knowledge and awareness.
And it showed Adam and Eve a part of them
that they've never seen before,
or could never unsee again.
That's what you've done for me.
You have opened my eyes to the possibility
that I could be happy again
with you.
And I can't let that be a one-time thing.
I won't.
Cass, you...
are my forbidden fruit,
and I wanna consume you over...
-Erik... -...and over,
and over again.
Enjoy it.
Girl. Hey, you've been
glowin' around here lately.
What? I don't... I have no
idea what you're talking about.
Of course, you don't.
Them extra-long breaks you've been takin',
you don't think I notice?
Who is it? You don't tell me?
You think I'm telling you anything?
Yes. Tell me. I ain't no snitch.
-Yes, you are. No. -I'm your girl.
-It's... bye. Hmm.
-Uh-hmm. No sneaky stuff.
Oh, Helen.
What are you doing here so late?
Just checking on you
and some of the other night staff.
Oh, uh, we're good.
No complaints here.
Good. Right, complaints.
Speaking of, I did receive a complaint
from one of the acquaintance
of Naudia's being a little too forward
with the staff members here.
Really?
Have you had any issues with her
or any of her "friends" at all?
I... no. She's been super cool with me
and I haven't really interacted
with any of her "friends."
So I don't know.
Okay. Good.
What about the other employees?
What do you mean?
Have you noticed Naudi and her friends
being inappropriate with
any of your other employees?
Um, I really... I haven't noticed anything.
Okay.
Good. Huh. All right.
Well, I'll let you get to it.
-Okay. -Oh, speaking of,
have you seen Erik?
I haven't been able to get him
on my cell.
Um, no.
I think he's already gone for the day, no?
Apparently not.
-His car's still out there.
-Oh, I didn't realize.
-I don't know. -Okay. Well, good.
He must be around here somewhere.
So, you have a good night.
-Uh-hmm. -And get home safely.
Thank you.
Dr. Smith, what are you doing here?
Good morning, Cassandra.
Did you forget about our
in-house appointment today?
Oh, my God.
It must've slipped my mind.
I'm so sorry. Please. Please come in.
Did I... did I come at a bad time?
No, no, not at all.
I was just making
breakfast for my mom and I.
Oh, good. So your mother's...
Oh, she's still sleeping, you know?
Well, we don't wanna disturb her.
-Where can we sit?
-Please come in. Have a seat.
Can I get you something
to eat? Any coffee or tea?
Actually, I wouldn't mind
a cup of coffee. Thank you.
Coming right up.
Here you go.
Okay.
Cassandra, I don't wanna
take up too much of your time.
I just wanted to check in with you
and see how well you're transitioning.
So, how are things going at work?
Oh, uh, good.
Good actually, really, really good.
Really? That's good to hear.
Yeah. I really... I really
love working there.
My coworkers, you know, I really...
they've really gone out of their way
to make me feel welcomed.
You know, that I...
that I feel like I...
belong.
Like a family, you know?
-That's amazing. -Yeah.
Glad to hear it's going well.
So, how are things here with your mother?
How are you two getting along?
Uh, as well as you can expect.
You know, she's...
got her moments and,
of course, I have mine.
But we're managing.
Are you finding it difficult
taking care of her at all?
Not as hard as you would think.
I mean, it's different.
Yes.
But A.J., her assistant,
does the heavy lifting.
Has that brought up any
past trauma, memories?
You know, I realized that
all that time that you had to work with me,
I was able to accept my past
or process it.
And I realized that my mom,
she hasn't had the same amount
of care and attention, you know?
And I can see it in her eyes, you know,
that she...
all the loss and all
the pain is still there.
That's understandable.
So do you feel that it could be impacting
your relationship with her at all?
Hmm, I think I can help her in time.
-Uh-hmm. -Just like you helped me.
Yes, time.
Last thing is I just
need to check your meds
before I go and I'll be off.
-My meds? -Yes.
It's mandatory that I check
your prescription bottle for consistency.
-You have it? -Yeah. Yeah. I can go get it.
Here, sorry.
-No worries. -I had to check on Mommy.
-Everything all right?
-Looks good. I'll take it.
Okay.
Cassandra, I'm happy that all these things
are going well for you.
Again, if you need
or you feel overwhelmed about anything,
please feel free to call me.
I will. Thank you.
-Thank you. -All right.
Uh, I will see you next appointment.
Tell your mother I said hi.
And hopefully, I'll get
to meet her next time.
Absolutely. I will. Thank
you so much, Dr. Smith.
Thanks.
Who the hell was that?
It was my doctor. She had an appointment.
You didn't tell me about
a damn appointment.
I'm sorry, I forgot. I forgot to tell you.
You had that woman in my
house with it looking like this?
-I think it looks fine.
-You think? You think?
You need to have a
brain to be able to think.
Look at that. Look at that.
That light switch is
filled with fingerprints.
-Look at it. Look at it! -I'm sorry, Mom.
All the light switches in the
house they look the same.
I need all the light switches
in the house spotless.
-Okay. -Do you hear me?
-Yes. -Spotless!
Now where's my goddamn breakfast?
- I want it now. -
I want it now.
Hey.
Look, um...
we, uh...
we gotta cool off for a while.
Like, Helen is starting to get suspicious.
Oh, my God.
Is that why she showed up the other night?
I believe so.
That woman is the bane of my existence.
I believe her only purpose in this life
is to make my life a living hell.
Listen, I don't... listen.
I'm not afraid of her, Erik, okay?
I've been around people
like her my entire life.
And she's just a bully,
and I'm not... I'm not scared.
Maybe we should just tell her.
Oh, no, no, no, no, we can't do that.
-No, we're not doing that. No. -We can...
No, we can get new jobs, we can move,
we can make sure that she
doesn't take your daughter...
No, no, no, you don't understand, Cass.
What is there not to understand?
You already told me
you're not in love with her.
What are you afraid of?
I'm afraid of her.
You don't understand.
Like, Helen is not as mean as you think.
She's worse.
She's vindictive
and she would not stop at just
trying to take Phoebe from me.
She'd try to figure out
a way to make your life
a living hell because that's who she is.
I don't care especially
when everything else
in my life feels like crap.
You're the only peace that I have,
and I don't wanna lose you.
-Please. No, no, no, no. -Okay. Okay. Look.
All right. Okay. No, no, relax, wait.
Listen.
Just because I said cool it,
doesn't mean we're done, okay?
You will never lose me. Look at me.
You will never lose me, okay?
Okay. Okay.
I just don't want her messing with you
the way she is messing
with everything else in my life.
I'm gonna figure out a
way for us to be together.
-All of us. -Okay.
You, me, and Phoebe.
Okay.
But it's gotta be on my time
-and you gotta trust me, okay? -Okay.
-Do you trust me? -I trust you.
-You trust me? -I trust you.
-Do you trust me, baby? -Yeah.
♪ Keeping on kicking, yeah ♪
Mommy?
Mommy, what are you doing?
Wait. What is this? What are you doing?
These memories are hell, Cass.
You know, I marry an evil guy.
Mommy.
Listen, to this. I don't
want Dad's history.
You shouldn't forget him! You
should have to remember him!
Well, you should remember him.
Erik, what are you doing here?
Hey.
After our conversation,
I just wanted to come by
and check on you to
make sure you were okay.
I walked by your house
and then your mom answered the door.
You spoke to my mom?
Yeah, for a second.
What? Did she say awful things about me?
-What did she say to you?
-No, uh, not at all.
She just said you left.
It was after midnight
and buses stopped running.
And I figured you
couldn't go too far on foot.
Are you okay?
I can't keep doing this with her.
Why? What's the matter? What happened?
Do you remember the fire I told you about?
Yeah. Yeah.
It wasn't a gas leak.
What happened?
My father was a drunk
and he abused me
and my mom physically and emotionally,
but me more.
And my mom used to say things like,
"We all have to make
sacrifices for the family."
One night, she caught my
dad sneaking out of my room
and she realized what
a monster he really was.
And they got into this huge fight
and she was burning all of his things
and she lit the house on fire.
Where were you?
I was in my bedroom.
I heard them screaming
and I was just terrified to move.
My mom managed to get
me out of the house but...
she tried going back in for my father.
And, um...
that's when the wooden beam fell on her.
Oh, God.
Cass, I...
My life has been filled
with unrequited love.
Everyone that I've ever cared
about, including my own parents,
refused to give me the same affection,
and I don't know why.
I guess my mom's way of making it up to me
was getting me out of the
fire, but she still blames me
for my father's death.
Cass...
listen, I can't imagine what that was like,
what you've been going
through, holding that guilt
for all these years.
And you shouldn't feel
like you're all alone in love.
I love you.
And I'm always here for you.
Always.
-Do you hear me? Always. -Yes.
I see somebody. Somebody's watching us.
What? Where? What are you talking about?
Yeah, by the tree, right over there.
-No, no, you're seeing things.
-No, no, no. It's right there.
Listen, I have to get back home.
My mom's gonna be up
soon and I just... I need...
I need to go home.
I have to go home.
Okay.
-I'll take you home. Okay? -Okay.
-I'll give you a ride. -Okay.
- Come on. -
What happened? Did you hear anything
or see anything?
-What's going on?
-Oh, my God, Cass. Naudi...
-Why? -Naudi is dead.
They found her in an
alley across the street.
Oh, my God.
What?
Hey guys,
Detective Shaw and
Detective Thomas would like
to have a word with some of you.
So day shift,
if you could please hang
around for a little while,
if you can.
I see that you all are busy here,
so we won't take up much of your time.
If you don't mind, we'd
like to ask a few of you
some questions individually
regarding Mrs. Mycenae's
comings and goings.
Uh, we'd love to start with
Ms. Cassandra Tanner.
Yeah. Yes, of course.
I'd like to reassure you that
the man who assaulted you
is still locked up.
Oh, thank you for that.
Um, but this means
that there's someone else
in the area that's attacking women?
Apparently so.
Let me ask you.
Are you sure you were the only one
in the alley the night you got assaulted?
I don't... I'm not sure.
Um, I think I was
but it was a very chaotic
night, so I don't remember.
All right. Please take care my card, okay?
Do not hesitate to call us if
you... if you need anything,
-all right? -Okay.
Ms. Tanner, if you don't mind, excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Wait, hold on.
Does this picture mean something to you?
Uh, I don't... I don't
think so. Is that, um...
Apparently, this is
something that the assailant
was wearing and fell off of them.
Does it look familiar to you?
I don't think so.
-Thank you, Ms. Tanner.
-Thank you. Thank you.
Erik.
That's a little suspicious.
This is weird. How did she
know? And why did she pick
-this picture up?
-Unless she knows something.
I'm telling you, I'm telling you,
I'm telling you, it's the same tassel.
Do you know which one I'm talking about?
-No, not really. -It's the same tassel
from that letter opener
that Helen has in her office.
Uh, how can you be
sure if you only saw the pic
-for a few seconds?
-I know what I saw, okay?
And it's the same tassel
from her letter opener.
-Okay? -Uh, listen, I...
look, Helen is capable
of a lot of things, all right?
-But I'm not sure about murder.
-Why are you defending her?
Because no matter how I feel about her,
she is still my daughter's mother.
And I'm not gonna jump to conclusions
without any proof.
Listen, what reason would she have
to kill Naudi?
Think about it, okay?
We've been spending all this time
in this hotel together.
And you yourself, you told me,
you told me that she was
getting suspicious, right?
What if... what if she
thought that you were sleeping
with Naudi and not me,
and that's why she killed her?
-Damn, Cass. -Exactly.
But I do need proof.
So I'm gonna go get the letter opener
-from her office.
-Okay. No, wait. Listen, look,
you're gonna need the
key to get to her office.
All right? And I'll try to distract her.
And you go now and I'll text
you when she's coming back.
-Okay. -Cass, be careful
because if any of what
you're saying is true,
-we could be in serious trouble. -I know.
-Okay. Be careful. -I know.
-Be careful. -Okay.
-Can I help you? -Oh, Helen,
I was looking for you and I... I'm sorry.
-I just came in to find a...
-Oh, that's funny
because I could've swore I locked the door.
No. No, no, it was unlocked.
-I'm sorry. I just...
-What are you doing?
Are you looking to open mail or something?
Yeah. Yes. Well, no.
Uh, one of the guests
asked me for a letter opener
and I just... I came in
here to find yours to...
Really?
What room?
Uh, 312.
Cass, two things.
One, no one enters into my office
when I'm not here.
It's a hard rule of mine.
Some may call it territorial
but it's really for everyone's safety.
There are way too many
confidential documents
for the hotel and we don't wanna raise
the suspicion of trust, now do we?
No, no, not at all.
Good.
And two,
we don't wanna get in habit of giving
our guests sharp items.
We do not want them
inadvertently hurting themselves
or someone else and then suing us.
You've seen what happened to Naudi.
It's most likely that the
killer has been here before.
Hell,
it's a possibility that they might be here
right now as we speak.
Can you imagine
giving some sick degenerate
something this sharp?
No.
Good.
I mean, I'm not one to judge but...
someone like Naudi in that line of work,
sleeping with all those people husbands,
something was bound to
happen to her sooner or later.
So...
until the killer is found,
let's try to prioritize
our safety over services.
Do you understand?
Yes, I know.
You smell so intoxicating.
Very... familiar.
I feel like I should get back to work.
Excuse me.
You do that.
Her killer has been here before.
I love you.
For all we know,
they could be right here, right now.
Cassandra!
Mommy!
Mommy?
Oh, my God.
Mommy.
Mommy?
Mommy!
- Oh, my God. Mommy. -
Just what the hell you
think you're doing, huh?
Mommy, I'm sorry. I heard you...
You're walking all around
making all this noise.
I need to sleep, dammit!
I thought I heard you. I'm...
You thought! You thought!
Cassandra, I can't deal
with you tonight, okay?
I need to sleep, dammit!
Shut the door! I need to sleep!
Shut the door! Now!
Okay.
Mommy, it's time for breakfast.
It's your favorite.
- Hey. Sorry, I'm in a rush. - Hey.
I have an errand to run before work.
Okay. How is she today?
Uh, she's in a mood.
Probably best if you stay out of her way.
Okay. Have a good day.
As we close this meeting,
we wanna make sure that we are keeping
the lobby clean.
Every per...
it's nice for you to finally join us, Cass.
Okay, folks, that is
all I have for you today.
Dayshift, have a good one.
Nightshift, go ahead and get to it, okay?
All right.
Make sure you're here on time.
Girl, why are you late?
Have you seen Erik?
They said he called in sick.
Why?
-Oh, damn. -Damn what?
Paris, I need to borrow your car.
Excuse me?
I can't explain to you, but it's...
Girl, you know Helen
is already on a warpath.
It's an emergency, okay?
Look, I think something
might have happened to Erik,
and I just need to make sure.
Please, just let me
borrow your car, please.
I don't know if that's a good idea.
Paris, please, let me
borrow your car keys. Please.
Girl, do you even know how to drive?
-Paris, give me...
-Girl, girl, you're tripping,
but I don't know what
you got going on, but, um...
-Thank you. -...do what you need to do.
-Thank you. Was it that hard? -All right?
I mean, you lucky I got insurance.
-Yes? Can I help you? -Hi. Hi. Hello.
Uh, is Erik home?
Well, uh, I'm Leto, his mother.
Is there something I can help you with?
Oh, I'm so sorry, ma'am.
This is not at all how I dreamed
of eventually meeting you,
but I really need to speak to your son.
Is he here?
No, sugar. He's not.
His wife told me he'll be out of town
for the next few days.
- Oh, God. - I'm sorry.
I didn't catch your name.
Oh, God.
Hello?
Answer the phone.
Hello, Cass.
Helen?
Where's Erik?
Come find him.
No. I'm going to the police.
And tell them what?
My husband, who you've been screwing,
is not returning your calls?
I'll tell them about Naudi.
And I'll show them security footage
of you breaking into my office
and say it wasn't your first time.
Do you think they'll be more
likely to believe you, psycho?
What? - That's right.
I know all about your little
stay in the mental hospital
and your affinity for
sharp objects on your wrist.
So, like I said,
if you want to find my husband,
come back to work, and you better hurry.
He might not be alive much longer.
Tick-tock.
Don't touch him!
Don't you fucking touch him!
Girl, Helen is looking for you.
I only cover for you for so long.
And what's up with Erik?
Uh, I don't... I didn't...
I never meant to get involved.
-I never... -Are you okay?
Because you're freaking me out.
Cassandra, please come to the third floor
east wing immediately.
Cassandra, come to
the third floor east wing.
Thank you.
Listen, Paris.
The maintenance room?
Girl, I told you she was looking for you.
Paris, if I'm not back here in 10 minutes,
I need you to call the police, okay?
The police? Girl, you're tripping.
-What's going on?
-Look, I know it sounds crazy.
You've been getting in
with Erik, haven't you?
When did this start?
I'm usually good at picking up on stuff.
I don't have time to explain to you. Okay?
But I think that Helen killed Naudi.
She's been stalking me for days,
and now I think that she's
done something to Erik.
What? That's crazy.
I know. I know. It sounds crazy...
- Crazy. -...but that's...
I just... can you just promise me
that you're gonna call the police, please?
Okay. I got you.
I repeat, Cassandra,
please come to the third floor east wing.
Do you copy?
Tick-tock.
I'm coming.
Okay. 10 minutes.
Okay, girl.
She's tripping.
Helen?
Helen.
Helen, where are you?
Helen, there's a hotel full of people.
Thanks for the reminder.
What did you do to him?
What did you do?
Looks like you found him.
- Helen. -
Hey, y'all seen Cass and Helen?
Helen!
Helen! Helen!
Please, what are you
doing, Cassandra? Please!
Police! Get on the ground!
Freeze! Freeze! Hands behind your head!
It's her. It was her.
You have to believe me.
Come on, Ms. Tanner.
Walk us through all this.
How did this start?
The human mind is very complex.
Science has shown us time and time again
that a person's subconscious mind
can actively work to
protect the conscious mind
without that person even
being aware it's doing so.
It can happen through blocked memories,
disassociation, or even creating fantasies
so realistic that the conscious mind
is unable to tell dream from reality.
Is that what we're dealing with here?
Cassandra Tanner was diagnosed
with suffering from paranoid
schizophrenia as a teen,
but with regular medication
and therapy, it was manageable.
From my knowledge, she hadn't
had an episode in many years.
She was one of my brightest patients
at the behavioral institution.
Just what the fuck...
And that's why we approved her release.
At some point, she must
have stopped taking her meds.
Yeah. Her toxicology report shows
that there are no
antipsychotics in her system.
So tell us about the affair.
I don't know.
I only know what I was told.
I guess Helen found
out about Cass and Erik?
Affair?
There was never any affair.
Never.
I just... I just spoke to her a few times.
Uh, I'm about to close up in a few.
Okay. One night, uh, she got mugged,
and I jumped in and I stopped it,
and I gave her a ride home after that.
And after that, it was...
it was business as usual.
And she just seem like one of those sad,
shy, scared woman who
is afraid to talk to anyone.
And that's what I got from it.
Well, we believe that
that's when she became
infatuated with you,
the night you saved her.
Oh, no.
Uh-hmm.
And that's why we believe
she killed Ms. Naudia Mycenae.
And your wife, Helen,
we believe that's when she was lured
to a part of the hotel
to talk about your supposed affair,
and that's when Ms.
Tanner attacked your wife.
Please, what are you doing,
Cassandra? Please! Please.
Can you tell us about the fire?
That was a tragic night for Cassandra.
And so that's when her father
Hector killed himself, right?
No. You don't understand.
Cassandra killed her
father in self-defense,
lit the fire to cover it up.
Her father sexually abused her.
Why didn't her mother help her?
I don't know.
Love? The inability to
cope with her own reality?
Maybe she was being abused herself.
But either way, that
young girl eventually felt
the need to take matters
into her own hands.
So I guess what we're
trying to understand is why.
Was there tension building
between Cassandra and her mother?
No. There couldn't have been.
Mommy?
I thought you could enjoy
some breakfast in bed.
Hija, thank you.
It's okay.
I understand.
Enjoy.
How do you know?
You couldn't have been there 24/7.
I mean, maybe her mother was tryna...
Because Evelyn Tanner can't move.
She's paralyzed from the neck down.
So she's quadriplegic?
Yes. I've been her nurse for that long.
From what I've been told,
it happened the night of the fire.
Something fell on Mrs. Tanner's neck
and fractured her spine.
She has been bedridden ever since.
Who the hell was that?
Look at that. Look at that.
That light switch is full of fingerprints.
I'm sorry.
- Hey. - Hey.
Sorry, I'm in a rush.
I have an errand to go run before work.
Okay. Is she doing okay?
Uh, she's in a mood.
Probably best if you stay out of her way.
Okay. Have a good day.
Oh, my God. Ev?
What? Evelyn, no.
No, Evelyn. Ev, wake up.
Evelyn, please.
Please wake up. Oh, my God.
I've never seen anything like that.
There was so much blood.
So much.
This must have been her plan from day one.
Convince you that she was
fine so you could release her,
and she could go back to what she was doing
all those years ago.
Unfortunately, she fell
in love along the way.
I suppose so.
At the end of the day, I
guess this is all my fault.
Oh, God. I should have known.
I didn't know.
Cassandra was my patient.
I advocated for her with the review board.
I made the call to my brother
and I asked him for a favor.
I knew his wife Helen would help.
Oh, God. What have I done?
Do you have any idea what
you've done, Cassandra?
Look, I'm not going for
your little loony bin crap.
What you did took cunning planning.
I need to hear you say it.
Do you have any idea what you've done?
Yes, I do.
I finished my fairy tale.
And in my fairy tale,
the monsters get to win, so I won.
I won.
I win. I win!