Agents say that this deadly drug
has a street value of $275,000.
Authorities are saying that
agents conducted a search
warrant at a Jackson Housing
Projects on Tuesday,
April 24th.
There, they seized
496.5 grams
of powder fentanyl,
11,976 dosage units
of counterfeit M30s,
17 firearms,
and audio-video
surveillance equipment.
I'm Vanessa Young reporting,
South Jackson.
Shit, shit.
Nigga, please.
-Hey, please, man. It's mine.
-You stupid, man.
Hey, where you going?
This is mine, man.
Hey, it's Mateo.
He's rollin' up.
You are late.
Somebody is skimming.
It's AJ.
That Somali lone wolf.
But I just texted him
done and told him
to get his ass down here.
Take care of that pendejo...
or it comes out of you.
-All right, boss.
-Entiendes?
We'll get it straight.
Why'd you tell Mateo that?
Say, who else could it be?
Look, bro. We gonna
have to take it out of
his ass, so they don't
take it out of ours.
Say, guys, look, somebody
been stealing product.
Y'all know what that mean.
Mateo not playing.
What if you're wrong?
Man, I ain't never wrong.
What's up right there?
-Yo, what up?
-Just working.
'Sup, man?
Word is, your ass been stealing.
I ain't take nothing.
Yo.
Is this bullshit
why y'all call me out here?
Mateo ain't say nothing to me.
-So, go fuck yourself.
-Man, you ain't part of
this motherfucking crew.
Man, you just jealous
'cause I'll sell you bitches
any day.
Yo, cuz, what you doing?
You better get him.
You with us or what?
Yeah.
Hey, yo, I'mna take
care of this for Mateo.
Hey.
Move away.
Yeah, you a real tough guy
with that gun.
Come on.
Who the fuck this guy is?
There you go.
Shoot.
Man...
you don't look too good.
I think you need to
change careers. What you think?
Let this moment be your rebirth.
Go on, get out of here.
The county has allocated
resources to the DA's office
to assist in curtailing
the criminal drug enterprise
which has spread fentanyl
from Jackson all the way
through small surrounding towns
right here in Madison County.
Ahmed Jama, goes by AJ,
Somali-American,
broke off from the Somali.
Outlaw Gang in Minneapolis
and migrated here.
AJ reports to Columbian
Lieutenant Mateo Ramirez,
and all report
to Demetrius Barkley,
the head of the snake.
Now, Demetrius
is a master puppeteer.
He never gets his hands dirty
and he's rarely ever seen.
Alonzo Young and Trevor Sears,
they run the most lucrative
street operation
and they oversee numerous
foot soldiers.
Now, these photos
are just the most current
that we have,
but I am pretty sure
that Mateo's been grooming
these two for a while now.
They look like kids.
Yeah, lots of them
practically are kids.
But look, do not underestimate
-these guys.
-Absolutely.
You'll work as a dedicated
team out of my office
until you can get me
enough evidence to prosecute
and put these men away.
Where do they get their product?
From Mateo's Columbian
connection through Miami.
Danny?
We've been surveilling
Trev Sears
and Alonzo Young for a while,
and finally paid off.
They took us to what we believe
is their
main stash house
which is where they break down
and re-package
all the shit they sell.
From what I understand, the.
Columbian product is a
good quality.
Uh, it is,
but they step on it a... a lot.
They cut it with benzocaine,
baby laxative, aspirin.
They get it nice and fluffed up,
and then they enhance
the effects with
just a little bit of fentanyl.
It's called Tombstone on the
streets around here. It's cheap
-and a powerful high.
-And keeps 'em comin' back.
They know just what it takes
to hook 'em but not kill them.
But there is zero
quality control.
I mean, it's basically
Russian roulette.
They've got random
low-level guys in and out,
cuttin' the drugs,
and two milligrams
of error can kill an adult
in less
than two minutes
from respiratory failure.
That's why this office is ready
to prosecute every single
drug trafficker that
comes through here.
Which brings me to you.
What's the plan?
It appears they get
a large weekly shipment.
They vary on the
delivery days, but
we got that part figured out.
We've never
seen Demetrius on site,
but Mateo oversees
the weekly sort
and our CIs will let us know
when the next drop is scheduled.
And once we know
when the drop is,
we'll have about 24 hours
to catch Mateo there
while they're doing the sort.
And Demetrius?
He stays at arm's length,
you'll never catch him.
But we think Mateo may give
him up to save his own ass.
It's the only thing we can
do at the moment.
Alright.
Let's hope that Danny
and Cisco are right.
Like I said, you'll work
out of this office.
I'll be right in here for
any support that you need.
And most important,
remember this,
our work here is confidential.
You're dismissed.
Now coming
to the stage, Serenity.
I wanna see everybody
put their dollars up.
Let's go.
I know y'all feeling good
out there, come on.
You here to see Demetrius?
This way.
How much for a lap dance, baby?
I understand you
boys were light last night.
Man, like I told Mateo, it's AJ.
Man, that Somalian motherfucker
been skimming.
But I handled it,
like I told you I would.
I beat the shit
out of that fool.
-Yeah, for sure.
-Bet he never steals
from y'all again.
My eyes on the street say you
started a job,
but didn't finish.
What do you say?
Why you ain't finish him off?
I pay you two to
take care of business.
Trev's telling it straight.
He was about to cut him down
when some bad dude swooped in
like Black Panther or something.
-Is this true?
-I swear to God.
You know about this?
I'm just hearing about it now.
So, who this Black Panther
work for?
Oh, we don't know.
We been asking around, but...
ain't nobody seen
his ass before.
Call Hawk and Jayboy.
See what they know.
I'm gonna be checking
on your story.
You better not be bullshitting.
Now get to work.
Hey,
you see him again,
I gotta hear about it first,
understand?
-A'ight.
-For sure.
You believe this
bullshit from them?
I don't know yet.
They're not stupid enough
to make up a story like that.
Don't look at them.
They're just trying
-to intimidate us.
-Well, it's working.
Put on your
big girl panties, Remi.
You said you wanted
to do real journalism.
I mean, this is real. all right.
Ready?
Yeah.
Camera's rolling.
Well, I'm standing in what
used to be a typical
suburban neighborhood.
The sounds of children's
laughter from playing
once filled these streets,
but now these homes
have been abandoned
by their former residents and
replaced by some of the city's
busiest trap houses infested
with addicts
-and the homeless.
-Girl, let me talk to you for a minute.
Keep rolling.
-That's a nice camera, white boy.
-Although drug use is
not a new problem,
the drugs that are being
manufactured today,
they are very different.
Fentanyl,
it's a national epidemic.
-The hell you say?
-Hey, say, cuz,
you better go get your sis.
Hey, Vanessa!
Stop rolling.
Alonzo, get off me.
You crazy? You can't
just come up
-in here like that.
-I am doing my job!
This is my block and you
can't bring cameras here.
Don't think you can
intimidate me, boy. I raised you.
Come on, Nessa,
don't do this here.
Am I embarrassing you?
You are embarrassing the memory
of our mama and daddy.
-Vanessa!
-Hey! Hey!
-Get away from him!
-Are you trying to get
-yourself killed?
-Let him go!
-No!
-No. Vanessa, Nessa!
Yo!
Why don't y'all just go home?
Damn.
-Who is that?
-I don't know.
-He's a bad dude though.
-Man, fuck that.
Y'all done?
Get y'all asses outta here.
Hey, come on,
let's go. Let's go!
Remi, are you okay?
How's your leg?
Leg's fine.
I just... I hope
the camera's okay.
Don't worry about the camera.
-You guys okay?
-Well, uh... we don't want
-any trouble, we're leaving.
-We're fine. Let's go.
Hey.
I seen you on TV.
What do you want,
my autograph or something?
What did you do to me?
Gave you new life,
a near godlike power.
You'll have the ability
to heal within minutes.
Your muscles will be stronger,
your reflexes faster.
Why did you choose me?
To become the beast that
feeds on the hearts
of evil men.
-You're hurting me!
-I'm tired of tracking your ass.
-Get... get over here.
-You're hurting me!
I'm tired of y'all.
Get your ass in the car.
-You get your ass in the car.
-No, no, no!
-Hey!
-What?
The hell, you...
Baby, I'll take you
around the world.
It's on the house.
-What's your name?
-Chelsea.
Chelsea...
find a new line of work.
Y'all hurry up with this batch.
I'm try in a' poke somethin'.
-Hey, man, you hear that?
-Bro, you getting sleepy?
I don't hear shit.
Man, that's what I'm saying,
man. Something ain't right.
You're just saying that
'cause Black Superman
-beat your ass up.
-Man, screw that!
-Yo, Trev.
-What's up?
-Look, AJ just called, we about to get hit.
-What?
-We need to go now.
-They gotta give us
-more of a warning than that.
-We lucky they told us at all.
Let's go, Cash.
-Come on, man.
-Pack this shit up.
-Get everything up.
-Pack everything.
What's going down?
Help us with this shit.
We gotta get out.
-Now.
-Move, move your ass!
They coming in
right now, come on!
-Hurry up, get the money.
-Come on, let's go, man.
-Bags, head outta here.
-Come on, come on!
Go, go, go!
Everybody get ready.
-Freeze!
-Ready?
Let's go!
Nobody move!
Freeze, freeze, freeze!
-Put your hands up.
-Everybody on the ground!
Everybody down!
Hands up, hands up,
hands up, hands up!
Put your hands up.
No one move.
-Go, go.
-Stop right there!
Go that way.
Put your hands up. Don't move.
Go that way!
Hands behind your back.
Hands up.
-Clear!
-Room clear!
-Stop, stop.
Put it down!
-Yo.
-Hey, say, cuz, where you at?
I'm rolling, bro.
What's up with you?
Bro, stuff's messed up, bro.
The spot got hit.
I need you, dawg.
Can you make it to
the other spot?
No, I can't get to
the other spot, bro.
I just told you stuff's
messed up out here.
I ain't going by myself.
Alright, alright.
Say less, man.
Meet me on Baker Street.
I'll roll with you.
A'ight bet.
But hurry up, dawg.
You have the
right to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you
in the court of law.
There's one of 'em.
And actually I do see
the captain right now.
Let me see if I can get
comment from him.
Excuse me, Captain.
Captain Cisco, please.
It's my understanding that
you and your team were
the first who were on scene.
You guys
went in, you took
out a couple of perps,
arrested some others.
Is that correct?
That's essentially correct.
Is it also true that you
recovered
guns, cash,
a large amount of fentanyl?
-I can't comment on that.
-Can you at least confirm that
this raid was a coordinated
effort with
the Justice Department?
I've said as much
as I can say at this time.
-Okay, Captain...
-Excuse me.
Well, as you can see behind me,
several arrests have been made.
We know two suspects are dead,
but of course, I will keep you
updated on the latest.
For now, I am Vanessa Young,
Action 4 You News,
reporting live, South Jackson.
-Clear?
-Yup.
Cisco, helpful as always.
It's that guy again.
-Who?
-The guy that...
He was right there.
The... the one who helped us.
Scares me.
And he's also kinda hot.
Uh... Okay.
You did a great job today.
Go home, get some rest.
We're back at it tomorrow, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Sit down and shut up.
You have the right
to remain silent...
What the fuck?
Do not scare people like that.
Who do you think you are? Blade?
Stop following me, please.
I wasn't following you
and I didn't mean to scare you.
I was trying to make sure you
got to your car safely.
Yeah, that's the lamest
pickup line I've ever heard.
I grew up in this neighborhood.
Okay?
I know how to handle myself
and I...
don't need a babysitter,
but, thank you.
Hey...
I just wanna help.
We on the same side.
And plus, I think your
work's important.
You're not afraid to tell
the people the truth
about what's happening out here.
I've lost a lot of people
I love to these drugs.
I'm not gonna lose another one.
So all this shit,
it's gotta stop.
The guy who pulled you aside
yesterday, you know him?
Yeah. Alonzo. He's my brother.
He's...
slinging the same stuff that
killed our dad, but...
I raised him better than
that, you wouldn't know it.
Yeah.
Well, I've been watching
that crew.
I think your brother's
being groomed.
I know.
And that's why
I gotta try to stop him
before he gets in any deeper.
Why are you out here?
Like I said, I'm just like you.
I wanna help.
I believe that if we expose
the gangs,
even the corruption
in this town,
you know, maybe...
you and me,
we can do something about it.
Put a stop to all of it.
Yeah, but...
they hide in the shadows.
I like the shadows.
Man, what the hell happened?
Man, bro, look.
Drug task force rolled in,
but, shit,
I got outta there
right before they busted in,
but I got outta there
with that right there.
Man, what you got?
Shit. Just some
weight of tombstone,
couple bands.
You got that from the house?
Yes, and?
The narcs was gonna
get it anyway.
Bro, we gotta start looking
out for ourselves.
So it was you?
You're the one that's taking
from our spots?
Man, don't nobody know.
Bro, you my cuz,
I'll cut you in.
You almost killed AJ
the other day
to cover your own ass?
Man, shut the hell up.
Put this bitch in drive.
What the hell happened tonight?
Months of surveillance
and all we got to show for it
is two dead low-level
gang members,
a couple of cutters and
a scumbag-nobody in custody?
-How you know he's a nobody?
-Beause everybody
that's a somebody got away.
-That's how I know.
-Hey, hey.
Maybe we'll get lucky
and one of 'em
will know something.
I mean, they all were there
-when it went down.
-Dwight, see what you can
get out of those three.
Hey, maybe offer 'em
a deal depending
on what they know.
Either our intel was bad
or they were tipped off...
or both.
They must've been tipped off,
'cause they were already running
and stashing stuff by the
time we got there.
What about this guy?
Who am I looking at?
This guy who saved
that reporter.
Yeah, yeah, this guy,
everywhere we show up,
he's already there.
But we've never seen him
make a buy.
We need to keep tabs on him
until we know more.
Cisco, my office, now.
Shit.
Why did I have to hear from
someone else about
tonight's debacle?
I was just about to tell you.
That raid was a fiasco.
I wanna know what happened
and how you intend to proceed
moving forward.
There's someone new
we wanna follow up on
who single-handedly saved
the reporter
and her cameraman the other day.
We're reviewing
surveillance photos.
-Do you have an ID on him?
-Not yet.
Well then, you get me
his picture and I'll see
what I can find out on my end.
There's something else.
We believe they may have
been tipped off.
What?
-How?
-I'm not sure.
-A leak?
Let me tell you something,
if there's a leak,
you better find it
and plug it fast,
no matter what it takes.
We have a problem.
One of the houses got hit.
I'm aware, and I'm
monitoring the situation.
They didn't get a call
in time to warn them!
That is your job.
You know, at our level
in this business,
or any business,
there's a certain poise,
emotional intelligence
and finesse that is required.
However, at the first sign
of complication,
you start bitch battling
and making accusations
like a little Medellín,
street urchin.
And that is how you panic
a bunch of little
street soldiers into thinking
they can take over
my operation.
You're not questioning
my position, are you?
Of course not.
I meant no disrespect.
I'm just trying to say
that if we don't jump
in front of this problem,
things could
get very complicated.
-For both of us.
-No.
You find out who's
stealing from me?
Yeah, AJ.
Street dealer,
worked his own corner.
He's been handled.
As the Bible say,
"You strain a gnat,
you swallow a camel."
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
You naive.
A street dealer appropriating
a gram here and there
is just the cost
of doing business.
If you do your job, those men
will be too terrified to abscond
with anything that will make
a significant impact
on our profits.
What are you saying?
We got another thief
whose misappropriation has made
a significant impact
on our bottom line.
So, let me know
when you find him.
I'll reestablish
some order around here,
put a personal touch
on the situation.
One more thing.
If you ever question me again,
I'll cut your heart out.
Hey.
I'm looking for a Mateo Ramirez.
Y'all know him?
Oh, I see.
You don't speak English.
Okay.
Let's try this a different way.
Hey, I'm Lazarus.
What are you doing?
Stop!
Babe, babe, are you okay?
No.
What did you do to me?
Trust me,
it could've been worse.
-It's nothing. No!
-Is this true?
Are you fucking that girl?
Sofia, I...
No.
-No.
Sofia!
Sof... So...
No.
You tell my girl that you
were just playing,
and you got a deal.
Deal.
Go get her.
Sofia!
Oh, shit!
Boss, I didn't know it was you.
Grab AJ.
Let's roll.
You disrespectful motherfucker.
Trev...
you really hurt me.
Did you really think
you wouldn't get caught?
Demetrius,
I'm trying to tell you,
I was just holding that
shit for you.
I wouldn't steal from you, man.
You blame your misappropriations
on one of my soldiers,
-No, D.
-who puts money in my pocket?
What do you know about this?
-I don't know anything.
-D, that's my cousin, man.
He don't know
nothing about this.
If he's your cousin,
then you're selfish and foolish,
dragging your own flesh
and blood in your own bullshit.
D, please, listen...
What are you saying?
Please...
Demetrius!
Hey, wait, man, come on.
Please, let him live.
That's my cousin for real.
Show 'em where my property is.
Leave, now.
The rest of you, outside.
D...
Come on, man,
give me one more chance.
-It's too late.
-D, come on, man.
There's no more chances for you.
D...
You a good man, Zo.
You're loyal.
And that's one thing
I'll never question.
You're too valuable to me
to let your fucked up cousin
take you down with him.
I'm your family now, huh?
Go on.
Gentlemen,
I believe you're all acquainted
with this vigilante
I keep hearing about.
What do we know about him?
Word on the street
is he can fight.
Yeah, and he's strong as hell.
Like, he just shows up.
He knows where we're gonna
be before we even get there.
No matter what we throw at him,
it don't faze him.
What do you say about it?
He saved my ass, man.
Told me I should change
careers or some shit.
What do they call him?
L... Lazarus?
I need you to find out
everything on this Lazarus.
We have a major shipment
coming in tomorrow.
I need all my crew.
This is a priority.
Tell your crew to stop selling,
cooking,
whatever the fuck you're doing.
A 100 grand to anybody
that can find me Lazarus.
Did anybody think of taking
a picture of this man?
I got one.
Send it to me.
Lazarus.
Today, in our continuing
coverage on urban decay,
we're focusing on the impact
that the drug crisis
in our community
has had on small businesses
that once thrived here.
-Okay?
-Good.
Great.
Thank you.
Yo, I think that's the guy.
Seriously?
Yeah, fool.
That's him.
Call it in.
I'll take care of him.
Great. Here's my stalker,
right on time.
I don't know if I should
be scared or flattered.
It's Ray Lazarus, by the way.
And I'm not the one you need
to be worried about.
Here we go again.
So you're saying
I need to be scared
of somebody else
-other than you?
-Yeah,
you bring a lot of attention
to things that people
wanna keep quiet.
What have you been watching?
Reruns of The Wire?
Bringing attention to things,
that is what I do.
-It is my job.
-I know and I understand.
Your work is important,
but right here, right now,
this spot where you are,
you could be
putting yourself in danger.
Y'all need to leave.
Lazarus!
Get inside.
Demetrius would like
to speak with you.
And I would like to speak
with you, Mateo.
Then we are in agreement.
You're coming with us.
Hey, hey. Get inside.
-Get inside.
-Whoa, whoa.
Get... Get... Get-
The hell is going on?
Okay.
Idiots!
Demetrius wanted him alive!
Get... get him!
Get him!
Hey, hey. Alonzo.
Alonzo.
Are you okay?
Ray, stop!
Okay, come on.
You're... You're hurt.
You need an ambulance.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
What you mean you're fine?
-How?
-Later for all that.
I just can't be here
when the cops come.
-Give me your phone.
-My phone?
-Phone!
-Remi.
Vámonos.
It's my number, if you need me.
Go!
Get your ass out of here!
Please take a look
at these photos
and let me know
if you can ID anyone.
These guys, they were there.
That's it?
Are you sure you
can't ID anyone else?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Excuse the interruption.
-Vanessa Young?
-Yes.
Assistant District Attorney
Alisha Page.
I know exactly who you are.
And I certainly know
who you are.
You keep popping up in places
we'd rather you not.
It's my job to show up
in those places.
I don't know
what your intent is,
but you're certainly ruffling
a lot of feathers on the street.
My intent is to shed enough
light on the endemic drug crime
in our community, so that way
sooner rather than later
we can take back our streets.
Well, we certainly share
the same goals.
We may even be able
to help one another.
In fact, I want you to
come back tomorrow morning
so that I can conduct
a thorough interview
after I've had the opportunity
to review today's events.
Then we can have
a detailed discussion.
Hmm?
And if I don't show?
Don't make me go there.
I distinctly remember saying
that I wanted to restore order,
and I don't see that happening!
We followed your plan,
but that pendejo
almost killed me.
I don't wanna hear that shit!
I pay an army of men that
got their asses handed to 'em
by that pendejo!
He... he ain't human.
What does it even mean?
He ain't lying.
He ain't human. Can't be.
He... he got shot in the chest
at pointblank range,
and still took down Mateo.
I thought he killed you.
I don't know what happened.
He put his hands on me and...
it felt like he was draining
my life... out of me.
I... I passed out.
Next thing I know,
I... I hear sirens
and I drag my ass out of there.
Alonzo, get out, I got...
business with these two.
Go on.
I hear Zo's sister
is becoming a big problem.
She was there.
She saw the whole thing.
I should've taken care of her.
But as a courtesy to Alonzo,
I'ma give her
one more chance...
to stop interfering.
I'm gonna give her a warning...
very convincing warning.
And that's you.
And it needs to happen
tonight, understood?
Understood.
Go.
You stay.
So, you're telling me he's more
powerful than just a man?
He took bullets to the chest...
and he didn't flinch.
Dinner was so good,
and I love talking to you.
My girlfriends think that
you are so cute,
and it's a big plus that you
haven't texted any of them.
Not sure what that means.
My girlfriends
and I, we're all single,
so we're all
on the same website,
and a lot of the same guys
will text us
and we'll compare notes.
Especially when they
use the same lines
and just cut
and paste it to a few of us.
People do that?
Wait, how many guys are you
-and your friends talking to?
-I mean...
you talk to
a whole bunch of guys
and then you narrow it down
to five or six, and then
you whittle that down to
two or three and then...
I'm gonna let you live...
this time,
but you need to keep
your mouth shut and back off.
-You understand?
-Yes.
Thursday.
Don't make me come back.
Just keep looking straight.
Hello?
-Ray?
-Hey.
Ray, it's... it's Vanessa.
Somebody just broke
into my apartment
-and threatened me.
-Uh, oh, okay.
I'm coming to you.
Give me your address.
37-15 Cadiz Circle.
-On my way.
-Hurry, please.
-Hello?
-It's me, Ray.
Okay, come in quickly, please.
-Is he... he still out there?
-No, no, no one's out there.
-You're safe.
-Okay. But I didn't see... I couldn't see his face
but he had a...
a knife to my throat,
and he
said for me to stop talking...
Look at me.
You're safe now.
I've got you, okay?
No one's gonna hurt you.
-Come on.
-Sorry, thank you.
I'm sorry it's so messy
right now.
Look,
I'm gonna stay here tonight
and keep a eye on you.
I appreciate you coming,
but I can't ask you to stay.
It's okay.
I don't get much sleep anyway.
Okay, do you, um...
do you want
some tea or something?
Sure.
D? What's up, buddy?
-What you doing here?
-Hey, it was a long day.
I was gonna grab a beer,
chill before I head home.
Love it, let's do it.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Hmm.
Interesting.
Yeah, you can say that again.
Mm...
Sit at the bar?
Man, this is not really
the vibe I was expecting.
-You wanna go somewhere else?
-No, no.
Let's... let's
definitely stay here.
I mean, we... we need a beer
and she's got two.
We wouldn't wanna upset her.
Yeah. All right, well, uh,
I'm gonna hit the head.
Just, uh, get me whatever
you're having.
Got it.
Um, how about two Colsons?
Coming right up.
Hey, baby.
Why the fuck you bring
another badge with you?
I didn't bring him in here.
Uh, he saw me outside,
he pulled in.
I just had to go with it,
grab a beer with him.
It's not a big deal.
Gotta head back, though.
Yeah, you're short.
Hmm, so was your notice,
which cost me more.
-Like that, huh?
-You can take it up with him
if you have a problem
with our arrangement.
My line of work keeps me
pretty busy.
Well, you look like a busy man.
Hey.
-You good, buddy?
-Oh, yeah.
Next round's on me.
Why are you doing this?
Helping me,
helping my community?
There's a dark energy
that covers this town.
That crew even.
I don't know what it is,
but the drugs they're slinging,
kill... and hurt people.
We all deserve
a second chance...
if we're lucky.
Ray, will you be straight
with me?
I saw you get shot a lot.
I...
saw the bullets go
through your clothes
into your skin.
I was given a gift
some time ago.
I'm still trying
to figure it out.
But I can't explain it.
It's just how my body heals.
Show me.
I wanna see for myself.
You have no scars
or marks at all.
Look, I, um...
I know this seems confusing.
But like I said...
sometimes we're lucky
and we get a second chance.
Look, um...
I think maybe you
should get some sleep.
An internal leak?
Is that what you're implying?
I'm not necessarily
implying anything.
But I got a guy running
digital forensic software,
social media and video analytics
on our team just to be safe.
So far everyone's clean.
Vanessa Young is on her way up.
Thank you.
I'll leave you to it.
I'll have transport standin' by.
That other thing stays
between you and me.
Captain.
Good morning, Ms. Young.
I appreciate you coming in.
-Please, have a seat.
-I don't know why I'm here.
I told you everything
that I know.
What do you know about him?
-Honestly, not much.
-Is he a friend of yours?
-Not really.
-Well, I've been informed
that he saved you from
a couple of dangerous
situations, but
you're saying that
you don't know him.
Why do you suppose he'd
do that for somebody
that he doesn't know?
He's a good guy, I guess.
Miss Young...
let me remind you
that lying to a government
official is a felony offense
punishable to up
to five years of imprisonment.
So I'm gonna ask you again.
Look, I had never
seen him before
until a few days ago,
but I'm sure you...
already know that.
He just... started showing up
and I didn't trust him at first,
but you are right. He...
has protected me.
And for reasons I don't know.
And do you trust him now?
I don't know
who to trust right now.
But what I do know is that,
for whatever reason,
he is trying to clean up
these streets
just like you and me.
Thank you for your candor,
but I'm just gonna cut
right to the chase.
We need you to testify against
gang leader Mateo Ramirez
and tell us everything you know
about Demetrius Barkley,
first to the grand jury
and then at trial.
-What?
-You have seen
Mateo Ramirez in action.
You identified him
and you confirmed
that he's the one
calling the shots.
That is huge to this office
and this case
because they're usually
much more protective
of their top tier
in that organization.
I cannot... testify.
That is gonna put a huge
target on my back.
Miss Young, have a seat.
Please, have a seat.
I assure you,
you're already a target.
And you're in danger.
We can offer you protection.
No.
No, I can't.
There is something else
I'd like to discuss with you.
What?
Yesterday, when you were
looking through suspect photos,
you neglected
to identify this man,
your brother,
Alonzo Young.
Now, what I find interesting
is that, of everyone,
your statement
was the most detailed
and yet you intentionally
omitted that he was there.
Both your cameraman
and the store owner ID'd Alonzo
as one of the perps.
That omission could be construed
as aiding and abetting,
another felony offense.
Now, Miss Young, listen to me.
I think that you have
a bright future ahead of you,
but your next decision
could ruin any chance
at a career for you.
Please, my brother has been
my responsibility
since we were children.
I have to protect him.
There is no more protecting him.
But you can throw a Hail Mary
and try to save him.
These guys have been grooming
your brother for a while now.
Okay?
Either to
move up or
to take the fall for them.
Now, I've shared with you that
right now, we have our eyes set
on Mateo Ramirez
and Demetrius Barkley,
but soon enough, we will be
going after your brother.
If he lives that long.
They'll know.
If I agree to testify,
they're gonna have my name
as a witness.
And that's why we've already
arranged to have you taken to
a safe house until your grand
jury testimony next week,
and into witness
protection until trial.
If you agree to this,
you'll be considered
a government witness
with immunity,
which means that this office
will forgive you
for aiding and abetting,
as well as the previous
false statements
that you've made.
Miss Young...
I am giving you a second chance.
Miss Page, please.
I cannot do that.
You are out here
risking your life every day,
prophesying about how you wanna
save your community.
Well, I am here giving you
the opportunity
to do just that.
To save your community and...
save your brother.
Right here, right now.
I lost a lot of soldiers lately.
Now it's time for you
to step up.
-I mean, what you need?
-We've got a situation
with this puta
named Vanessa Young.
Yeah, she's a problem.
I sent AJ to give her a warning,
and she still turned up
at the DA's office this morning.
Nah, that ain't good.
I don't give warnings.
I made an exception for Alonzo,
but now it's on.
You want me to take her ass out?
Not yet.
I have another situation
we can use her for.
As bait to lure Lazarus
into the open.
He somehow manages to show up
when she needs protecting.
And this Black Panther
and I need to have ourselves
a conversation.
You keep this shit
on the down low,
especially in front of Alonzo.
I got this.
You trust this fool?
He wants to prove himself,
so we'll let him.
It's not fancy,
but you're safe here.
Hmm, maybe for now.
When I testify, I'm dead.
No, you're dead if you don't.
Look, after your testimony,
you'll be relocated
in witness protection.
You'll be safe
and can start a whole new life.
I don't want a new life.
I want my life.
I have worked...
exceptionally
hard for my career,
and what, I can't even...
tell my boss why I don't show up
for work anymore?
No.
Look, Vanessa,
I'm sorry, but no one
can know where you are.
And they can't know
why you're here.
Especially your brother.
I'm picking up on that.
We've got a situation
with this puta
named Vanessa Young.
You want me to take her ass out?
Not yet.
I have another situation
we can use her for.
As bait to lure Lazarus
into the open.
Hi, it's Vanessa.
Leave a message.
Hey, it's Ray.
Call me when you get this.
Hey. No.
Get away from the window.
What Officer Johnson
is trying to say
is we don't wanna cast
shadows at night,
so have a seat, please.
I thought you said
we were safe here.
We are.
But we still need
to be cautious.
Only Cisco knows we're here.
-Jesus!
-Danny?
Put that shit away
before you kill someone.
Yeah. I should've shot you
for not giving us a heads-up.
Thanks, asshole.
Asshole, huh?
You don't want burgers?
Fine.
Yeah, I figured.
Sorry if I scared you.
Only three?
-So, you're not staying?
-No, uh...
I've got, uh, some work
I gotta get back to.
I'm Danny, I hope you like food.
Thanks, Danny.
Yeah, you got it.
-Yeah?
-What's the set-up?
You got two cops on duty
and one posted outside.
We hit tonight.
My man, Alonzo.
Thanks for coming, man.
Sit.
Am I in trouble?
Of course not.
We family.
How you been?
-Sensational.
-You doing good?
-Yeah.
-All right.
Listen,
I gotta be honest with you.
I didn't wanna
involve you in this,
but since Trevor
ain't with us no more,
I need my people to step up.
What you need?
Can I trust you?
100%.
Even if it involves your sister?
Sure.
We're gonna use her.
Help us bring
your Black Panther to us.
He's interfering in our business
and I can't have that.
Clearly my soldiers
can't get it done.
The Jakes are holding her
at a safe house,
but tonight we're gonna
move her,
and when Lazarus shows up,
we'll be ready for him.
Is this gonna be
a problem for you?
Nah.
Nah, that... that ain't
a problem at all, D.
As long as Vanessa don't
get hurt, right?
Oh, no, she won't be hurt.
She'll be safer
when we take out Lazarus.
He's a dangerous man.
So, you trust me?
I trust you.
All right.
-Stop!
-Hey!
No! No! Rachel!
Freeze!
Shit.
Shots fired. Officer down.
No...
Why you wanna mess with me
and my business?
What do you expect
to accomplish?
Take down some
of my foot soldiers?
Your own brother?
Ruin your life and career
on some witness
protection bullshit?
I'm bulletproof.
Nothing is traceable to me.
And don't kid yourself.
The Feds can put you
in an Alaskan tundra
and I'll still find you.
I need you to find your Lazarus.
Tell him you know
where your sister is.
Alonzo, why are you doing this?
Shut up, bitch!
Go.
Perfect.
Electrical currents
will weaken him
and deplete his life force.
Lazarus!
I'm here!
Where are you?
I need you!
I'm here!
Lazarus!
I'm here.
I know where my sister is.
You coming?
Why you wanna help her now?
We had our differences,
but she's still my blood.
I don't want him hurting her.
Meet me around the corner.
You lead the way.
Come on.
Stop!
Lazarus!
Keep back.
Get rid of her.
Wait, Demetrius.
Demetrius, you promised.
You... you
promised me, Demetrius.
You promised me!
Vanessa!
Vanessa...
Let go of me!
Get out of here while you can!
Go!
Mateo.
For as long as I can remember,
I heard there
was others like me,
but you're the first
I've actually encountered.
Amazing.
Weak mortals.
Lazarus, our immortality
gives us great power,
but you misuse your gifts.
Now, see,
I was resurrected
for a great purpose,
but I don't know about you.
These powers we got,
gifts,
they supposed to be for good.
The world is corrupt,
and you're naive thinking
you can save it.
But imagine...
what we can do together,
you and I,
we can rule the world.
Join me... brother.
I ain't your brother.
You chose
the wrong side, Lazarus.
Why?
'Cause I don't choose evil?
The world is evil!
Men are innately evil.
You can't save them.
I don't believe that.
Then you're a damn fool
and immortality
is wasted on you.
When I was brought back...
I saw a light,
and I follow that light.
I can see the light in people.
When I look at you,
all I see is darkness.
Darkness is beautiful.
Join me,
and I'll give you riches
that only darkness can provide.
This is your last chance
to save yourself.
I'd rather die again
than join you, bitch.
As you wish.
Hey. Come on, man.
I need your help, man.
Come on, I need your help, man.
Demetrius!
No!
Oh!
Come on, Zo.
Come on, Zo, no!
He's dying.
Come on, Zo. Please.
Please, wake up.
No, please!
Please. Please,
he's my brother.
Trust me,
it's okay.
No!
Hey. It's me.
It's me. It's me.
Thank you.
Go.
Go!
I'll be okay.
Oh, I love you.
Is he dead?
If he lives,
he'll spend the rest
of his life behind bars.
So, you're saying this guy,
Lazarus,
saved your life,
took Demetrius
and his entire crew out,
-and just vanished?
-Yes.
Where is he now?
I have no idea.
You know we're still gonna
arrest your brother.
I understand.
I'll meet you downtown.
I'm gonna get these assholes
questioned and booked.
I wrap up here.
Hey, we got him.
Where's he going?
Precinct.
How is she?
Shaken.
I still wanna put security
on her, though.
Just for a few days.
-Agreed.
-Captain!
Captain!
You need to see this.
She's dead, Captain.
He won't get far
in his condition.
All right.
Let's be clear
what's on the table.
He agrees to take the plea.
He agrees to fully cooperate
with this office.
He agrees
to testify as a government
witness against the
other defendants.
And in exchange, the state
will agree to reduce
the charges brought
against your client
to aiding and abetting in
a criminal enterprise.
What's all that mean?
It means you tell them
everything
they wanna know, the truth.
You agree to testify
whenever they call you,
and you plead to aiding
and abetting, which
essentially means that
you knew or assisted
the other defendants
in committing crimes.
And if I agree,
I don't do no time, right?
Wrong.
Pursuant of the
Mississippi State
sentencing guidelines,
you'll be facing imprisonment
not greater than five years.
F... five years?
Hang on.
Based on my client's testimony
and cooperation,
he shouldn't do more
than six months.
Alonzo Young,
you got a lot of
people fighting for you.
One year is the best that
I can do,
and that is predicated on
good behavior
while serving time.
You get a second chance, Zo.
Take it.
Your sister's right.
All right.
Wise decision.
Your attorney and I
will work out all the details.
Look at me.
A year should give you
ample time
to figure out a career change
by the time you get out.
Do we understand each other?
Yes, ma'am.
Please, he's my brother.
-One second.
-Alright.
Hey.
You made the right choice.
Even with the imminent
threat of your safety
now removed from the streets,
are you sure that you wanna
still stay in Jackson?
Jackson's my home
and I love my job.
But...
really, I wanna be here
when Alonzo gets out.
You know, I may not be able
to protect him from everything,
but I will...
always, always support him.
He's lucky to have you.
Hey.
How are you?
-What do you want?
-Information.
What kinda information?
Yeah, you're short.
So was your notice.
Which cost me more.
What's the setup?
We got two cops on duty,
and one posted outside.
We hit tonight.
So it was you.
Demetrius' errand boy.
You don't deserve that badge.
It's over.
Oh, I am thrilled to be
reporting to you from
these now quiet streets.
Just weeks ago, they were home
to one of the worst drug-related
violences in our city's history.
People were afraid
to shop at stores.
But because of the recent arrest
of Jackson's major drug ring,
I am happy to report that
business is starting to
revive once again.
A special thank you to
law enforcement and...
someone else for their efforts.
And although these arrests
are just one small victory
in the war against drugs,
we will continue to fight
to take back our city.
I am Vanessa Young reporting.
Great work.
You, too.
I honestly did not think
we'd be able to make a report
like that.
Wait for me.
Thank you.
Should I be worried?
I mean, you only show up
when my life is in danger.
Nah, I think you good.
I...
I... I didn't wanna leave
without seeing you.
Leave?
Yeah.
I can't stay as long
as Demetrius is out there.
I have to find him,
finish what we started.
I figured that.
And...
it's why I brought you this.
A proper thank you
for saving my brother's life.
And mine.
It...
represents healing.
People know that they're in
safe hands when they see
somebody with it.
Be careful.
And come back before
I'm taken off the market.