All right, so this
shouldn't take long.
Just need to go over what
happened.
We already answered
questions at the house.
Well, any time there's a
shooting, we need to be thorough.
I'll try to be quick.
Okay.
-Is my wife okay?
-She's fine.
We've got her in another room.
Okay, why is she in another
room?
Standard procedure.
Like I said, it shouldn't take
long.
Okay.
So, at approximately
10:00 p.m., you confronted
a homeless man
who'd broken into your backyard.
He then wrestled
your gun from you and...
I'm sorry, it's a little hard
for me to read this,
"He then wrestled your gun from
you and used it to shoot himself."
That about it?
Yes.
How'd you know he was homeless?
How'd I know he was homeless?
Yes.
Had you seen him
around the neighborhood or?
Yes, I saw him
earlier tonight on the walk
bridge.
A lot of unhoused people live
down there.
"Unhoused"?
Ah, right, that's the better
term these days.
Tough issue in the city. Sad.
It's very.
-Dangerous.
-Yes.
Yes, I guess it can be.
So, why would you be
down there at night?
Well, I was taking a walk after
dinner.
I mean, it's still my
neighborhood.
Hmm.
And, you were alone
at the time of the break-in?
Me and Brett, yes.
So, no kids in the house?
Not yet.
Okay, and are you
normally at home during the day?
I'm an emergency room doctor, so
my schedule's always changing.
That's impressive.
Being in a wheelchair must make
it...
Hospitals are made for
wheelchairs.
Ha, never thought of
it that way.
So, what time did you get home
today?
About 5:00 p.m.
Uh-huh, and Brett?
He works from home.
Jesus Christ.
Guess who's ovulating?
The gardner's still here.
Oh, good.
Well, maybe he can put a baby in
me.
What is your problem?
Ah, clients hire you because
they say they love your vision,
and then they want to change
every good idea that you have.
Oh, is this for Janine?
Um-hmm.
-Oh.
-She wants polished ash for the stairs,
like it's an Apple Store.
It's an art gallery.
Well, it is her money, you could
polish her ash a little.
Oh, you're very funny for a
doctor.
Just throw her a bone.
The stairs are supposed to be
the centerpiece of the whole gallery.
Aren't the paintings the
centerpiece of the whole gallery?
No.
Paintings come and go.
A building is actually there, forever.
Wow.
Okay, yes, sure, that...
Like, massively.
I know, that might have been a
little...
You know what it is?
My ego, it's just...
it's too big-
-Oh, yes?
-For one person,
and I think that we are going
to have to make a baby.
Yeah?
Just so somebody can take
half of it and carry this weight.
Okay, let me... I need to wash
off the emergency room stink. No.
No, you don't.
That is delicious.
It's blood and appendix juice.
I'll suck your...
All right, so you were in a good mood
when you headed out for your walk?
Yeah.
Yes.
And when you saw this
homeless man, did he see you?
We'd literally bumped into each
other.
Was he aggressive toward you?
No, no.
It was my fault.
I was distracted.
I was texting a client.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I didn't see you there.
What's wrong with you, huh?
What's wrong with you?
Then he showed up at our house
about an hour later.
Just showed up, huh?
He explain why he was there?
You think he was trying to rob
you?
No, no.
It was... It was creepier than
that.
So, at that point, you went
outside to confront him?
Yes.
And you took your
gun at that time?
Yes.
So, you felt
like he was dangerous?
I mean, honestly,
I took it out for Angie.
I just wanted to make her feel
safer.
No.
No, the gun did not make me feel
safer.
I see the statistics come through
the hospital doors every night,
they are not in the gun owner's
favor.
I hate that gun.
So, Brett went
outside to confront the man.
What did you do?
I called 911.
Hi, yes. Yes, I would like to
report a break-in.
He appears to be having
a psychotic episode.
I called 911, but not
because I was afraid of him.
A total stranger
shows up in my backyard,
I'd be pretty freaked out.
It's not that simple.
I'm confused.
I had a crazy person in my
backyard, what the fuck does it matter
why I brought a gun out?
But you knew him.
Your wife says you all went
to college together.
Okay, yes.
Yes, yes, I should have said
that.
Yes, we knew him.
So, why would you need that gun?
Because I haven't seen the guy
in nearly 10 years, it's...
I didn't even recognize
him tonight.
It's not the same person.
I didn't recognize him when I
saw him on the walk bridge.
So, let's go back to
that bridge.
You ran into him,
and then you just kept walking?
No.
So, you recognized him?
No, he recognized me.
I just said that I didn't
recognize him.
Right, right,
right, right, right.
I'm so sorry, I didn't see you
there.
Brett?
It's Kevin.
Kevin Broady.
-Come on, man.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Crazy, what?
Crazy. That's crazy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
How are you?
I'm good.
Good, yes.
How've you been?
Oh, good.
Good.
Better than good.
I would have called you,
but I lost my phone.
Then I broke it.
Then I lost it.
No, I lost... I broke it, then I
lost it.
Kev?
Just, I'm glad to see you're
alive, man.
Wow, okay.
Okay.
Oh, man.
-Wow.
-Yeah.
Are you married?
Yeah.
Okay.
Angie.
Wow.
Why was he upset when you
told him you were with Angie?
Maybe he was jealous?
How do I know?
But, at that point...
yeah, at that point, he got
violent.
Got some money?
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
I don't want your taco money.
No, it's $60. Here you go, Kev.
No, I don't want your fucking
gas money either.
Calm down. What the...?
What's wrong with you?
We were friends, huh.
What's wrong with you, huh?
What's wrong with you?
We were friends.
Kevin was never violent.
I mean, I'm not saying he was
stable, but not violent.
Unstable, how?
I don't know.
At first, it was more like a
crazy-genius sort of unstable.
You're a doctor,
can you be more precise?
I'm not a psychologist.
Okay.
For example, one morning,
our final year of school,
I woke up to the smell of fish.
Kevin was cutting the scales
off...
he was cutting the scales off a
live trout
and applying them to a painting
because, according to him,
sometimes you just can't
replicate nature.
He was tragic and unpredictable.
I loved that about him,
but not violent.
He was never violent.
So, he was a painter?
Yes.
We were all Art majors, it's how
we met.
And you and Kevin were a couple?
Yeah, for a while.
So, like a college fling, or?
No.
I loved him,
but eventually,
his illness got so bad that I
couldn't be with him anymore.
And when did you and
Brett get together?
After.
After Kevin.
Right after?
Too soon.
Was Kevin jealous of Brett?
No, it's more like the other way
around.
Were you jealous of Kevin?
I was never jealous of Kevin.
Why would I be jealous?
I got the girl.
Okay, did you ever see the movie
Amadeus?
Won an Academy Award, right?
It's about...
Well, it's about this composer in
the 1700s named Salieri who is...
he's so dedicated to his art,
he's literally willing
to give everything to it,
and it breaks his heart.
Why?
Because he meets Mozart.
And he realizes that he'll never
be able to compete with this wild,
inappropriate, instinctual force of
nature with this seemingly God-given gift.
So, Brett was
Salieri and Kevin was Mozart?
Maybe in college, a little bit.
He was talented, but obviously I
don't feel that way
anymore.
What changed?
I have spent the last 10 years building
a pretty decent architectural business,
and he has spent it living on
the street, eating out of trash cans,
and it's hard to feel anything but sad
about the way it turned out for Kevin.
Okay.
So, you tussle on the bridge,
and then he follows you home?
No.
He had my address.
What makes you so sure of that?
Because he stole my wallet on
the bridge.
Yes, he got to the house before
me.
-Ooh.
-Oh, fuck.
-You scared the shit out of me.
-Okay, it's just me.
Don't be dramatic.
Why are you always
sneaking up on me?
Why am I always...?
Sneaking up on me?
-Coming into my own bedroom, Angie?
-Okay.
-Hey?
-What?
Look at me.
Wait, why is your face all
dirty?
Can we just talk about
this tomorrow?
Please.
Hey?
What?
Listen.
Can we go to bed?
I am exhausted.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Shh.
Listen.
-Brett?
-Look, it's okay.
Wait.
It's fine.
Sorry I stole your wallet.
Not cool.
Thanks for bringing it back.
You should leave, Kevin.
Hey, you can't be here.
You need to leave.
Architecture, huh?
Hmm.
Makes sense,
all those straight lines.
What's so funny?
I find it ironic that someone
who couldn't fucking paint
is building an art gallery.
At least I didn't waste
the time that I had.
I'm sorry.
Saying you sucked isn't cool.
Yes, that's why I just want you
to leave.
My soul is fucked.
Hey.
Your soul is not my problem,
Kevin,
but I need you to leave.
Okay? I need you to leave.
No, it's real this time.
It's real, intertwined,
and I've seen shit.
I've seen just...
Man, nothing.
Nothing. I just...
I get a little dazed and
confused,
I ain't going to lie. It's bad.
Maybe you shouldn't be getting
high then.
It's a little late for that,
Brett.
You know, I broke
the two rules to better health.
Number one, avoid stressful
situations.
Now, good luck with that,
living on the street.
Number two, stay away
from drugs and alcohol
unless you were
being prescribed by your doctor,
and then you can just keep
pumping fucking pills until you turn
into a zombie.
You know, you can get
bionic legs.
Just stop.
Okay?
You've done enough.
What the fuck do you want?
Oh, yeah. I'm sorry,
I...
Forgiveness, I should have...
I should have said that.
I should have led with that.
I need forgiveness.
I want forgiveness.
Did you have any
idea what he was talking about?
Yeah.
And?
Angie.
What happened to her, it was...
it was his fault.
He crippled her.
What happened?
It was...
Sorry. It was a car accident.
I think it was an accident,
I don't know for sure,
but that is the last time that
we saw Kevin before tonight.
He went to jail
or the psych ward, whatever,
and...
Angie and I went on
with our lives, you know?
We recovered.
It was hard.
Okay.
So, when he asked
for forgiveness, what'd you say?
"You're forgiven."
You're forgiven.
Okay.
You were forgiven.
You are forgiven.
Just please leave.
Not from you, you jackass.
-From her.
-She doesn't deserve this.
Oh, she does.
I do, I need...
forgiveness.
She needs an apology.
I need forgiveness.
Apologies and forgiveness,
we're...
I need apologies and
forgiveness.
She needs apologies, I need
Ah, shit.
Apologies and forgiveness.
Brett?
Stay over there.
It's all right.
What? No. If you need that,
then it's not all right.
Just wanna make sure.
I'm just going to make
sure that he's gone,
-all right?
-Who...
-Who was that?
-Don't worry.
-Angie...
-No, no, no.
No, you're not going out there.
Angie, give me one second.
-Yes, I hear... Okay?
-You're not going out there in the dark.
What is he doing here?
I bumped into him when I was out
walking.
What do you mean you bumped into
him?
Tonight, on the walk bridge,
I bumped into him.
What were you doing on the walk
bridge?
I was taking a walk, Angie.
-It's my fucking neighborhood.
-What do you fucking mean?
Okay.
-What do you mean?
-I know how this must feel.
If I just... if I go talk to him.
Just give me a sec.
Was he... Was he waiting for you?
No, okay?
I think it was a coincidence.
I'm pretty sure he's hearing
more voices than just mine,
all right?
Just do me a favor,
call 911 and lock the door
behind me.
Angie?
Yeah.
You need to go.
Fucking breaks my heart
to see her in that chair.
I'm guessing that means
she doesn't want to talk to me.
For the last time, Kevin,
you need to leave.
It's like a beautiful fish
caught in a fish bowl.
We already called the
cops, Kevin.
Please, just...
can you just get her
so I could talk to her?
What happened, happened, okay?
A long time ago.
There's nothing left to say.
I never got to say anything,
just stuck in a bed
at a fucking psych ward.
What would you even say, Kevin?
Huh? Do you remember anything
from that night, huh?
Because you were out of your
fucking mind, no offense.
I stole her life.
She has a life, okay?
We have a life, and you're not
part of it anymore.
I'm begging you, please.
-I'm begging you, please.
-She has no interest in talking to you.
Please, please.
-Stop.
-You get out of here.
-Go.
-Stop. Stop.
Hi, Angie.
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry.
-I'm so...
-Stop.
I'm so sorry.
Stop. Stop saying that.
If you take one more step
towards her, I will fucking shoot you.
No.
No, you're not a killer.
I will fucking shoot you.
Why are you whispering?
Because I don't want
to wake up my neighbors.
God, that's so you.
-So, then you shot him?
-No. No.
That's so you. Just do it.
Wait!
Just say the word, Angie.
-I swear to God I'll...
-Kevin, put the gun down.
I need mercy.
I can't carry this any longer.
Put the gun down, Kevin.
I can't carry this anymore.
Kevin, put the gun down.
You don't get to change
what happened that night.
Then why?
Why would the universe put me
on that bridge with Brett tonight...
if not for some greater purpose?
Huh?
I'm asking for forgiveness.
He shot himself.
That's not what your wife says.
What?
She says you shot him.
No.
I was there when she talked to
you when you first got to the house,
when she told you the story.
You're fucking... Are you trying
to gaslight me?
Your wife's changed her story.
It happens once a person's
had some time to process...
No, that's not... there's no way
that would happen.
Look, look, look, look, look. Maybe
you were acting in self-defense.
He trespassed on your property.
He wasn't in his right mind.
Of course, on the other hand,
you were jealous of him.
He crippled your wife.
It's complicated.
Do I need a lawyer?
Do you?
Look, I'm just trying
to untangle the truth here.
I'm sorry. This is crazy.
Can I speak to her, please?
Your wife?
Yes, my wife.
Sure.
Are you all right?
They're recording this.
Just... Why would you say that?
What?
Angie, don't do this.
Please don't do this.
Angie?
Angie, don't do...
Don't do this
to me. Don't fucking do this.
Don't do this. Don't do this.
Don't do this.
Don't fucking do this.
I don't ever want to see you
again.
We're done.
-We're done here.
-Don't.
Angie.
♪ Drunk in the morning,
Sunlight warming ♪
♪ The shadows fade across my
Face ♪
♪ Long way down below the
Rainbow ♪
♪ Wait for the voices
To speak our names ♪
♪ There is no rest along this
Journey ♪
♪ And your love must be sincere
♪
♪ When I was young
And not so lonely once ♪
♪ I knew that love and felt no
Fear ♪
♪ I had a dream in the mirror ♪
♪ We were wandering some
Faraway place ♪
♪ I am no stranger to a
Stranger ♪
♪ Oblivion in search of grace ♪
♪ I found you in a movie
Theatre ♪
♪ The lights are dim across
Your face ♪
♪ You speak the truth
Like a knife fighter ♪
♪ Cut like a shining steely
Blade ♪
Kevin!
Kevin.
Fuck.
-Kevin!
-Okay.
-It's going to be okay.
-Do you think he's okay?
Yes. It's going to be okay.
-How do you know?
-He swims all the time.
He's going to be...
Ooh.
I just went swimming with the
most beautiful dolphins...
or maybe they could have been
sharks.
It's exciting.
So, what happened next?
What happened next?
Honestly, Detective...?
-Mike.
-Detective,
why exactly do you need to know the
details of what happened 10 years ago?
Context.
To understand what Kevin's mindset
was when he broke into your house tonight.
The context is that Kevin had
a fucking mental episode
and ran me over with his fucking
car.
Sorry.
I need you, Angie.
Was he trying to kill you?
When...
When a person...
When Kevin's...
illness became acute...
Maybe if you just give me the
facts as you remember them.
Ha.
Brett went to get a towel out of
his car.
He didn't want to leave me alone,
but I told him that I needed
to talk to Kevin alone.
Told him that we would meet him
back at his car.
But that's not what happened.
What did you do?
So, you never heard it coming?
No.
No, not until the last second,
I guess, because of the waves.
Do you think he
intentionally hit you?
Angie.
No.
What makes you so sure?
Because I saw his face when he
saw me.
Help!
He was destroyed.
Your wife says you
went to get the car.
I did, yes,
but when I got down there,
it was gone, and then I just...
I saw the headlights down on the
beach.
Worst night of my life.
I blacked out after that
and woke up in the hospital.
It was a long recovery...
and Brett was there every day
that I can remember.
He's been there every day since,
and it was the last time, here,
I ever saw Kevin.
Until Brett accidentally
ran into Kevin tonight,
on the bridge?
-No. -What do you mean no?
Kevin didn't accidentally run
into Brett tonight.
He was waiting for him.
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't see you
there.
How do you know that?
Because Kevin told us.
Did he mention why?
Everything that I thought
was true for the last 10 years...
it's a fucking lie.
It's why Kevin came back.
Because he remembered.
She has no interest in talking
to you.
-You get out of here. Go.
-Stop!
Stop.
Hi, Angie.
You look good.
What are you doing here, Kevin?
I just wanted to talk to you,
to tell you that...
You take one more step towards
her and I will fucking shoot you.
No, you're not a killer.
You're a liar.
I bet you he didn't even tell
you, did he?
Tell me what?
About what really went down that
night.
You've done enough, Kevin.
Oh, no. I mean, really, you're
going to want to hear this.
-You should...
-I will fucking shoot you.
Look at him.
Look how scared he is...
because he knows
that I am the destroyer of lies.
No, I just... I think you're
very, very confused.
No, no.
I'm as clear as a bell,
and I'm here to ring, Brett.
It's the shock of bumping into
me on the bridge.
-Explain it to him, Angie.
-Explain what?
Explain how bumping into me
on the bridge
has probably set his mind off
into some state of paranoia
or something.
I wasn't surprised
to see you on the bridge.
I was waiting for you.
What?
You know, when I got out,
I got off those fucking meds...
and the fog lifted,
and it all came rushing back to
me.
The fucking voices? Come on.
You know, that gun
doesn't give you license
to be a fucking dick, Brett.
She needs to know.
This is bullshit.
It is bullshit.
It was a coincidence.
I saw the surprise on his face, okay?
Street people, street people,
are able to be invisible.
You can just walk through the
world and just be a ghost,
nobody wants to see you,
and you can just walk
to your local library, find a
computer, and sit down,
unbothered.
Focus.
Ten years finding you.
-Come on, this is fucking...
-Shut the fuck up, Brett!
He's nuts.
Tell me what you need to tell
me, and then you leave.
-Okay?
-Okay, sounds good.
Come on.
-Angie.
-Let him talk.
Now let him talk.
What are you afraid of?
What did he remember?
-He said...
-I wasn't alone that night?
No, he wasn't alone.
Because we were all there, and
you were the one behind the wheel.
It is time to go.
-Let's go.
-Hey.
Don't touch me. Come on, Brett.
Come on, Angie.
You need to apologize, Brett.
Stop fucking talking.
No. No. No. That is bullshit,
that is not how it happened.
So, Angie's lying?
I'm listening.
It's okay.
No, wait, just wait, just wait,
there's more to the story,
okay?
Just fucking wait, wait for one
second.
You want to fucking hear this?
Just fucking wait.
Brett's got a story to tell.
You want to hear Brett's story?
-Yeah, I want to hear his story.
-Okay.
We want to hear the story,
Brett.
Go for it.
Caught you. Where are you going, huh?
I'm just getting you a towel.
Getting a towel?
Going to see your girlfriend.
Oh, no wait.
You're going to see my
girlfriend.
-No, Kevin.
-No, of course not.
Of course not.
Bullshit, me.
Huh?
I can see it now, man.
The blinders are off, bitch.
It's so clear. I can see you.
I see you.
Kevin, you've been raging
for 48 hours straight,
so I don't think you're seeing
anything very clearly right now.
That's a fucking bale.
I see the whole fucked up
equation.
Yeah, you don't even want her.
Did you know that?
You want me.
You settled for her.
You settled.
You sinister little fucking
vampire.
You settled.
You want me.
You want my fucking skin.
But you can't steal it.
Because it's God-given.
You fucking talentless hack.
Aww.
Aww, is it...
Hey, you want to be me?
You want to kill me.
Hey.
Huh?
-No?
-Yes.
Fucking frowler.
You blood sucking fraud.
Whatever Angie says I'll live
by.
That is so you.
Waiting for somebody to say
it's okay.
It's okay, go ahead.
How can you be an artist
and you're afraid of risk?
Huh?
Oh. Okay.
Okay, where are we going?
Buckle up.
I'll risk it.
You'll never know.
You'll never know what it's
really like.
Shit is torcher.
What are you doing?
How's this for risk? Huh, bitch?
Hey man, turn the lights on.
Who's afraid now?
This is not risk. This
is just...
Just turn your lights on!
It was me.
That's a hell of a secret to
hold on to for all these years.
Say, you double back
and acted like you weren't
in the car all this time.
Until now.
But then...
why would he shoot himself?
If anything, I think Kevin would
have turned the gun on you.
Okay, well, he didn't.
Obviously, he didn't shoot me.
Well, you see the problem
I'm having with your story here.
Right, Brett?
What do you want me to say?
I ruined my marriage to try to
stop a friend from killing himself.
Angie doesn't want to speak to
me, and he's dead anyways,
so.
You could judge me.
You could call me a liar,
but I didn't kill anyone.
Nobody's saying you
killed anybody.
Okay, so then you believe me
that I didn't shoot Kevin.
No.
I just know you didn't kill him.
Here, it's cold tonight.
The MT said the bullet barely
grazed you.
It's just coffee.
You brew it yourself?
Yes, if you call throwing
some grinds at a coffee maker.
You didn't put any meds in here,
did you?
Because I'm off that shit.
Huh.
No meds.
You wouldn't lie to me, would
you?
I could ask you the same thing.
I just got shot in the head, so
I'm not the most reliable narrator.
Let's just say
we'll trust each other, deal?
So, you are currently homeless,
is that correct?
Look, it's not a crime to be
homeless.
I have two houses.
One in Chicago, one in Hawaii,
on the Big Island.
Didn't we just agree
that we were going
to be honest with each other?
No, I'm trying to do that.
Okay.
Ask me if I am currently
unhoused.
Ah, I got it.
Sorry. Didn't mean to offend
you.
Are you currently unhoused?
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
When I choose not to live
in my other two houses.
Yes, we're honestly
going to be honest.
We're going to be honest
because we said honestly.
Let's go then and be honest.
So...
You live on the street by choice,
is that what you're telling me?
No.
No, I had a heavy heart.
I needed to be around other
heavy-hearted individuals.
I don't follow.
Certain unnamed professionals
told me that I have
a need to self-flagellate
and I wanted to inflict pain.
You want to hurt other people?
No, on myself.
I want to inflict pain on
myself.
Look, man, please don't put
words in my mouth.
Okay. Okay, look, I'm
just trying to help you here,
Kevin.
Help.
Maybe we can even become friends
and I can come stay at your house
in Hawaii.
Are you being funny?
Are you being funny right now?
Are you the funny guy?
Did you track down
your old college friends
in order to tell Angie the truth
about the night of the accident?
How can you be an artist
when you're afraid of risk?
No.
You didn't tell Angie that
Brett was driving the car?
No. Do we have to talk about
this.
So, up until
tonight, you thought...
Every day, I wake up
and I see Angie in the sand.
In the sand.
Over and over
and fuck!
-You didn't kill Angie?
-Help!
Help!
When I woke up and I had bloody
hands on the steering wheel
and I saw Angie out in the sand
and that's all I had.
Every day, over and over and
over, every day.
Seeing her out there
from that day until today,
it's all I had.
That's all I had to...
Can we please just stop talking
about that night already now,
please?
So, tonight was
purely by accident?
I... I don't think anything
in the world is pure chance.
I mean there's...
I mean, that gets into a whole
metaphysical belief system.
That's just dependent on what
you believe.
-Kevin.
-But...
Kevin.
I don't know.
Is there really free will?
-Kevin.
-I mean, who am I to say?
Were you waiting for
Brett on the bridge?
Did you come looking for him
tonight?
I mean...
Maybe.
Maybe? Maybe what?
It's just it's possible that I've
been carrying that day around.
Dragging it through the dirt.
Sleeping with it.
It was in my pain.
It was in my fucking...
He's never getting it.
We're all just never getting
this.
Stop. Stop.
Stop saying that!
You know, maybe I just had an
ulterior motive.
Brett?
Kevin.
It's Kevin Broady.
Wow.
It's crazy.
Yeah.
Did he invite you up to his
house when you ran into
him on the bridge?
No.
So, why did you
break into his house tonight?
To return his wallet, I guess.
The one you stole on the bridge?
I didn't steal his wallet.
He dropped it when he shoved me.
He shoved you?
Maybe I shook him first.
I don't want your taco money.
It's $60, Kevin.
Take it.
-I don't want your fucking gas money.
-What's wrong with you?
-Take the money.
-We were friends.
-What's wrong with you?
-What's wrong?
Take the money.
-What's wrong with you, man?
-What's wrong with you?
Huh? What's wrong with?
What's wrong
with you? What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
Stay the fuck away from us,
Kevin. Stay the fuck away from us.
Kevin.
Hey, hey.
What's wrong with you?
I was just returning his wallet.
That's it.
Dropped your wallet.
Okay.
Thanks... Thanks for bringing it
back.
Architecture. huh?
Makes sense.
All those straight lines.
You were so good with order.
You stole my wallet so you could
come here and talk to Angie?
Hm?
I didn't steal your wallet
but I wouldn't mind seeing
Angie.
Some things that need to be
said.
I got a lot hanging on me,
Brett.
Heavy.
Guess I always knew
you would come back eventually.
Maybe you shouldn't be
getting high, Kevin.
It's a little late for that.
A little late for that, Brett.
Get the fuck out of my house.
Now.
Look, I can't change what
happened.
But Angie and I, we have a good
thing now that we have built over hard,
hard time.
Sounds like love.
I'm begging you, man,
just fucking... leave.
You bring this back,
then she's going to leave me
and she's the only fucking thing
that I have.
Please.
There he is.
Brett wanted to come clean too,
I just couldn't see it.
I'm not going to leave
until I get my forgiveness.
So, clearly,
Brett was afraid that you knew
what really happened
and you're telling me you had no
idea.
No.
No idea.
I guess I...
I guess I tend to
miss out on social cues.
I just wanted to apologize to
her.
Brett says you were
going to shoot yourself tonight.
I couldn't carry it anymore.
And he tried to stop
you by admitting
the truth about the accident.
Yeah, but I wouldn't give him
a fucking medal.
He let me carry that around for
10 fucking years.
Not to mention what he did to
Angie.
Not cool.
Yeah, well, he also
said you shot yourself anyway.
Why the fuck would I do that?
So how did you end up shot?
You were driving?
You did this to her?
Why now?
Because I don't want your blood
on my conscience?
It's a little late for that,
Brett.
Put the gun down.
You ran.
Yes, to get an ambulance.
People call me delusional.
Hold on, let me remind you
of something, okay?
I've been there for you
ever since that night, Angie.
Oh, God. It's all been a big
fucking lie.
No, it has not. Not to me.
What we have here,
what we have built, I love you.
Love?
You fucking call this love?
Fuck.
Kevin, oh, fuck.
I...
I owe you an apology.
Okay, hold on!
Hold on!
No one here is fucking innocent, okay?
You needed me
when he started losing his shit.
I was there for you.
Fuck off, Brett!
-Fuck off!
-Yeah, fuck off, Brett.
Run.
No.
That's what you'll do.
Angie...
don't do this.
Yeah, ain't that much fun when
the rabbit got the gun, huh?
That girl's got some serious
rage.
She shot you?
Of course.
I like to think
that she was aiming for Brett.
Okay.
Hey...
let it go.
Angie.
Listen to me.
Hey, hey, Angie.
Look at me, look at me.
The cops are up front, okay?
They're going to be back here
any second.
We need to get our story
straight.
I was aiming for you.
That's okay.
Hey, I know this is fucked up.
I know that we have
a lot of unpacking to do.
You think?
We can't change
what happened 10 seconds ago.
what happened 10 years ago.
I can keep you from going
to jail for murder.
I'm not going to let
you go to prison, okay?
I love you.
They don't need to know
anything about our history.
They don't need to know our
story.
He broke into our... A homeless
man broke into our backyard.
Had a psychotic breakdown.
I went outside to talk to him.
I took my gun.
He wrestled my gun from me,
and he shot himself in the head.
That's our story.
That is the story.
Aren't you tired of lying?
The truth is a luxury
we don't have right now.
And you will go to jail
if you do not listen to me.
So please.
Police officers.
Let me see your hands.
-Get your hands up.
-We're the homeowners.
We're the ones who called you.
Where's the weapon?
He's in the pool.
He shot himself.
The gun's in there, too.
Control, have medics roll in.
We need you to step away from
the pool.
Just stay calm and follow our
directions.
You're free to go.
What?
I guess you can file a report on
Kevin for breaking and entering.
But, personally, I think you've
already done enough to him
for a lifetime.
Don't you think?
So?
Please get the fuck
out of my police station.
Get the fuck out.
Please.
Now.
Thank you. I guess...
You're free to go, Kevin.
I... I can just go?
Yeah.
Unless you want to file a report
against Angie for attempted murder.
But I mean...
She was trying to shoot Brett who
you probably feel kind of deserved it.
No, no, no. I'm... I'm good, man.
I'll go. I'll go.
I know that was a
lot to process tonight,
but the good news is... that's
it.
You're done.
That's it?
You can file a report against
Brett for vehicular assault.
Not too late for that.
Kevin would end up back in jail
since he was in the car,
and seeing how you shot him
tonight,
maybe you can cut him
some slack.
I don't want to file a report.
Okay.
Angie.
Kevin asked me to tell you
apologies and forgiveness.
Brett?
-The stairs.
-Hm?
They're still that recycled wood
I mixed.
They're upcycled, not recycled.
Oh, okay. Let's just call
a thing what it is, okay?
Remember, it's not about the
space.
It's about the fucking
paintings.
Please.
Okay, what else then?
Please don't touch that.
-Ah.
-My wife must have done that as a joke.
She moved out, right?
This leaf blower is...
I can't think straight.
-Give me one second.
-Hm.
Can you... Can you
turn that thing off?
No, turn it off.
Thank you.
Is this a Broady?
What?
This painting...
isn't this a Kevin Broady?
You... You know him?
Nobody knows him.
Allegedly, he lives on the street
and drops his paintings off
at the back of the Marks
Gallery.
This is worth over $100,000.
♪ Jump in the morning so that
I'm warming ♪
♪ The shadows fade across my
Face ♪
♪ No way tell me love, no way
Back ♪
♪ We follow the voices we can
Reach ♪
♪ There is no rest along this
Journey ♪
♪ And your love must be so
Silly ♪
♪ When I was young
And not so lonely at once ♪
♪ I knew that loving felt no
Fear ♪
♪ I had a dream in the mirror ♪
♪ We're wandering to a faraway
Place ♪
♪ I am no stranger to a
Stranger ♪
♪ Oblivion in search of peace ♪
♪ I found you in
A movie piece ♪
♪ The lights are dim across
Your face ♪
♪ You speak the truth
♪ Collect the shining steel
You've laid ♪