Dovzhenko Film Studios
Ukrainian Ministry of Culture
'Veselka' Creative Group
The Seventh Route
Don't look for me. Yours, Nadiia
[Nadiia literally meaning "Hope"]
Hello.
I'm on my way.
Oh God...
Poems, by Danylo Prytuliuk
Happy birthday, mom.
Good morning.
It's not morning yet for you,
but over here it's your birthday already.
Over here, in your city.
Here's my greetings and here's my gift.
This very morning.
Those streets, familiar to you.
Those majestic hills.
Alright.
Here, kitty kitty!
Don't freak out.
As you can see, I'm currently in Kyiv.
Unfortunately,
I know so little about it.
It's precisely because you keep
your secrets to yourself
that I'm drawn towards them.
Towards your first life,
your native city.
I don't know
how much it has changed,
and if those alleys and boulevards
still look familiar to you.
But I hope my gift pleases you.
This is especially for my mom,
from your native city,
your loving daughter.
Well, alright then.
Here, kitty kitty...
Nadiia,
I did not want to wake you up,
you slept so peacefully.
Breakfast is ready.
I will call you
from work.
Yours, Danylo.
Don't look for me. Yours, Nadiia
Sorry I didn't tell you about my trip.
It's a surprise.
I am as adventurous as you once were.
I looked through all the letters
you've ever received from Kyiv.
Honestly, I would've read them,
but I don't know Ukrainian.
At least I wrote all the addresses down.
I don't know what they mean to you,
but I'm visiting all of them.
It's peculiar.
One of those addresses
is a cycling track.
And on top of that...
...that's where most of your letters
came from.
Does cycling mean something to you?
Alright.
This one beats even the cycling track.
Were you friends with all
these renowned people?
You have no idea how surprised I am.
Pavlo Shans, Prof.
[Shans literally meaning "Chance"]
Oh, how I want to open this door,
apartment 64.
Envelopes from this address
were the thickest.
I'm absolutely sure you've
visited this place.
You're familiar with this stairway,
this alleyway...
Honcharna street, 7
This address is the most mysterious one.
This building's in ruins.
But what really confounds me
is the letters.
You know what I want to ask you.
I want to know what's in those
three letters sent from Honcharna street.
Danylo Prytuliuk!
What the hell's keeping you?
I'm tired of waiting.
There was no bus. I had to walk.
What's with the forehead?
- I slipped, changing the lightbulb.
- You look terrible.
- I'm Danylo.
- Olia.
What's for today?
Americans on tour.
You mess the tour up, you're paying
with your own money, got it?
- Got it.
- Hit the road!
They are asking which route
we are doing today.
- Which one did we do yesterday?
- The sixth.
There's no seventh route.
It's paid for already.
Oh, come on now!
What am I to do?
Hear him?
What does he want?
He wants to hear the tongue.
Can you do that?
Will they understand?
They want to
hear their ancestors' tongue.
Why does he talk in English then?
He only knows his English.
This is their first time.
They aren't learning Ukrainian yet.
They just want to hear how it sounds.
He's asking what
the seventh route is about.
The seventh route?
Oh well, ladies and gentlemen.
It's something to behold.
Follow me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
today we are following
the footsteps of an artist.
Once you've encountered his art,
you'll remember the name forever.
Today we are...
I'm repeating myself.
Ladies and gentlemen.
He spent his younger days here.
Our great poet...
He's our great...
Sorry, my voice is trembling.
What I'm about to tell you
is the story of life and death
of a poet, and a friend of mine.
Danylo Fedorovych...
Prytuliuk.
Inhale, like that! Exhale! Again!
And reach upwards!
Now in front of you!
Up, back, down!
Now the other shoulder!
Great, now the back muscles!
Wide steps!
Back straight, stomach - tight!
Four, three, two...
Now add arm movement!
Great, now walk in one place.
You and Tolik went insane yesterday.
How is he?
Did you deliver the paint yesterday?
Do you know Prytuliuk, the poet?
I don't.
Here he is, hat and sunglasses.
Back straight,
without turning your shoulders -
Like this!
Add some arm movement!
The food's out on the balcony.
Don't worry.
And again, from the beginning!
A salty rain had graced the city,
Dnipro now has...
...a touch of salt.
See: in a dried-up salty puddle
Reflection of a star of gold.
No, no.
See: in an oversalted puddle
Reflection of a star of salt.
The night's a roof above the town.
The Milky Way is raining down.
One star is left, and only one.
There, under the rooftop...
is where the poet lived.
And over there...
his star was shining.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The next exhibit is very unique.
Let's go.
There used to be
a huge fence right there.
I was 12 when I first
saw Danylo drunk.
We were friends already by then.
I have no idea
how and why that happened.
I saw Danylo right there.
He said to me, come over and see.
And brought me...
...here.
Here was the fence,
here, an old shed,
and there was a narrow
gap in between.
Allow me.
He pushed me...
right into the gap.
Allow me.
This very gap.
He lit a match.
Does anyone have a match?
And on this fence...
for the first time ever...
he wrote a poem.
How does it go again?
She's all...
It'll come to me.
...grown-up, if not yet wise,
She came of age, she's in full bloom.
She's not too sure,
She's not too tired.
She has desires.
Her face is one
Big question mark,
She's crying shyly
In the dark.
♬ If your so-called friends ♬
♬ Are telling you what to do - ♬
♬ Listen, ♬
♬ Go with your true desires. ♬
♬ Go with the crows, crow just like them, ♬
♬ Go with the crows, crow just like them. ♬
♬ "Don't look her way",
my friends would say. ♬
♬ "She is too young still,
she won't understand". ♬
♬ Go with the crows, crow just like them. ♬
♬ I followed their advice, ♬
♬ I left her. ♬
♬ Tears were rolling down her face. ♬
♬ Go with the crows, crow just like them. ♬
He dedicated the poem to his sister.
Eventually, once the seventh
route becomes official...
the tourists will visit the plaques,
the Prytuliuk Museum, his school.
But what's a museum
compared to this fence?
Or to Sukhohryz.
Sukhohryz, the poet's nemesis.
What's his question?
They want to know more about Sukhohryz.
Later.
Now, we'll meet the poet's
penultimate wife.
No...
We'll start with the latest wife.
But I would have to make a call.
Vira.
Is Nadiia there?
Tell her I was looking for her.
Give her my love.
Danylo's philosophy was simple and wise.
A philosophy thousands of years old.
- Full contact.
- Don't get in the way.
He told me once...
I'm paraphrasing of course.
"It seems to me, he said,
that almost everyone treats
their life as a rehearsal.
We're abusing the luxury of
coming to the rehearsal unprepared.
We've not learned the script yet.
We don't know our scenic partners well.
We use the sets which are left over
from someone else's performance.
The sets are dusty and deteriorating,
and we're in no hurry to put
some fresh paint on them.
We wait for
someone else to do it for us.
We drink our tea from broken cups
and wait till one day, God willing,
the rehearsal will end,
and we'll perform
at the opening night.
Here's where the actual life starts.
But there will be no opening night.
We wait in vain."
I know this chair, I ate this bread,
I made some babies on that bed;
In fringe's depths, the cold's residing,
There's
vacuum cleaner's somewhere, hiding.
The ice paints white
the bottle's glass,
In sour spirits, I - alas! -
Reach for my trusty wishing well,
With rhymes too intricate too tell.
I've rhymed my dreams with vile advice,
Bad jokes and rotten luck - with lies,
Rhymes of self-pity and disgust,
My solemn thoughts which no one asked.
♬ I'm away to search
for the latest fashions, ♬
♬ I won't find any around here. ♬
♬ I don't know what I'm looking for
all alone, ♬
♬ I just want to hear some singing. ♬
♬ Do you own anything? ♬
♬ Hear, what are you selling? ♬
♬ I can buy it all from you. ♬
♬ I ended up
same way I started out. ♬
♬ Listen,
Queen's not dead. ♬
Missing
Ira, it's me. Is Nadiia home yet?
She hasn't called, either?
Tell her I called from work.
Give her my love.
Bye-bye.
So?
Good for you?
Bring something more colorful.
He's picky.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Another exhibit coming up.
This key is of huge importance.
It opens the poet's desk drawer.
Everyone agrees that after Prytuliuk died,
his manuscripts were stolen...
since the drawer was found empty.
All was gone but for the poet's last will,
in which he left the table to me.
They reached out to me
from the Prytuliuk Museum...
looking to get the desk.
Good luck with that.
They're aligned with Sukhohryz.
Sukhohryz who destroyed the poet's
first printed work.
We're about to see the desk.
Oksana's place? No, thanks.
No one's home, I called.
Though if you see Oksana, honk the horn.
Danylo, you're a horse's ass,
you know that?
Can we learn more about Sukhohryz?
You may.
Sukhohryz ordered...
for the whole first edition
to go into the recycling facility.
The editor, Nina Shans,
kept several copies hidden.
Danylo was lucky: Nina had close ties
to the communist party.
Come in.
I have a key, and there's nobody home.
Don't sweat.
Come in.
Some more exhibits
which will go to the Prytuliuk Museum.
He was the best cyclist
of his neighborhood.
And here, ladies and gentlemen,
is what we came here for.
The famous desk,
and its famous drawer.
Full of rhymes and inspiration.
Take your trash away,
I'm changing locks.
It's for you.
They want to know more
about the political ties.
Yes, there's a poem about it.
There's a poem.
Just a moment.
One day, when I die,
Will I burn in hell?
Weather's warm and dry.
Thus, it's hard to tell.
6 am...
The architect is Rastrelli. What a shame.
[pun: Rastrelli sounds like "was executed"]
6 am - no kidding! -
Stars are shining bright.
I am in the city.
Foggy is my mind.
♬ I'm no fool, I can tell
I drink way too much vodka! ♬
♬ My neighbour had a drink with me -
I think I love her now. ♬
♬ Help a guy out, please -
pour me another one! ♬
♬ I'm no fool, I can tell
I drink way too much vodka! ♬
Interesting.
Let's go.
Just some asshole.
Call me.
♬ Oh, I want a rich woman! ♬
♬ Oh, I want a woman
of such and such sort. ♬
♬ I'm so glad we've met each other! ♬
Don't fall asleep.
Cigarettes.
Bilomorkanal!
He doesn't bite.
Thank you.
Nina Shans!
You too?
Let's go.
♬ I want a rich woman! ♬
♬ Oh, I want a woman
of such and such sort. ♬
♬ How fortunate that we've met! ♬
Did this poem's manuscript survive?
Sukhohryz took care of it.
Tell her the woman in the car
saved Danylo's life.
It was Nina Shans.
Liudmyla, is Nadiia with you?
She went where?
How do you mean, airport?
What do you mean, flew home?
If I'd known, I wouldn't have called.
Perhaps you
bought her the ticket too, huh?
Thanks. Thanks a bunch.
I have no time to chat with you.
Tell me. Wait, tell me,
what's the Lviv city code?
Ok. Close it down.
Are you about to head off?
Yes.
Wait a second.
Get out of there. Get out.
Let's go.
I know a poem too.
One of Prytuliuk's earliest.
Olia, translate, please.
I don't pass my in-law's house
Without doing something nice.
Pull my... nose... out, tease a little,
Then I moon her with my... ear.
They ask where did all the drafts
and manuscripts go.
There weren't any drafts.
Danylo showed me the desk drawer once.
Empty.
Still, he kept
a key with him at all times.
He told me
he keeps the ideas in the drawer.
That tragic day,
he had the key with him as well.
Tragic?
He drowned.
How did it happen?
I'll be damned.
He was saving a child.
And did he succeed?
Yes, this boy is 25 now.
Last two years, in jail.
Wow. For what?
For robbing a cash truck.
Terrible.
What happened then?
- To the cash truck?
- No, no, Prytuliuk.
- Some said he couldn't swim...
- What's the hurry!
Some say he couldn't swim.
Some say he was too drunk.
Some say someone
"helped" him drown.
Only Nina Shans knows the truth.
She was with him that day.
After that she went cuckoo.
She spends
every summer in an institution.
God damn. Fuck.
Pardon. Pardon. Two minutes.
What happened?
The damned pump.
The pump!
Help me out here, Bohdan.
Listen.
You translate in a peculiar way.
How do you manage the verse?
It's gotta be hard.
Not really.
It was all in my university thesis.
What thesis?
Ukrainian folksongs in English.
(reads incoherent poetry)
This country brought me pain.
Brought me pain.
Pavlov Psychiatric Hospital
A Study of History, by Arnold Toynbee
Lukian.
Oh, hello. You came back?
Have you seen Nina?
Nina, Nina, Nina, Nina...
She ran away two days ago.
- The search is on.
- The search is on?
The search is on. Do come in.
She's not in there, she was sent home.
She got better.
Imagine, bringing flowers to a lunatic.
Damn you all.
If I knew what this day will turn into,
like hell I would've shown up.
Well, there you are.
They say your tour is no good.
What's not to like?
They are tired of empty drawers,
absent people and missing fences.
What does she want to see then?
Something substantial,
to film and to show at home.
Oh.
I can show you the poet's peasant house,
but it's in the Zone.
In the Zone?
Chornobyl zone.
And who's gonna let us in there?
No one.
We'll go to Feofaniia instead.
[a park with historic architecture]
It's closed down today.
Even better.
We won't go through the main entrance.
I'll lead the way. Let's go.
Here we go again...
Always at lunchtime.
Okay, we're here.
Now move backwards a little.
No entrance
Yes.
Ladies and gentlemen, behind that fence
lies the Chornobyl zone.
Over there, a house.
In that very house, the poet was born.
They are asking what are
these people doing here.
People?
They're used to it. It's safe on this side.
The zone starts only after the fence.
And the horses?
Those are wild horses. Mustangs.
Okay, let's move on.
We shouldn't stay here for long.
I will now show you the place
where Danylo wrote his last poem.
Hello, granddad! Thank you!
[with a strong accent]
What does she want?
Bring it on. Prytuliuk's last poem.
In this very spot,
his last poem was written.
Who had set this town ablaze?..
Who had drank the blood and brains?
Causing enemies to rot,
Gods of vengeance, are you not?..
We had send them all to rot
Firing steady from our Grad
[Grad = Soviet rocket launcher]
After all the shots we've fired,
Sat in ruins, a little tired.
Who can read the stars and tell
Where to drill to find a well?
We're all family, understood?
Step ahead, if someone could.
All is quiet but for one man,
In his back, a deadly wound.
Some are fallen, still we're plenty.
Kitchen here is an ordeal.
Step ahead who'd like to turn
Those camelthorns into a meal?
Step ahead who'd like to try it!
All are quiet...
But for one man,
In his back, a deadly wound.
Who knows how to wash his clothes?
Who does all the household chores?
All are quiet, of course relying
On a man with a deadly wound.
"Who can build a house from blocks?"
"I can,"
said the deadly wounded.
"Who can sew and patch our socks?"
"I can,"
said the deadly wounded.
"Who can fix a pair of shoes?"
"I can,"
said the deadly wounded.
"Who can sing some pretty tunes?"
"I can,"
said the deadly wounded.
"Who can bake a piece of bread?"
"I can," said the deadly wounded.
"Treat the wounded, bury dead?"
"Sing a child a lullaby?"
"I can," said the deadly wounded.
"Pray to God above the sky?"
"If you're lying, you are dead!"
"Me?",
the deadly wounded said.
"I don't lie and don't you doubt it."
"You're a stupid ass, you got it?"
"I'll destroy you, no remorse,
I will drown you like a puppy!
15 mins to prove your worth."
Don't get lost, Oksana!
Come inside, brothers.
Any manuscripts left?
Or Sukhohryz again?
Of course Sukhohryz.
You said it was the last poem. Why?
It went in print...
the day the Afghan war started.
If not for Nina Shans,
you know what awaited him.
Danylo quit writing.
Why?
Lost the taste for it.
Have you seen anything like this
in America?
Paper recycling plant.
Produces toilet paper.
Danylo, is this Sukhohryz?
No, it's a prominent novelist.
It's not Sukhohryz.
Sukhohryz is higher up.
He's in the office.
Oh, hey, Danylo. You still alive?
Alive, can't you see?
Is she filming me right now?
She is. Americans,
you know how they are.
They came to see how poetry
becomes toilet paper.
Oh well. It's a complicated process.
It's not some juvenile scribbling.
It's physics!
Let's go!
Danylo, wrap this tour up, will you?
We're taking them to lunch now.
You, meanwhile, go find Nina Shans,
whatever it takes.
They want to meet her.
Pavlo Shans, Prof.
Nina.
Nina!
This day is full of surprises.
I still can't wrap my head around it.
The tour keeps taking us
to various addresses from your mail.
Happy holiday.
Why aren't you
at lunch with the others?
Stupid...
Let's go.
Dear sailors! Happy holiday.
I salute you! Safe travels.
Yours, Nina Pavlovna Shans.
Moscow, Kremlin.
Nina Shans
No one's home.
Such a bitch.
Nina!
Move.
How did you get home yesterday?
- Yesterday?
- Yes.
I see now.
What do you see?
On the bridge, remember?
- Do you?
- Remember what?
Ah.
- What do you see?
- You don't even remember the bridge.
I remember the park on the river.
Are you at it again?
Again, fighting for
the freedom of the press?
Nina!
How many times do I have to tell you!
Lenin has been dead for a while!
Give him peace.
Better tell me
what happened in the park.
First of all, it happened...
not in the park,
but on the footbridge.
And the police...
Is it coming back to you now?
Who is she?
She's American, can't you tell?
You're into foreign chicks now?
Why is she filming you?
She's in love. Don't you mind.
Tell me, what's
the city code for Lviv?
The code is 32.
What was that about the police?
Aha!
It's the third time I'm saving his life.
From the police?
What's the police
got to do with it?
Are you mad? Are you making fun of me?
- You don't remember, do you?
- I do!.
- He doesn't remember
what brought him to the bridge!
I went to get paint.
Yes. You went to get it from Tolik.
From Tolik.
Of course, it was obvious when I saw you
that you're getting the paint from Tolik.
- Enough.
- Enough what?
I went to the bridge. Then what?
Then what, then shmat.
One more second and you'd be done for,
that's what.
What's with the forehead?
Nina, it is true?
It is.
If not for Sukhohryz, you'll be dead.
Sukhohryz?
It's warm out.
He's selling his books on the bridge.
Okay, let's hurry up.
Let's go.
In the car, come on.
Let's go!
Didn't they want to see
where the poet has drowned?
It happened right here.
He and Nina
were walking across the bridge.
And then, police,
lifeguards, everybody...
Right here is where it all happened.
Right here, is where the poet died.
Top grade poems.
Top grade.
Who can read the stars and tell
Where to drill to find a well?
We're all family, understood?
Step ahead, if someone could...
...drag us out from utter shit.
Meet Sukhohryz.
Sukhohryz, pleased to meet you.
Take a picture of me with the poet.
Like that.
Americans or something?
- Yes.
- Well, thank you.
Will they buy the books?
Ask them.
Take a look. Cheap prices.
"The Art of Gambling."
I'll be damned.
I saved his life. Yesterday.
Right here.
He's a genius, but an idiot.
- Hello.
- Well, finally! How are you?
Oh, hi. I'm good. I'm all alone.
Hello?
The sound of trumpet summoned me...
(mumbles)
The trumpet was a telephone,
The call was all a ruse.
Hello.
I'm calling now,
My eyes at rest.
I used to beg on churches' steps.
Now I don't need your pity dime,
I pay for every word I rhyme.
I'd gladly pay the whole amount,
But, see, my thoughts are on discount.
On discount.
Again, I hear the phone demand
I heed it's tired shrill command.
But I have used up all replies.
Please say...
Please say it's
someone else you've called.
Please say you don't know me at all.
Hello.
So glad you're on the phone.
Oh, hi. I'm good. I'm all alone.
Last night, I didn't sleep at all.
I stayed up, watching
the seventh route videotapes.
Here it is, apartment 5.
My plane leaves in three hours,
and I had to come back
to these mysterious ruins.
You know what I want to ask you about.
Three envelopes, sent from this address.
You haven't opened them. Why?
Stay back!
Password!
Such a nice camera.
I wonder if it works.
I know that you're aware that I'm aware:
My rope's about
to end right now and there.
And I'm not telling you exactly where:
You know that
I'm aware that you're aware.
You know that I'm aware...
...that you're aware.
I won't be hiding from
my own damn stare.
Won't give advice, won't help,
I wouldn't dare
Whilst knowing
you're aware that I'm aware.
Today?
Now?
"I can," said the deadly wounded.
No, no. We must...
What a stupid girl.
Stop! To the airport.
Stop!
You're going the wrong way!
A complete horse's ass.
Where do you need to go?
She says we must bury it.
Bury what?
A dog.
She says some dog got hit by a car.
Have you seen it?
I saw it.
She says we must bury it.
Bury it, huh!
What a burial!
Having dreams can be sweet.
Having dreams can be sad.
In the morning, they taste
Like that last cigarette.
On the railroad tracks
Sleep is cozy and tight,
Sky is your shiny blanket,
There's no stress on your mind.
Sleep is deep and rewarding
When your roof is ablaze:
You're a reckless teenager,
Dreams are light like a haze.
Sleep is good while you're jumping
Far away and high up;
Not for everyone, true, but
I don't want it to stop.
Proper bed is excessive:
Maybe too much to ask,
But just once, try some asphalt
Or a mattress of grass.
In the morning, I'm adding
To my dream almanac
Children hungry for love,
Parents not loving back.
I am lucky like this:
I am dreaming today
Of that someone I've missed
Long ago, far away.
Dovzhenko Film Studios, 1996