(sheep barking)
(slaughter sound)
(sheep screaming)
(bell sound)
(♫tense music building♫)
Whoever finds this, be careful,
and leave before sunset.
I came here to find my daughter,
but there are so many more.
They all seem to be cursed.
I don't know if I can help,
I don't know if I'll survive.
I can feel Lissy is here,
but I cannot connect with her.
One of them came close to me.
I tried to take a photo,
but it just disappeared.
I have reason to believe
they're after me and my life.
I'm not sure how I can help
get Lissy out of...
(tense breathing)
Hit that like button!
Click the link in the bio!
The first influencer suicide
in Koh Samui is now confirmed.
13 year old Susan Chang's
body has been found.
Just hit 10,000 followers,
you guys mean the world to me.
I have months and months of giveaways.
The global health
organization reported that
social media is now the No. 1
cause for suicide and addictive behavior.
Oh my god, my tribe is so amazing.
I love you guys!
I have a month's giveaway.
Sebastian Kraft, the overnight
sensation amongst influencer coaches
is set to give a weekend
workshop in Thailand.
#clean living Don't forget to subscribe!
It's Blue Moon tonight,
prepare yourself with my breath-work.
#blessed. Subscribe!
That's for my friends!
I have a month's giveaway.
Like! Share! Subscribe!
I love you guys.
(♫ pop music ♫)
(cell phone notification)
Hi, welcome, make sure you sign in here.
Thanks.
(♫ pop music becomes louder ♫)
(cell phone vibrating)
And now welcome: "Sebastian Kraft"
Alright.
Clap your hands.
That's right.
(clapping and chanting)
Why are you here?
I mean it, why are you here?
Because we want to get rich and famous.
Okay.
Fair enough, but I had
plenty of people,
who are already rich and famous
come to my seminars.
Why do they come then?
No idea.
You're here, because you want more.
You want more than you already have.
And there's zero shame in that.
It is human nature to want to improve.
It is your birthright to want more.
Who wants more?
Yeah.
Me, yeah.
I want more.
I wanna take something away from you.
I wanna take away an excuse you might make.
(coughing)
Who here uses a sentence sometimes like
"I need to learn how to appear confident."
Or "I need to learn how to say yes."
Who said a sentence like this before?
"I need to learn to..."
Yeah, you have?
I have. Let me tell you something.
You don't need to "learn"
how to appear confident.
You don't need to "learn" how to say yes.
You need to "choose" to say yes.
(coughing intensifies)
Can we please get rid of the cougher?
Scared of Corona?
Corona is fake, but what about 5G?
My god, let's not
start this nonsense again.
It's probably just normal influenza.
Normal influencer?
I'm one of the top influencers
in my country.
Guys, guys, a virus won't kill you.
Hiding from choices will kill you!
Okay, "choosing versus learning",
how many people in this room
know how to pronounce the word "Yes"?
Anybody? Yeah?
You know how to pronounce the word "Yes"?
Oh, good.
Anybody here still needs
to learn how to pronounce the word "Yes"?
Anybody?
Okay, smarty pants over here,
you need to learn that?
Shall we practice together
how to say a three letter word?
Look, I just don't think the
choice is that easy for most of us.
People have really deeply
ingrained ideas about
what they can and can't do.
That is exactly my point.
Okay, well, with smaller
risk free decisions
just going for it
and choosing yes might be fine,
but with more complicated decisions
we often need to learn skills
in order to trust ourselves.
Okay, let's try this.
What do you still need to learn?
Well, I mean all of us here
Don't speak for all of us here,
just speak for yourself.
Okay, well...
I'm here, so I guess I wanna
learn how to self-promote.
Okay, is there something
that you already know,
that would promote you like crazy,
but you're not doing it yet?
I'm really trying to let
the quality of my writing dictate
The quality of your writing
dictates fuck all
if nobody reads your writing
in the first place.
Do you want your social
media channels to explode?
Sure!
Do you know how to post a selfie?
But that's exactly the kind
Do you, just in theory, know
how to post a bikini picture of yourself?
Of course, but I choose
You, my dear, choose to miss out.
God or nature or whomever
gave you a killer body,
and killer looks.
Good for you!
And you can choose to use
that to your advantage or not.
Most of the horse faces
in this room would kill
for your looks and use it immediately.
I'm here to show you
the choices that will lead you to success.
What you do with
them is your responsibility.
But never forget, it is a choice.
(♫ tense music starting ♫)
Guys, try and "learn" success,
and you will learn forever.
"Choose" success and you will succeed.
Who wants to be successful?
Yeah!?
Woo.
Woo, yes.
(clapping hands)
(mysterious music)
(people chatting)
In order to create engaging content
you have to do two things:
A: Never stop.
B: Always keep moving.
Who here needs to keep moving?
Who here needs to transition further?
Yeah?
Anybody? Anybody?
There you go.
Introduce yourself.
Get up, get up.
Hi guys, I'm Isla from Budapest,
but I have been living here
in Thailand for 8 years.
I'm divorced, I have two children.
I'm an influencer,
a self love coach and
own a fitness studio that
is doing really well, but I feel like
I need to transition it into
something completely new.
I'm just holding back for some reason.
So, your studios are going well?
Yeah, it's doing really well.
And your channels are going well as well?
They're still growing,
but they are already super profitable.
So, why transition it into
something completely new then?
Well, I just feel like I'm
at that stage of my life.
Isla, when was the last time you had
a big old dick in your mouth?
(♫ tense music ♫)
Excuse me?
When was the last time
someone went down on you
and licked your pussy until you screamed:
"Oh my God, oh my God,
that's so amazing,
oh yeah, oh yeah."
When?
Yeah.
Really?
When?
Two years ago...
Two fucking years ago!
Never!
Never ever ever project your
own fucking misery onto your business.
You will destroy it.
If you wanna go out there
and reinvent yourself,
and suck dick then you have
to do that all by yourself.
Do you wanna go out there
and get your pussy licked?
Well, as a mother
As a mother what?
As a mother you don't have a clit anymore?
You're a fucking hotty.
I would lick your pussy in a heartbeat.
Any other man here would
like to lick Isla's pussy?
Yes. Sure.
I would.
Or woman!
(crowd no ice)
Well, well, well, who do we have here?
The PC police.
And you are?
I am an impactfluencer.
A fucking what?
An impactfluencer,
an influencer that has an impact.
Anyway, I was born as a CIS man,
but I now identify as "they".
He, she, it, they,
I don't give a flying fuck
what you identify as.
I give a fuck
if you leave this place
a righteous asshole,
or a positive, motivated,
ready to take on the world, they!
So, which one will it be?
Well, the second one of course!
Give it up for "they".
(hands clapping)
Be interested in the world,
the world will be interested in you.
Be interested in someone's dick,
(croud cheering)
They will be interested in your pussy.
(cheering and clapping)
Give it up for Isla!
Give it up for Isla, come on, come on.
(♫ tense music starting ♫)
The trending hashtags at the moment are:
♪ Climatewar, ♪the end is near,
and ♪thevirusisahoax.
They are not:
#lets be nice and neutral to each other.
Think about that
when you create content for your channels.
Be loud! Be edgy!
Be ruthless, and shit will
take off by itself for you.
Guys, you've been absolutely amazing.
I also wanna invite you for
a focus group tomorrow
on this property.
It's a very small, intense group,
and you will gain inside knowledge
on how to gain 1 million followers.
So, go book your spot.
But now, shall we party it up?
Shall we have a party?
Shall we party it up?
Come on! Come on!
(hands clapping)
(♫ pop music ♫)
Fucking party it up!
Hey guys, today I want to
inspire you to live your life
the way you want to,
and you can start the new journey
by downloading my ebook and...
Work hard and play harder motherfuckers.
If you wanna be with me
at these kind of parties,
then you have to push yourself,
level up, and swipe up
for my business program.
Guys, dance like no one's watching,
believe in yourself
and take the next step...
(♫ pop music ♫)
(♫ dark mysterious music ♫)
(birds chirping)
My God, it's gonna be amazing.
I know, I can' wait.
Welcome to heaven guys.
I'm super glad that you guys
committed to the focus group today.
We live in a world,
where nobody knows what's true anymore,
where everyone and anyone
is allowed to create a truth.
Especially on social media.
So, how can we take advantage of that?
I'm not really sure about the truth thing,
I think that attention trumps everything,
including the truth.
Okay, fair enough,
but authentic sides of your persona,
that create attention
are twice as powerful for your channels.
Has anyone got an example for that, maybe?
Yes, introduce yourself!
Hi everyone, you know me already,
my name is Grace,
I'm half Russian, half Argentinian.
I'm 25 and I've been an
influencer for 15 years.
I wrote a book about my
life that is very truthful,
and will get your attention.
And what's your book called?
It's called: "Me and Mary Magdalene,
christians, prostitutes and feminists."
Wow, talking about authentic attention.
Does that title grab your attention?
Yeah, definitely.
Fuck yes, it does.
Anyone else? Louis?
How about you?
Hey guys, so I sell an online
business marketing program,
but where I get my real attention is on my
second Youpipe channel called
"Only Milfs for this guy".
It's a parody on porn.
Fuck yes!
Talk about attention!
Remember, any attention is good attention!
Why?
Because any attention will make
people land on your channels.
It will make them land on your products!
Good god!
"Queen of doubt" would like to speak again?
Any attention is good attention?
Should I use my mom's death
to increase my following?
Yes, you should!
Posts with #funeral are
8 times more popular.
That's sick!
That's not sick.
I'm here to tell you how
to increase your following.
It is my only and absolute only incentive,
but I think you have a
fundamental hate for success.
Of course I wanna be successful,
but not in this sicko selfish way.
I want success for me and others.
This might sound bullshit-hippie,
but I think it's a lot healthier approach
than this narcissistic
me, me, me attitude.
It's not bullshit hippie.
It's beautiful!
You go girl.
So, you think that you are
better than all of us?
That you're going to save the world?
Maybe I just wanna improve it a bit?
So, let me tell you something.
With that attitude,
you're going to end up in a 9 to 5 job,
making someone else rich.
After that, you become depressed
about slaving away for others.
In the end you'll be
whining to your therapist
about how "unfair the world is".
Is that what you want?
Of course not!
Exactly.
What do you do?
I'm a writer.
Okay, what if I told you,
I can make you so popular
in the next 10 minutes
that you can sell your writing,
whatever it is, for the next
three months like this?
Be my guest.
Challenge accepted.
Okay, everyone here
get out your cell phones and start filming.
What is your social media name?
(♫ tense music ♫)
@Mia_writer
Okay, @Mia_writer.
Okay, you will all film how
Mia and I here will have a massive fight.
And then you will shout
at me and shout at us:
"You are all influencer scum,
especially you Sebastian,
"you fucking creep" And you will get up,
you will rip open your shirt,
and you will shout:
"Is that what you want to see,
you cheap bastard?"
Then all of us will post those
videos on our channels,
tag you and use the hashtag
#hot writer goes crazy
It's amazing idea!
How do you sleep at night?
I sleep in a multi million dollar mansion
lying next to a model.
(♫ dark music ♫)
Hey.
So, are you pumped to conquer the world?
He does make you want to go
out there and do things.
You have to give it to him.
With a very aggressive energy though.
True, I do you feel like punching someone.
Have you been here before?
This place looks strangely familiar.
Guys, being unconscious
comes from unhappiness,
unhappiness from desire, desire from fear,
fear from uncertainty.
So, trust is the way to achieve
and heal consciousness.
(♫ mysterious music ♫)
No, they love it.
Yes.
No, I actually think that all
of them will go for it.
Yeah... No, I mean I can suggest it.
Alright, I'll see you later.
(door shuts)
Isn't it beautiful here?
It sure is.
It's Isla, right?
I'm Rick.
I know.
So, what brought you here?
Well, I'm building the biggest brothel
in the world here in Koh Samui.
You know, labor is super cheap here,
and I'm at the seminar to learn
about social media marketing.
And how I can use it to become
an influencer for my brothel business.
Wow, okay.
I'm not sure how I feel about that.
Well, I can help you feel
something if you like.
(♫ tense music building ♫)
(♫ dark music ♫)
Hey!
What are you doing there?
I'm just...
I thought I had left something.
We are taking a group picture, wanna join?
Okay.
Yeah, let's go.
One - two - three.
So, which hotty are you guys after?
Hot tea?
Which one of the girls are you after?
Left one, definitely! You?
The Jesus girl is cute.
Oh yeah.
Or Mia - the serious ones are
always super kinky.
Please guys!
"Guys please", what's that
supposed to mean?
Don't be so stuck up,
you need to relax a little!
I find Isla intriguing.
She has something I don't have.
Character!
Yeah, maybe.
Wait, what?!?!
Don't waste your time on dates
and dinner and all that bullshit.
In a couple weeks they'll all
be working for me.
I'll give you a Corona discount,
much cheaper that way.
(laughter)
Hi, I am Chloe,
I am a sacred femininity pioneer,
and a magic fire dancer,
and what I need to choose
is to become a global femininity icon.
I want to empower women
from all over the world.
Wow.
Okay, and how do you empower women?
By guiding them to discover and share their
divine feminine beauty.
That is amazing.
Women should never be scared
to show their beauty,
show a little curve,
show a little skin, use what you have.
Little titty, little ass, anything, okay.
Well, I was more talking about
awakening your inner goddess power.
Okay, Chloe, how many followers
have you got?
300,000.
Okay, and you have 300,000 followers
because of your goddess power
or your titties?
Sorry?
You have 300k followers because of
your goddess power or your titties?
So, I should hide my god given beauty
because perverts like you
constantly sexualise women's bodies?
Can you still see true beauty in a woman?
Chloe, I can see true beauty
all around the room here.
I'm not fighting you.
I'm applauding you for
using what you have.
And what I have is cosmic radiant beauty.
And that's why people follow me,
and it's why I can make other women shine.
(♫ pop music ♫)
Let's go to see Isla.
Yeah.
Hey, Isla.
Have you seen the little
Asian kids from earlier?
I think they went that way.
Oh, but let's take a selfie.
(♫ pop music continues ♫)
Koen, can you take a picture of us?
I'm not really taking a picture...
Please! Please!
I can take a picture of you girls.
Thank you.
How many followers have you got?
About 200.
200,000. Amazing.
No, no, just 200.
(♫ interruptive music ♫)
Let's get out of here, keep walking.
Just keep walking.
Oh, hey Louis.
Hi.
Have you seen those
Asian kids from earlier?
We want to take a pic how we
give them food with the basket.
Yeah, no.
Give me one minute, alright?
Let's just take pictures without the kids.
Or I can pretend to hold
out my hand like a kid,
and you just take a selfie with
the basket and my hand.
That is so true, and we can still
inspire people to do the same.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
(♫ pop music continues ♫)
Like this?
Yeah.
Ah, that's nice.
Wow, so good.
We got it!
Or I can hold my hand like this,
so it looks like a disabled child.
That's amazing, let's do it.
Oh my God, look, look, look.
It's amazing.
Wow.
So good, oh my god.
I told you, she ran away!
It was your fucking job to get her back.
What hashtags are you using, guys?
Nobody cares about hashtags anymore.
What you have to do is ask questions,
and make them comment.
Or, tagging.
Tag somebody that needs to be with us.
I always do it with psalms.
Psalms?
Which psalm would fit this place?
I love palms!
How many people usually read your posts?
An average of 18,000.
Mine is around 56k, and yours?
Well, I mean...
I write longer articles,
and I don't use social media all that much.
Hey, food is ready.
You know, Louis is really amazing
with his creative marketing.
I will ask him if he wants to get together.
Yes, yes.
I will also ask him.
Sex sells.
And that is why you should
invest in my new brothels.
Hmm.
I have an option for you, 500$ a month.
Ongoing accumulation on my market.
What I want is you involved
in an ongoing basis,
for marketing purposes.
Now, what do you think about this:
Slick-Ricks-Flatrate-Chicks,
the brothel so big you can't bang them all.
Unbelievable.
Get lost in the largest
bossom in the world.
Wow, you two should try out
this crazy thing one day.
And what is that?
It's called listening.
Just shut up know-it-all.
You really want to build a brothel here?
I already own three brothels here.
You know, I have some upscale clients,
who are always looking
for some entertainment
that is also intellectually stimulating.
I mean if you're ever interested...
Are you serious?
Absolutely!
You could make a killing honey.
(♫ tense music building ♫)
They all come back eventually.
Sometimes you have to drag
them back from their village.
What the...?
Really annoying!
Inner and outer beauty go hand in hand,
you feel one, you feel the other.
Yesterday, Sebastian made me
experience my inner beauty again.
What is inner beauty?
Just that feeling of liking yourself.
Is beauty or health more
important to you girls?
How much do you weigh honey?
60 kg.
That's my suicide weight.
Your what?
Nothing! You're right, health
is so much more important.
Do you mind me asking
if you've had things done?
I mean...
Of course she did,
and there is no shame in that.
All of us did I think.
I got some lipo on my waist,
and a tiny bit of Botox, just here.
Same, I only did small adjustments.
I like the natural look.
And, uh you, Isla?
Well, of course I've had things done.
You have to, to keep up, you know.
Looks are not as important as
you think they are for us.
For me, it's really secondary.
My faith is first and foremost.
Your face?
My faith!
Ah, faith.
And the book you wrote,
is that autobiographical?
Yes, it is.
I'm a devoted Christian,
a high class escort and a feminist.
I also do girls if you're interested,
but I'm $800 an hour.
Good to know.
Maybe I'll book you one day.
You want a little free tester?
(♫ mysterious music ♫)
You girls are hot.
Anyway, I don't think there is
anything wrong with what I do.
I don't either, but I'm sure
there's some people thinking
a little differently.
Well, the uneducated ones.
But I always make them understand,
that today's culture makes them confused.
I respect you Grace, you're amazing.
(♫ soft music building ♫)
Hey, girls.
Let's go down to the stream.
Come on, let's go.
Come on Gaia, let's go, clean your spirits.
Oh, perfect, I haven't done
a cleanse in four weeks.
(♫ tense music building ♫)
(♫ tense music continues♫)
Just follow my lead when we get there,
I have a heightened awareness
of these things.
I can't wait to feel the power.
This stream is gonna be amazing.
Look guys, it's the stream.
The gardener said it has magical powers.
It's called spirituality.
(soft ghost whispers)
Give me a hand.
Careful honey.
Yeah, step here.
Don't let my hand go, please.
I will miss you when you're gone.
(♫ disruptive music ♫)
Don't feel like going down?
(jungle sounds)
Not really.
What about you?
I don't want to gain too
many special powers.
Yes.
Nice one.
Grace, you don't wanna join?
Is she okay?
She's crying.
She is crying?
(crying)
She shouldn't do this as a born-again.
She's a grown up, she can
do whatever she wants.
Sometimes it's better for the
blind if they stay blind,
cause once they see,
the bright light hurts.
Shut the fuck up.
(♫ mysterious music ♫)
Is she okay?
Grace.
Okay Gaia, this is your chance,
go and be nice to her.
(crying continues)
Thank you Grace,
for being so mature and
showing your emotions.
You're so powerful.
It's okay, just breathe.
(♫ tense music building ♫)
What the hell are you doing?
What?
You're grabbing my ass!
What? No!
You had your hand right here, you perv.
What are you talking about?
Guys, I didn't
#me too all over again guys.
That's not #me too.
Of course that's #me too.
No it's not!
Guys, guys, guys, wait, wait, wait.
Where exactly was the hand?
Here.
Look, my hand was on the hip.
Not the ass, the hip.
Okay, that's not #me too,
#me too starts down here.
What the fuck!
Look guys, reality is subjective
due to our own perception of
Shut up you perv.
Did you ever rape someone?
No, no!
Of course not.
And you had to think about that?
Oh my God!
Honey, come here.
Guys, I just witnessed sexual assault.
Men, if you touch a woman,
then ask her before.
Never hug a woman without consent.
You okay?
Let me give you a hug.
(♫ soft mysterious music ♫)
Is she okay?
There's something about this place.
Maybe we are here for a reason.
Maybe we're here for someone else's reason.
(♫ dark music ♫)
No, it fucking wasn't.
You know how to fucking
upload a video to Youpipe,
so you know how to fucking
start a fucking channel, correct?
It's still hard to become a star.
What you really want to know, Koen,
is how do I have the balls to go about it.
How do I choose?
So let's try this.
Let's try this little experiment here.
Koen here, Mr Comedy, will tell us a joke.
And then none of us will laugh.
Just as an experiment.
Can we agree on that?
Get up.
Get up, tell us a fucking joke.
You can do it.
Murphy's Law says that anything
that can go wrong, will go wrong.
Cole's law is thinly sliced cabbage.
So.
Did you die?
No, I'm well alive!
Then try it again.
Tell a joke?
Yes.
Tell a fucking joke,
this time if it's funny
everyone will laugh,
or hottie next to you
will give you a little kiss.
Whatever happens happens,
tell a fucking joke.
Thinking a mask is going to stop Corona
is the same as thinking
that your underwear will protect
everyone from a fart.
(soft laughter)
Well done.
In order to be successful,
you have to stop caring about
other people's feelings.
Stop caring how people feel?
Yes, stop caring how people
feel about what you say.
What a sad world that would be.
What a free world that would be,
if everyone and anyone says
whatever they want in any given moment.
So, we should just allow everyone
to hate on anyone they want?
How does any violence on earth start?
With hate speech!
Honey, we don't live in la la land.
Why is everybody so much against
conflict and hanger anyway?
Hanger?
Yeah, hanger.
You guys have to pick up your failures,
your heartbreaks, your problems.
Everything!
And just turn it into fuel for motivation
Okay, okay, thank you so much.
That was great.
Look, look at fucking Koen.
If he was constantly scared
of offending people,
then he won't be able to start
a fucking Youpipe channel.
He won't be able to start
any fucking business.
He's already semi domesticated as is.
Look at him.
What he really wants to do
is to be raw, alive, aggressive,
young and be successful.
And that's what it's all about.
Success!
Who wants to be successful here?
Who wants to be successful?
(cheering)
(♫ tense music ♫)
(moaning)
You're so smart, I really like you.
What time are they picking us up?
Sebastian, you said they will
be here soon right?
Yes, they are here soon.
Just ask him.
Don't be shy.
Nah, maybe later.
You're so cute.
Look, there is no later,
and it's right there.
You're so beautiful.
You got a nice dick.
(soft moaning)
I love you.
(laughter)
I mean on a spiritual level.
I can feel you.
Okay.
How did you become this kind of person?
I started adjusting my behavior
only to what sells and what doesn't.
What increases my following
and what doesn't.
If you guys adjust your behavior
only to the truth,
if you face the truth,
listen to the truth,
then you're unstoppable.
Wow, that's absolutely amazing.
It was an awesome event and
I took so much out of it.
Anytime, anytime.
You think anyone here actually
gets one million followers
from this event?
You're a bit negative, Mia.
Yeah, you've got such a
negative attitude, darling.
Just because she's smarter than you,
doesn't mean she's negative.
Whatever.
He's talking about the power of truth.
Right now the only one with
a million followers is him,
and I doubt any of us is gonna get to that
in the next days.
Yeah, not with that attitude
that's for sure.
But, one tool I use that I haven't shared
with you yet.
And what's that?
You really want to know?
I just said yes didn't I?
(♫ bell sound ♫)
Witchcraft.
Wow, the dark side.
No, no, no.
It's white magic.
It's not dangerous if you
know how to use it.
And how do you use it?
Well, there's a Thai witch
on this property actually.
And you can go to her,
and she can make anything you want happen.
That's where I got my success from.
Sounds amazing.
How does it work?
An assistant comes and you have
to pay him and he brings you to her,
and then you just ask her
for whatever you want.
That's actually where I got
my first million followers.
Are you serious?
Yes.
How much?
To see her?
No, to fly to Hong Kong.
Yes, to see her.
How much?
$1,000
Let's go guys!
You mean now?
Fuck yeah, I mean now.
An opportunity like this.
This is what I've been waiting for.
Seriously, who's in?
What the hell, it's only a thousand bucks.
Chloe?
Yes, okay.
You?
Yes or no? Are you in?
Yes, let's do it.
Koen?
I'm in, yeah.
Grace?
Of course!
You in?
Yes, sir.
Would you come with us?
Sure, I can come along.
Mia?
Wanna join us?
(♫ mysterious music ♫)
Yeah.
Yeah, if you all want to, I can set it up.
Yeah?
Of course.
I'll set it up.
So nice.
(♫ tense music ♫)
(♫ rhythmical dark music ♫)
Look, he's here.
Get up guys.
He's here.
(♫ music continues ♫)
Hey, why did you let go?
Hello?
(jungle sounds)
Hello? What's going on?
Um, I think, I think we arrived.
Are we allowed to take it off?
Yeah, well, the guy who let
us here let go of my hand, so...
Yeah, I think so.
Wow.
And now, who goes first?
Go where?
I don't know.
Are we supposed to do something?
I'm not sure...
I'm...
You don't seem so sure,
I thought you have done this before?
Well, it's up to Venefica to decide
when to appear, you know.
Guys, that's...
It's the freaking villa right there.
What?
How is that possible?
(♫ mysterious music ♫)
We walked like what, 50 meters?
What?
I don't know, let's just go back up.
Yeah.
Yeah okay, why not.
(♫ mysterious music building ♫)
Be careful, watch your step.
What the fuck!
(♫ mysterious music continues ♫)
I can't believe this is the same Villa.
This can't be the same villa.
How di they...?
What is this?
Where did all the furniture go?
I can feel her presence already.
Guys, guys, come here, come, come, come.
Come here guys.
Guys, I have an idea.
Come, listen to me.
Let's breathe together!
What?
Idiot.
And out through the mouth.
We should follow the traditional rules.
What traditional rules?
Just for the focus.
Guys, guys just be patient.
Dharma, Artha, Kama, Moksha.
Stop trying to impress the chicks,
you soy milk mocha chin a clown.
(intense surprising sound)
(♫ majestic music starts ♫)
(♫ mythical chanting and music ♫)
Whomever seeks a new kingdom
of wealth and abundance,
shall step forward.
What is your name?
Chloe.
Tell me your wish my dear.
I wanna become a global femininity icon.
Repeat after me:
I'm open and receptive to all
the wealth life offers me.
I deserve prosperity and abundance.
All my dreams will come true.
Now, close your eyes my dear.
From the power of god that I am I decree:
You shall dwell in the midst
of infinite abundance.
The abundance of god is
your infinite source.
Now, step back my dear.
Whomever seeks a new kingdom
of wealth shall step forward.
(♫ soft mysterious music continues ♫)
Hello.
I was wondering if I can
also do this for my sister.
What's your name?
Ah, yes, it's Koen.
But is it okay
Tell me your wish my dear.
Well, I had this idea to
start a Youpipe channel, but
Battery low.
What's that?
Disconnected.
What is your name?
Still Koen, same as before.
You shall have what you deserve.
No, don't shine light on me,
or the Gods will
Who are you?
I'm Venefica Bhuta,
the dark witch of prosperity.
She will curse you.
Grow some balls.
What is your name?
I'm Venefica Bhuta.
Keeper of...
Stop that nonsense.
What is your name?
You shall all be cursed.
What the heck is going on witchy?
You'll have to leave immediately,
go, go, go, go.
(♫ soft music ♫)
Mary Magdalene can save you.
You wronged people,
but all can be forgiven.
Oh fuck off!
Listen, get that guy that brought
you and he will explain it all to you.
That guy left when we
took the blindfolds off.
What? He said he would wait.
He's the one who booked me for this gig.
Gig?
Acting gig, I'm an actress.
What? Actress?
I've got a great acting gig for you,
if you ever need a job.
Really?
An actress? Using spirituality for your
own personal advantage, shame on you.
Okay, guys, my name is Kaya and
I'm an influencer from Koh Samui.
But soon
Let's look for this guy.
Come on guys,
let's go up to the restaurant.
(♫ mysterious piano music ♫)
I wanna go home.
Let's find this hooded asshole.
What do you think the refund policy is?
This is all bullshit.
I can't believe this.
(♫ mysterious music intensifies ♫)
Guys?
Hello?
Anyone?
(♫ mysterious music continues ♫)
What?
(♫ tense music building ♫)
Hello.
How can this all be like...
They must have had a lot of help.
But why?
And who are "they"?
Hello. Are you guys okay?
All the motorbikes are gone.
Seriously, it looks like the
devil was back there.
I'm out and if I were you,
I would get the fuck out too.
(sci-fi sound)
You were just...
Why would he be there?
Oh fuck!
Teleportation!
He must be the chosen one.
(sci-fi sound)
Oh my God.
How? But... What?
(chatter)
Does anyone have reception?
Somehow my phone doesn't work anymore.
We need to call for help.
Shit, same here.
No reception?
(panic chatter)
What's going on here Sebastian?
This is all his idea!
Not really.
I mean I got booked by a guy to teach
this weekend workshop.
And when I arrived he pitched me
this idea with Venefica,
and said I would get an extra $5,000.
It's not cool okay, but it's not my idea.
Not cool?
Where's our fucking money?
I don't have your money, okay.
My money!
I got scammed just like you did.
Where's my fucking money?
I got neck issues, I got neck issues.
Okay, enough.
You're such a wanker.
Yeah, you really are.
What about your social media followers?
Where did they come from?
I bought them on these
platforms in Pakistan.
You fucking dick.
And what do we do now?
I don't know.
What the fuck is going on?
And how come all our phones
have no reception all of a sudden?
Look guys, calm down, calm down.
Here's what we do,
we stay the night, okay?
And then I'll teach a night workshop,
completely free of charge and tomorrow
What are you talking about?
You guys need to chill out
We don't need to do anything.
What about her?
She did the same!
I'm just a
Guys, we don't fucking care, both of
you will go and find a way out of here,
and get our money back.
It's fucking dark,
I'm not gonna spend the night here.
Let's go this way, okay.
(jungle noises)
You go!
What, why should I take the lead?
You have got great courage.
I do have great courage.
You know what you are, you're a hero.
You know, you can talk such bullshit.
I give you $1,000 if you go first.
2000?
Okay, 2000, I've got it.
Okay.
(♫ dark music ♫)
If they're not back in an hour,
then we think of something else.
Yeah, I agree.
It doesn't hurt to think about
our next steps already.
Well, we're all thinking it,
so should we just do it?
What?
Well, we're all young.
You're not young.
Anyway, we might all die tonight,
so you know, why don't we have an orgy.
Oh my god.
Hey guys, he does have a point.
Please, you're still not
taking this seriously.
At least we can get naked
and see what happens.
(♫ mysterious music ♫)
You know...
I think we're lost.
Jesus...
(♫ tense music ♫)
You know.
You're kind of hot.
What?
No one cares about you.
(ghost whispers)
You're useless.
There is no escape.
(scream)
(♫ driving music ♫)
What was that?
Sounded like an eel.
Quiet.
I have a bad feeling.
Don't worry, nothing's gonna happen
to you, not on my watch.
I need to warn my community.
Hey guys, I'm in a
very stressful situation,
I hope I can share this video soon.
I just wanted my tribe to know that
I'm focusing inwards and on my breath.
Doesn't that ever stop?
He doesn't even have 100k followers,
it's pathetic.
I do have 23% engagement though.
Amazing.
Are you serious?
Teach us. Tell us how.
How did you do that?
Yes, how did you do that?
Well, it's not as hard as-
Engagement rates? Really?
We have to figure out what's going on here.
Exactly.
Okay, maybe someone will
come back here soon.
And what do we do until then?
Maybe it's just a stupid prank
and they pick us up soon.
Look, we just stick together
and look out for each other, okay?
Yes, one person awake minimum or two,
one in each direction, or four?
I don't know, I'm freaking out.
Guys, guys, guys.
Am I dreaming?
Oh my god.
We will play a game, every
hour you have to take a selfie.
The selfie will be posted with a poll
on your social media channels.
The person with the least
popular poll result
after 15 minutes, will die.
Can't be.
The game will start at exactly 10 p.m.
and will repeat with a new poll every hour.
If you try and leave this place
before sunrise you will also die.
(scratching noise)
What the heck?
The second coming.
Hey, this doesn't make any sense.
I don't have reception.
What does that even mean,
"a poll posted"? Who's posting?
We don't have WiFi,
we don't have reception,
we couldn't post anything anyway.
What if they hacked our phones
and they're posting for us?
This must be some kind of a stupid joke.
This doesn't freak you out?
Of course it does.
You don't look freaked out.
Botox.
Anyway, why a poll?
How did they do that writing?
Projection Mapping.
Where is the projector, bird brain?
Guys, we need weapons, just in case.
How long do we have?
24 minutes to 10 p.m.
Hey, what we need to do is find somewhere
with reception, and call for help.
Who wants to go?
I think you should go, you're the bravest.
No, no, no, guys, just because I'm a
man, doesn't mean I'm brave.
Women are braver, women are smarter.
I think a couple of women should go.
Come on, be a gentleman.
It's not about being a gentleman,
I think you're smarter.
Look, why don't you go?
I go.
I'll come with you. Pussy.
No way you girls are going alone,
I'll come with you.
Thanks hun.
Okay, I'll go.
There was some stuff in this
one room I was in earlier.
I'll have a look at that.
Yeah, I'll come with you.
Okay.
And what do we do?
I don't wanna stay here by myself.
Can you two wait here for
Sebastian and Kaya?
But how long?
We'll all be back before 10, don't worry.
(♫ anticipating music ♫)
5 minutes.
Okay guys.
Be safe, yeah?
We will, yeah.
(♫ mysterious music ♫)
What the hell happened here?
How did it get so overgrown?
Still no reception, nothing.
I have a bad feeling about this.
What if nobody comes back,
what are we gonna do?
(♫ tense music building ♫)
And if this whole posting
thing is really true,
then we all have to die anyway.
Chloe, calm down.
Let's go this way to the roof,
we'll get better reception.
No, no, no, no, definitely garden,
open field.
No, this way.
Rock, paper, scissors,
winner gets to choose.
Okay, okay.
One, two, three, shoot.
Okay.
Let's go.
1, 2, 3, shoot.
Corona-elbow, paper has virus.
Paper dies.
Let's go Grace.
What the fuck was that?
Hey.
Slowly, slowly.
Waaa.
Idiot.
Sit down.
You have to trust the universe.
Everything happens for a reason.
As long as we trust we'll be fine.
Trust your heart.
(♫ soft music building ♫)
Can you feel it?
Whatever happens, just flow.
Just flow with it.
Just flow.
(♫ soft music continues ♫)
What?
What the fuck are you doing
you creep, what the hell?
We were just connecting.
Connecting to my tits maybe.
Hey, up here!
(cell phone notifcation)
Fuck! How the...
Has anyone got reception?
Nope, nothing.
(cell phone notification)
(♫ tense music driving ♫)
(cell phone writing out)
(♫ tense music continues ♫)
(photo camera clicking)
Let's go.
Enjoy my content...
Why would someone follow me,
and not enjoy my content?
You'd be surprised.
Fuck this poll, they wanna drive us crazy.
But why?
Someone wants to mess
with our heads, that's why.
By the way, I didn't mean to...
Are you gonna tell the others?
Of course I'm going to tell
the others you pervert.
What's there?
(♫ tense music ♫)
Look.
(chalk writing noise)
What the hell?
How?
Fuck it.
Let's keep going.
Look at the moon, look at the trees.
My goodness, mother earth is so beautiful.
Amen.
You don't have anything better to do?
For later, I don't have that
many great moonlight selfies.
Rick, I didn't know
you were the selfie police?
Let's just look for reception.
Yeah, exactly.
(♫ mysterious music ♫)
(creepy noise)
(foot steps)
What's this?
I think we should go back.
(♫ mysterious music continues ♫)
What does it say?
My God, no way.
What's going on?
Can anyone see the results
from their polls?
No. No.
Let's just try again.
Anyone?
No, nothing.
Me neither.
Fuck! Then how come our stories got posted?
It's quarter past soon.
(distant ghost whisper)
What was that?
(♫ tense music ♫)
It's 15 past.
Shut up you creep.
But the poll!
I'm going to tell everyone,
that you're a fucking rapist.
And I will also show a picture of you
in the influencer community group.
(ghost whisper)
(camera clicking)
What the...
Oh my God.
What was that?
Hey, wait.
(foot steps)
What does it say?
One sec!
(♫ soft music ♫)
First influencer suicide.
This guy came here to find
out about these ghosts.
Apparently his daughter
is one of the ghosts,
and she appeared in his dreams,
and told him to come here to release her.
(♫ tense music building ♫)
His daughter was the first influencer
ever announcing her suicide online,
and she killed herself here.
How can you release a ghost?
Her father found out that
all these ghosts here
are ghosts of influencers
who committed suicide and
they can only move on to
heaven or hell or wherever
if they kill someone.
(heavy breathing)
(♫ tense music ♫)
(scream)
(♫ soft music restarts ♫)
My goodness, if this is true.
It's already half past.
You see, it's way more than 15 minutes.
I told you it's just a prank.
We don't know what happened to the others.
Fucking Sebastian, I will kill that guy.
Everything happens for a reason.
God brought us here, maybe for
some other reason than we thought.
And you can say whatever
you want about Sebastian,
but he helped me more in two hours
than any therapy in the last two years.
Guys, isn't anyone concerned
about the next poll?
It's fake bullshit,
we don't even have reception.
What if someone else is dead,
and one of us is next?
Maybe, we don't know, and Isla I don't
really care how much he helped you,
I'm going to fucking kill that guy.
The hate in your eyes makes
you blind and ugly.
Grace, I fucking love you okay,
but now is not the right time to
give me a fucking lecture about eyes.
You are what?
Christian? Prostitute? Feminist?
You do you and I'm not judging,
but maybe you should
turn it down a little while
you're running around all day
half naked taking selfies.
You think because I'm not
afraid to show my body,
I'm cheap and a bad role model?
I come from Vladivostock.
You know what girls from my
city see when they look at me?
They see a self made girl boss,
who had no help,
and they celebrate that,
and not my tits and my ass.
Whatever.
Don't worry honey, he did not mean it...
He's just on edge.
He's not just on edge.
He's just an asshole.
(footsteps)
Hello?!?
(door sound)
Anyone?
(♫ tense music rising ♫)
(surprising sound)
Huu.
Jesus, you scared me.
It's just me.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay, nothing is okay,
we'll all die here.
Hey, hey, relax.
I'm here.
I won't let anything happen to you.
You won't believe what I saw,
I need to show you something.
I really like you.
But I thought...
(cell phone notification)
(♫ tense music building ♫)
(cell phone vibrating and notifications)
(cell phone typing sounds)
What?
Well...
At least for this one we're safe.
Not sure, lot of haters out there.
(♫ suspensful music ♫)
(cameras clicking)
(♫ tense music ♫)
(camera clicking)
"Would you fuck me?",
that is so disgusting.
Isn't that how you girls
take your selfies anyway?
With that question in mind.
No, we just wanna look good for ourselves.
That's why you have to share it
with thousands of other people,
to look good for yourselves.
Okay guys, let's just go up to the others.
You go ahead, we'll join you
in a few minutes.
No, let us please stick together.
We will all go to hell tonight.
(laughter)
I'm just kidding, go ahead.
We'll join you in a few minutes.
(intense breathing)
(♫ tense music ♫)
Hey guys.
Hey. Hey.
Are you okay?
Where is everyone?
I don't know, they left.
Did you see Chloe?
No, why?
It's just, she also went that way.
You're acting a bit weird Gaia.
I am not acting weird.
Yeah, you're acting weird.
What are you talking
about? I'm not acting weird.
Did you put a stiffy on the chicky?
I don't speak Belgian-Bogan.
Guys, at exactly 15 past
something approached me
and Chloe took a picture and the flash
made it disappear.
Yes, yes, how did you know that?
You're not gonna believe this,
we found this book and...
I can't see the Rigel.
It's Rick, and I'm lying right next to you.
I mean the star you clown,
I have never seen it missing.
I'm sure it will come back again soon.
What star sign are you?
Unicorn.
That doesn't exist, you egg.
None of them exist.
You know, you really
are a beautiful person.
Thank you.
(♫ soft music ♫)
Women my age are usually not seen anymore.
I think this poll could be my end.
Women of any age who think they're
not seen, aren't seen anymore.
And babe, if anyone's dying
from this pole, it's gonna be me.
(♫ soft music continues ♫)
Let's just be here in the moment.
Plenty of time for that later.
(moaning)
(♫ tense music building ♫)
(heavy breathing)
(chalk scratching)
(♫ tense music with drums ♫)
(swoshing sound)
(♫ forceful driving music ♫)
(ghost whisper)
Hugh.
(♫ tense music ♫)
(heavy breathing)
There is no escape.
I'm gonna make it.
(cell phone notification)
(ghost wispers)
(scream)
I feel like recording a video for my kids.
Is that weird?
No, not at all, go for it.
Send it to them in the morning.
Okay.
Hey guys,
I know I haven't been in
contact much lately,
but I just wanted...
(deep breath)
You know all the things I
have been going through
had nothing to do with you.
And I guess that's what
I wanted you to know.
I love you both so much.
Perfect, perfect, perfect.
I just really love you guys
right in this moment.
(slashing sound)
The question is, why do cell phone
screens attract them then.
Maybe they can't help themselves,
just like the rest of us.
What kind of asshole influencers
kill themselves anyway?
You have such a dark energy man.
Maybe you should do a cleanse?
Hanzi-Bread, you'r behaving as if
you got baptized by a pedophile,
so don't lecture me, alright?
Shut up.
Why here in this place,
in the middle of nowhere?
This is the place where the first
influencer ever committed suicide.
Her father came here and
found out a bunch of things.
Anyways, he didn't survive,
but we need to survive, okay?
So firstly, how much battery does
everyone have on their phones?
I got half.
He's dead.
Fully dead? Mine is only halfway.
What? Rick! Rick's dead.
What? What?
We were lying in the garden
and they came from...
It all happened so fast.
I'm so sorry.
We found a way how to kill them.
We just need to stick together,
and we can survive the night, okay?
Apparently this is the building
where all ghosts of influencers
who committed suicide end up,
and in the journal the guy wrote
they're only active from sunset to sunrise.
So we just need to survive three
more hours and we'll be okay.
What journal?
It doesn't matter, important is
cellphone flashes kill them.
So, how many are we? Us four, then...
Where's Chloe and Louis and Grace?
We need to tell the others how to survive.
Yes.
They know where to find
us, anyway, they'll be fine.
We can't just let one of us die every hour.
Who's gonna go and find the others?
Come on.
Hey, you could go because if you die
you will be reborn in a better person.
No, thanks.
Isla, you? Got a lot of
mileage already anyway!
Mileage?
From being the village bicycle.
What?
Nothing, I can go. No worries.
(♫ tense music building ♫)
(moaning)
(weird noise)
What was that? Hello.
Huh, huh, huh.
(phone camera click)
(♫ intense music ♫)
Put the cell phone away.
Fuck off you pervert.
Come on guys, there are ghosts.
I'm just trying to
What the hell is wrong with you?
Just put... Come on,
put the cell phone away,
the screen attracts ghosts and...
Get the fuck out right now.
Mia
Why did you do the seminar?
Same reason as all of you,
I wanted to increase my following.
I think there's something else.
Yeah, I can feel it too.
It's true that I'm a writer.
(♫ soft mysterious music ♫)
And?
But I'm also a journalist.
I'm writing an investigative
article on Sebastian.
He's also known as
Marcelo Pervesi Enrico Garcia.
In two other countries, he's wanted for
fraud, sexual assault and misdemeanor.
I wanted to write about the
fraud of influencer coaches.
But why him?
My brother Jim attended
Sebastian's workshop last year.
And afterwards he tried to
start a social media business.
He took out a 20,000 dollar loan.
It failed.
He was blind and stupid.
And then, what happened then?
Jim emailed Sebastian what happened.
Jim didn't want any money,
he just wanted Sebastian to know.
But Sebastian wrote back
what a loser Jim is,
and that he should go and kill himself.
Oh, no way.
Jim didn't kill himself, but he tried.
Oh God, I'm so sorry honey.
Do you want a hug?
It's okay.
(♫ tense music continuous ♫)
I saw you with this
hooded guy at the party.
What did you do with him?
I tried to ask him a few questions,
but he was really evasive.
I cannot believe Sebastian
is getting us all killed.
Who would have thought, it's not a virus,
it's this whole digital bullshit world
we're all trapped in,
that's what's going to kill us.
(♫ tense music ♫)
(cell phone notifications)
Oh my god.
Did you also get it?
I think you'll be fine for this one,
and you...
Let's just do it.
(♫ tense music continuous ♫)
Well it was nice to get to know you Chloe.
Fuck off.
You wanna know how
you can kill the ghosts?
Taking a picture of them.
No, it's...
Yeah, flashlights, how did you know?
I already killed one.
Oh, nice one, but the cell phone screens
also at track them,
so only use them when you really have to
Alright, know-it-all, it's time for
you to get the fuck out.
No problem.
Go.
Hey, nice ass Chloe.
Fuck off.
What an idiot.
Actually, I think this just might
be a stupid prank.
No, I saw it with my own eyes, look.
(weird noises)
What was that?
I am smart, I went to college,
I finished high school.
Wow, congratulations to you.
I'm just saying.
(♫ tense music building ♫)
I'm just not the smartest.
I'm gonna die.
Nobody's gonna die,
if we just stick together.
I have 15 minutes to live.
(strange noise)
(footsteps)
Do you think Chloe is still alive?
You know, it's a poll for your
followers opinion, not an IQ test.
What was that?
I think it's over there.
(strange noises)
Turn your light on.
No, that's what attracts them.
(ghost whispers)
How about we live-stream your death?
Take a picture.
(camera flash sound)
(dissolving sound)
Fuck, this is real!
Told you!
(chalk scratching on wall)
Chloe, what is that?
(heavy breathing)
What? 2002...
Um, um.
2,848.2,848!
Sorry honey, not sorry at all!
But you're not as smart as you think.
(slashing sound)
(scream)
You're dead.
(♫ tense music ♫)
Oh my God.
It's coming.
What's that?
Hello.
Who are you?
Get ready.
(heavy breathing)
Oh my God, it's you.
What was that? What happened?
Louis got killed.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay, how could anyone be okay?
Oh honey. So sorry.
We're gonna die.
We're gonna die here tonight.
(cell phone notifications)
No, no, no, no.
(cell phone typing sounds)
Should I kill myself?
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Just do it.
(♫ tense music ♫)
(phone camera clicks)
What?
The posts don't matter,
they want us all dead.
But what should we do?
What should we do?
(scream)
What's wrong with you?
I heard a noise up there.
And that's why you decided to
creep up on us like that?
Did you do the poll?
Yes, I did. Anyway, I'm sorry.
Are you guys okay?
That's it, I'm going to die.
What? Why, but why?
Let's just stick together,
we can protect each other.
No, no, no, it doesn't matter.
We'll protect each other, she's right.
No, no, no.
No, I'd like to go out on my own terms.
It could be anybody of us.
Trust me, I have so many haters that...
Listen.
I can beat them my way.
I'll reach higher consciousness
through meditation and,
and they will leave me alone.
Good for you.
What? But how?
(♫ soft music ♫)
Anyway, I found some sticks and knives
over there, I'll grab them.
Sticks? Whatever, it might help.
(♫ mysterious music ♫)
No one will even notice you're gone.
No one cares about your engagement rates.
Everyone knows your holistic
attitude is a sham.
Any second now.
Keep to your side.
(♫ tense music intensifies ♫)
(soft ghost whispers)
You'll be worth more once you'r dead.
(♫ tense music continuous ♫)
(laughter)
(slashing sound)
Guys?
You think we're the only ones left?
Yes, seems pretty likely now.
Hey, what if none of us
take a selfie next time?
Then all of us get killed.
You mean we all ignore the game?
Yes maybe nothing will happen
if we all switch it off?
What if they come for all of us?
Then we all try and fight our way out.
I don't know.
They'll try and kill us either way.
Okay, okay, I'm in.
Let's switch them off, yeah, let's do it.
(cell phone shutdown)
(♫ tense music ♫)
(soft ghost whispers)
(phone notifications)
What? It switched on.
How is it possible?
Fuck.
(phone typing sound)
What?
Guys, should we do it?
Don't, don't do it.
Okay, Okay.
Okay.
Ignore it, just ignore it.
(♫ tense music ♫)
(cell phone notifications)
(cell phone writing)
(gasp)
Oh my God, no.
Have you seen it?
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's fine, just ignore it.
If we don't react to it,
nothing will happen.
(♫ tense music ♫)
Girls,
you're all beautiful by the way.
Oh, thank you.
Really? Now?
Look.
Guys, what the fuck.
(chalk scratching)
Get ready, we have to run.
Oh my God, oh my God.
Guys, get your cellphones ready.
(ghost whispers)
(screams)
(♫ fast paced music ♫)
You are not as funny as you think.
(slashing sound)
(ghost whispers)
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
(heavy breathing)
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
(continuous ghost whispers)
(panicky breathing)
Like. Like. Like.
Please don't kill me.
Please don't kill me, please don't kill me.
No, please.
(scream)
No, no, no, no.
(camera flash sound)
Run, run.
(♫ mysterious music ♫)
(jungle sounds)
Switch it off.
(♫ tense music ♫)
(foot steps)
(stabbing sound)
Oh shit, damn, sorry.
What the? What the fuck?
I thought you were one of the ghosts.
My bad, my bad.
Do I look like a fucking ghost to you?
Fuck...
I don't think I hit an organ though.
What happened to you?
Where's Venefica?
She ran away just after I left.
She just wanted to save herself.
I found a path that gets us out of here,
and I was just on my way back
to get you guys.
Really?
Yes, yes, of course.
Koen, get the fucking knife out of me.
I don't believe a word you're saying.
Why would I lie? What the fuck,
get the fucking knife out of here.
Where are the others?
They're all dead!
What?
Fuck.
Fuck, we need to find a way out.
We need to find a way out immediately.
Help me with the fucking knife.
I thought you found one already.
Yeah... Well... I...
Guys, look.
What does that mean?
We're saved.
There are no ghosts after sunrise.
(♫ soft music ♫)
Fuck, yes.
(relieved exhales)
(laughter)
Fuck, yes, we won.
You know, you're still in trouble, right?
Shut your fucking mouth you stupid bitch.
You're always fucking nagging,
nag-nag-nag.
I know everything better, oh my god,
I'm so smart, I'm the smarty one.
Fuck, you're such a fucking stupid bitch.
What the... Write me a fucking email if
you've got a problem. Why don't you just
(stabbing sound)
What?
Please...
What? Please.
(♫ dark music ♫)
Please.
Oh no.
How? What?
What was that? I just...
I tripped.
I think he's dead.
(gasping)
(jungle noise)
(♫ uplifting music building ♫)
(foot steps)
Grace.
Mia.
(♫ soft music ♫)
(foot steps)
What happened?
I panicked and then ran away.
I get this text, and it said I would die,
but I became nature. I think it worked.
But...
And how...
Hey,
what is this?
Is this blood?
Yeah, I...
We ran into Sebastian.
There was an accident.
You know that nothing can happen
to us anymore after sunrise, right?
Really?
Yes.
(sigh)
(♫ soft string music ♫)
Are you,
you know...?
(cell phone notification)
It works again.
Well, I guess we should get going.
One million.
A million what?
One million followers.
I have one million followers.
No way, what?
Look.
Check mine, Mia_journalist.
(gasp)
What?
Oh my God.
No way, I also have a million.
What?
Do you know what that means?
Do you know how much you get
for one post? Thousands.
We're so rich.
My goodness, this doesn't seem real.
It is real, you better believe it.
(♫ music darkens ♫)
Hey, did someone else survive,
or is it just us?
It's just us.
Come, let's try and find a way out of here.
(intense sound)
(♫ mysterious music ♫)