[girl] & There's a place I long to be ♪
♪ A certain town that's dear to me ♪
♪ Home to Mohawks and GE I
♪ It's called Schenectady ♪
♪ I was born there and I'll die there ♪
♪ My first home I hope to buy there ♪
♪ Have a kid or at least try there ♪
♪ Sweet Schenectady
♪ And when I'm buried ♪
♪ And I'm dead ♪
♪ Upstate worms will eat my head ♪
[man on radio] --7:45 on this beautiful,
almost balmy 22nd of September
in Schenectady.
And it's the first day of fall.
So in honor of that fact,
we have Elke Putzkammer,
professor of literature at Union College,
to talk about autumn in poetry
and literature.
- Good morning, professor.
- [woman] Hi, Alex.
[man] So, what about it? Why do
So many people write about the fall?
[woman] Well, I think it's seen
as the beginning of the end, really.
If the year is a life, then September,
the beginning of fall,
is when the bloom is off the rose
and things start to die.
It's a melancholy month and maybe
because of that, quite beautiful.
[man] Is there something
you might read to us?
[woman] Oh, I'd love to.
Whoever has no house now
Will never have one.
Whoever is alone will stay alone
Will sit, read, write long letters
Through the evening
And wander the boulevards
Up and down, restlessly
While the dry leaves are blowing.
[man] Goodness, that harsh, isn't it?
[woman] Well, perhaps. But truthful.
[coughing]
[girl] Mommy, done!
Okay.
- Good morning.
- [Adele] Good morning.
- I tried not to wake you.
- Well, thanks.
You didn't. I just--
You know, I couldn't get up.
[phone ringing]
- Caden, can you get that?
- [Caden] It's Maria, I don't want to.
[sighs] Caden-- Oh, that's weird.
[woman on machine]
Hey, it's me. How are you?
Mommy, is something wrong with my poop?
Uh... No, honey, it's just green.
You probably ate something green.
I didn't. What's wrong with me?
[cell phone ringing]
I have to get that, Olive.
You're gonna be fine, okay?
- But, Mommy--
- Yeah, I'll be right back, Olive.
Oh, nothing. Just wiping Olive's ass. You?
[man on radio] An earthquake in Kashmir...
Oh, you're kidding. Holy fuck.
- ...has killed an estimated 73,000...
- I don't feel well.
Oh, my goodness.
[mellow music playing]
[man on radio] --march
in Washington, D.C., today, October 15th.
- [Caden] Harold Pinter died.
- [Adele] Wow. Well, he's old, right?
- No, wait. He won the Nobel Prize.
- [Olive] Mom.
What, honey?
[Olive] Do you need to come
and look at my poop again?
- You sure it's all right?
- It's fine, Olive. Just-- Just flush.
[Olive] What if it's alive?
What if I kill it?
- It's green like plants.
- It's not alive, honey.
- [Olive] Everything's alive.
- Remember the production
of The Dumb Waiter I did at Albanyfest?
[toilet flushes]
Have your oatmeal, honey.
- I want peanut butter and jelly.
- It's oatmeal.
- This isn't a restaurant.
- [Olive] I don't want oatmeal.
- [Adele] Okay. Fine.
- [Olive] Mommy, I'm sorry.
They found avian flu in Turkey.
In the country Turkey, not turkeys.
- Can I watch TV till school?
- In some chickens. Yeah.
[music playing on TV]
[bleating]
[man] There is a secret something
at play under the surface,
growing like an invisible virus
of thought.
But you're being changed by it...
- [Caden] Milk's expired.
- [Adele] Okay.
[Caden] Jesus.
- [Adele] You better eat this.
- I will.
Yeah.
[woman] How did I guess
you'd ask me that question?
[man] Happy Halloween, Schenectady.
[woman] And how long have you been
in New York for?
[Caden] The first Black graduate
of the University of Alabama died.
Vivian Malone Jones.
Stroke, 63.
[eerie music playing]
ow!
Fuck! [yells]
God! Somebody! Adele, help!
- Jesus, Caden, what the fuck?
- I was shaving and the thing flew off!
Oh, my God! Jesus, look at your head.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God, I can't turn it.
Oh, wait.
- Mommy, Daddy has blood.
- [Adele] Yeah.
- [Caden] Will there be a scar?
- Probably. It looks like a mud flap.
- I prefer there not to be a scar.
- Yeah.
- [woman] You'll be fine.
- [man groans]
That fellow is annoying.
He's in here every week, like clockwork.
There. I think that should, uh--
Let's see.
- What?
- Change in bowel movements?
It's a little more yellow than usual. Why?
Yeah, I'd like you
to see an ophthalmologist.
- A neurologist?
- What? No.
An ophthalmologist.
I said, ophthalmologist.
Do you hear that?
Yeah.
And today is Tuesday.
Mommy, is today Tuesday?
No, honey, today is Friday.
So, what exactly did he say?
[man chattering on radio]
That my pupils weren't properly,
uh, opening and closing.
Dilating.
- No.
- Yeah.
- I don't think that's what he said.
- Yes.
- That's not what he said.
- Is it the bump to your head?
He doesn't know. Maybe.
He said he doesn't think so, but maybe.
But he doesn't know.
- But maybe. Who knows?
- Okay, Jesus, Caden, I got it.
- He doesn't know--
- Sorry. I'm a little anxious.
- Did you have to get a shot, Daddy?
- No, honey.
- It's the start of something awful.
- [Olive] Do I have to get a shot?
- [Caden] Course not.
- Did you tell him I have green poo?
- [Caden] It's just fucked timing.
- I'm gonna call the plumber. Hey.
Sorry. I have rehearsal. Fuck.
- Hey, come on.
- Sorry, sorry, sorry. Everybody, sorry.
How many years
until I have to get more shots?
- Not for a really long time, babe.
- A million years?
[Adele] Mmm.
Remember what Dr. Woodman said...
- What's a plumber?
- ...at your last vaccination?
- Um, he's a man who--
- Or a woman, Dad.
Right. He's a man or a woman
who fixes sinks and toilets and, um...
- Do you know what pipes are?
- [Olive] No.
- [Caden] Hey, Jim. I had an accident.
- Like to smoke out of?
[Caden] A different kind of pipe, honey.
All right, bye.
Houses have pipes,
and they're made of, um...
They're like tubes,
and they're behind the walls,
and they're under the floors
and everywhere.
- And--
- [Adele] What's the matter, baby?
- Every single where?
- [Caden] It's okay, honey.
They just carry water
to and from sinks and toilets.
- It's like in your body. You have veins.
- Capillaries.
Capillaries filled with blood.
I have blood? I don't want blood!
I don't want blood.
- Jesus, what are you doing?
- Just trying to explain plumbing.
- Well, stop.
- God, I can't do this now.
You don't have to worry, honey.
You don't have blood.
I don't think you should tell her that.
- Caden, stop it.
- I don't want blood. I don't want blood.
Thanks for getting me in right away.
- Was it the bump to the head?
- No.
Could be, but I think we need
to get you to a neurologist.
- Neurologist?
- It's a brain expert.
I know what a neurologist is.
- I thought from the way you asked--
- I just thought you said "urologist."
- Why do I need to see a neurologist?
- Just for a look-see.
The eyes are part of the brain, after all.
No, that's not true, is it?
- Why would I say it if it weren't true?
- It doesn't seem right.
Like morally correct,
or "right" as in accurate?
I don't know. Accurate, I guess.
Interesting.
[man 1] Now, when you kick off, boy,
I want a 70-yard boot.
And get right down the field
under the ball.
And when you hit, hit low and hit hard
because it's important, boy.
There's all kinds of important people
in the stands.
And the first thing you know-- Ben?
Ben, where do I...?
- Ben, how do I...?
- Willy, you coming up?
Shh!
[Claire] Willy?
Willy, answer me.
[engine starts]
Willy! No!
[Claire grunts]
- [man 2] Oh, Jesus, come on.
- Oh, crap.
[Caden] Claire, are you okay?
What's happening here?
It's too late in the game
to have these problems!
[David] I know, Caden.
I'm sorry. We'll get it.
Oh, my God.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I think the wig saved my life.
- Yeah.
- It's okay, honestly.
[Caden] That was good, Tom.
- [Tom] Yeah?
- Yeah.
I was trying something different.
I was crashing differently.
- Ambivalently.
- Yeah, I saw that. I liked it.
Um...
Try to keep in mind
that a young person playing Willy Loman
thinks he's only pretending to be
at the end of a life full of despair.
But the tragedy is that we know
that you, the young actor,
will end up
in this very place of desolation.
Okay.
Uh... That's great.
- Let's try it again. How long, David?
- [David] I think 15.
- Anything?
- Uh... [groans]
So now what?
- Hey.
- In search of an elusive signal.
- The signal's good here, oddly.
- That is odd.
- I know. Cell phones, they're crazy.
- See you in a few.
- Yep.
[Caden chuckles]
Yeah, Dr. Heshborg said
I should see a Dr. Scoriano.
My pupils don't work.
I think I have blood in my stool.
That stool in your office?
[Adele] When I was pregnant with Olive.
What was it like?
I don't know. Hopeful or something.
Like something was gonna change.
- Yeah, something did. No?
- [Caden] Yeah.
- Yeah, of course.
- I mean, bigtime.
I mean, maybe not as much as I'd hoped.
I'm sorry. That's a terrible thing to say.
There are no terrible things
to say in here, only true and false.
- Can I say something awful?
- Yes, please do.
I've fantasized about Caden dying.
Being able to start again, guilt-free.
I know that's-- That's bad.
- Caden, does that feel terrible?
- Yeah.
Okay, good.
It's a nightmare in there.
I'm sorry.
So I'm reading The Trial.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- You like?
- Love.
I'm such an idiot
for not knowing about this book.
- It's famous, as it turns out.
- Yeah.
You're not an idiot.
Then you say:
"In fact, Hazel, you're very bright,
and I love your eyes."
- In fact, Hazel, you're very bright.
- Oh, am I?
- And I love your eyes.
- Do you? Oh, you're a darling.
Then what do I say?
- I can't say what then you say.
- Why?
'Cause it's dirty.
[stammers] Could you step out
for a second?
Go ahead. I've seen boy parts.
- Can I take a piss in your sink?
- Yeah, sure. I guess.
We're sold out.
Great.
[Caden clears throat]
[Caden] Gorgeous.
Thanks.
- How was rehearsal?
- Awful.
We have, uh, 560 lighting cues.
- I don't why I make it so complicated.
- That's what you do.
Yeah.
We got through it though.
That's really pretty.
Caden, I'm sorry, I--
I just-- I can't come tonight. I'm sorry.
I have two canvasses I have
to get ready to ship for tomorrow.
- I know it sucks--
- It's opening night.
I know. I wish I could come.
I would if I could.
- [Caden] I've gotta get ready.
- Tomorrow--
I have to get ready.
I don't know what I'm gonna wear.
I have to figure out what I'm gonna wear.
[indistinct chatter]
[mouths] Hey.
[jazz music playing over speakers]
- Oh, boy, oh boy.
- [Claire] Willy?
It's all right, I came back.
[Claire groans]
I hated myself tonight.
- Plus, I'm so-- Excuse me.
- Hey, Tom.
I'm so bloated and enormous.
No, you look good.
You were great. I was very pleased.
- [Claire] You okay?
- Sorry. A little bit of a headache.
[man] Willy Loman.
Aw.
[Claire] I just wanted to say
thank you for everything.
You've been absolutely brilliant.
It's gonna be miserable
going ahead without you.
- I'll be around. I'll check in.
- I'm such a baby.
Okay. I'm gonna go get drunk, that's what.
Okay. Claire. Mmm. Sweetheart.
Aw.
- Good. Good job.
- Oh, don't worry, I'll get better.
- Good work. Mmm.
- Don't worry, it'll get better.
Hey. I figured I'd better get in fast.
- Hey, you wanna sit?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Where's, uh, el wife-0?
- Had to work.
Uh, her show in Berlin is in two weeks.
We're gonna go there for, like, a month.
- Why do I like you so much?
- l couldn't begin to guess.
Me neither.
Do you get high, my friend?
You know, sometimes.
Do you want to now? With me, in my car?
I get kind of, uh,
something when I'm stoned.
What does "something" mean?
You know...
bothered.
- What does "bothered" mean?
- You know.
Bothered. Horny.
Oh. Ahem.
And me with a station wagon and all.
Could be dangerous.
- Yeah, could be.
- You're absolutely zero fun.
When are the reviews gonna get here?
Don't know.
[woman] His best friends finger
two babies--
One this big, one this big.
- -and two kittens.
- Hey.
- Hi, Caden. How'd it go?
- [Caden] Hi.
- Hi.
It's late.
Maria came over
to keep me company 'cause, um...
And we just lost track.
I got everything done.
But I'm sorry I missed your play.
I'm sorry. But how'd it go?
Great. We're a hit.
Reviews are great.
Times said it was brilliant casting
young people as Willy and Linda.
- That's great, Caden. Good for you.
- Great!
I can't wait to see it tomorrow.
That's-- Tonight.
That's great.
[Maria] Wow, it's really late-- Early.
Early! [laughs]
It's late.
Hey, I would love to see it too.
- [Adele] Can we get Maria a ticket?
- You're stoned.
I mean, a little. It's, you know--
I don't know.
But are you happy with it?
Yeah. Yeah, I'd love for you to see--
To know what you think.
It doesn't matter what I think.
Absolutely. It's all about
your artistic satisfaction, Caden.
[Caden] Yeah. Whatever.
- Congratulations.
- [Caden] Yeah.
[mellow music playing]
[buzzes]
- [Hazel] I've always loved this house.
- [woman] Yes, it's a wonderful place.
The truth is, I never really
imagined I could afford it.
Well, the sellers are very motivated now.
[coughing]
It's a scary decision.
I never thought I'd buy a house alone.
But, you know, I'm 36,
and I wonder what it is I'm waiting for.
- Home buying is always scary.
- And with the fire and all especially.
It's a good size though, 2200 square feet,
not including
the partially finished basement.
[Hazel] Oh, I don't know.
I'm thinking I should go.
It's a perfect size for someone alone.
I like it, 1 do. I'm just really concerned
about dying in the fire.
[board thuds]
It's a big decision,
how one prefers to die.
Would you like to meet my son? Derek!
Derek's living in the basement
since his divorce, if that's okay.
Hey, Mom.
- [Davis] Let's go, Ma.
- [Claire] I want just a minute.
[jazz music playing over speakers]
I never...
Forgive me, dear. I can't cry.
Don't know what it is, but I can't cry.
[Claire sobbing]
It seems to me
that you're just on another trip.
I keep expecting you.
Why did you do it?
I search and I search,
and I can't understand it.
I made the last payment
on the house today.
We're free and clear.
We're free. We're free.
- [man] Well done.
- [woman] Bravo.
- Well done. It was very successful.
- I thought it was wonderful.
Why did the older people look so young?
It was a choice, Dad. I'll explain later.
- How is it a choice?
- [Adele] I can't get excited about...
your restaging
someone else's old play, it just--
There's nothing personal in it.
[Caden] People are coming out
of the theater crying.
Great. Be a fucking tool
of suburban, blue-haired,
regional-theater subscribers.
- You didn't think it was long?
- No, I did not.
But what are you leaving behind?
You act as if you have forever
to figure it out.
[man] When you're dead,
there's no time. The world is...
[Adele] I don't know.
I slept maybe three hours.
So we're both tired.
No, I cuddled with Olive all night.
It was great.
Morning. Morning.
- Morning, Caden.
- I think I might have arthritis.
Friends on fire.
I'm going to.
[music playing on TV]
No, I know exactly.
Okay, I will. I'll call you later.
I know. You're right. Bye.
My joints are stiff.
Who was that?
- Maria.
- Right.
Three hours since you spoke.
Caden, I think I wanna go
to Berlin with just Olive.
- I think it would be good for us.
- Oh, Christ.
Morning, kiddos.
Why don't you want me to go?
You know, I just think
it would be a good thing
for the two of us to do alone.
How do you think I'm supposed
to respond to something like that?
- Want me to zip your coat up?
- Yeah.
What's wrong with your face, Daddy?
Uh...
It's pustules.
It's called sycosis.
Spelled differently than "psychosis,"
but it sounds the same.
I don't know what that means.
Of course not. Uh...
Well, there are two kinds of psychosis.
Ahem. They're spelled differently.
P-S-Y is like if you're crazy, like Mama.
S-Y is like these ugly things on my face.
- You could have both though.
- I could, but I don't.
Can I ask you something, Ad?
Have I disappointed you somehow?
I don't know what I'm doing.
We're just spending a little time apart.
We'll talk when I get back, okay?
Everyone is disappointing.
The more you know someone, it just...
This whole romantic-love thing,
it's just a projection anyway, right?
I mean, I don't know.
I'm-- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[dramatic music playing]
I love you.
I don't know what I'm doing. I don't know.
We'll talk when I get back.
Okay?
[music playing on TV]
[man on TV]
Flurostatin TR allows you to live life
when it's your turn to face
the challenges of chemotherapy.
Ask your doctor
if Flurostatin TR is right for you.
[ominous music playing]
[spits]
[woman 1 on TV] --and I'm
on the first train out of Palookaville.
[man 1] --the Miracle Brush, you can
scour everything from bottles--
- [man 2] Rise and shine--
- [woman 2] Lift those legs--
[woman 3]
♪ There's no real way of coping ♪
♪ When your parachute won't open ♪
♪ You're falling down ♪
♪ You're going down ♪
Jd You fell ♪
♪ Then you died ♪
♪ Maybe someone cried ♪
♪ But not your onetime bride ♪
- I'm lonely.
- Yes. Anything else?
- I'm hurt.
- Yes. And?
I think Adele's right when she says
I'm not doing anything real--
What would be real?
I'm afraid I'm gonna die.
[whimsical music playing]
They don't know what's wrong with me.
And I wanna do something important
while I'm still here.
That would be the time to do it. Yes.
I have a book
that might help you get better.
- Better?
- It's called Getting Better.
- Who wrote it?
- I did. All of these.
- Wow, I never knew that.
- Yes. Well, wow, indeed.
[Madeline laughs]
[Madeline] In conclusion-- Cats eat rats--
Within his own plumbing--
Me who am as a raw nerve--
Synthetic vaginal juices--
Substantial crease--
That's $45.
Five. Five.
[Muzak playing over speakers]
Five.
Um, some fives. That's not good.
Keep with the flossing.
We'll see you in three months.
Six. Six. Six.
I'm gonna recommend
you see a periodontist.
He'll probably recommend gum surgery.
[drill whirring]
[Muzak playing over speakers]
[line rings]
- [Adele] Hello?
- Hey, I'm so glad I finally got you.
- Hello, who is this?
- It's Caden.
Ellen?
It's Caden. I can't wait to see you
and Olive on the 12th--
No, I have to go.
I'm sorry, there's a party. I'm famous.
- [Adele laughs]
- Have fun--
[grunting]
[buttons beeping]
[woman on phone]
911, state your emergency.
- I'm sick! I'm sick!
- Ma'am?
[monitor beeping]
[woman] Mr. Cotard?
Mr. Cotard?
Mr. Cotard.
You've had a seizure of sorts.
What does that mean?
Seems to be some synaptic degradation,
fungal in origin.
Autonomic functions are going haywire.
You'll lose your ability
to salivate, cry, et cetera.
- It's serious?
- We don't know. But, yes.
We'll get you enrolled
in some biofeedback program.
Maybe you can learn
some sort of manual override.
[tender music playing]
We should get a drink. It'd be fun.
- It'd be weird.
- I like weird. I like you. See?
Anyway, I don't wanna
make you uncomfortable. I...
Okay, so I do wanna
make you uncomfortable.
[woman] ♪ I'm just a little person ♪
♪ One person in a scene ♪
And what do we do with all this?
You wanna come over to my place, Cotard?
I won't let you off the hook this time
by saying, "Never mind."
Adele is only on vacation.
She hasn't called since she left.
It's been a year.
It's been a week.
I'm gonna buy you a calendar.
Okay.
Just for one drink.
Come on. Scraps for my scrapbook.
I can't-- Uh... I really can't drink
very much because of my condition.
Did you put something in it?
If that's what it takes, consider it done.
Poof.
Love potion number 69.
Mmm.
- It's good.
- Does it make you wanna kiss me?
- Kind of.
- Tell me why.
Because I feel a lot of longing.
Mmm. Beg a girl, why don't you?
- Please, Hazel.
- On your knees.
What?
I want you to beg me
on your knees for a kiss.
Just for fun.
[both laugh]
Why am I doing this?
For fun, baby.
Will you help me forget my troubles?
Oh, kiddo.
You don't even know.
- What?
- I don't know. [sniffling]
- What is it?
- I don't know, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- What?
- I'm getting just, um...
I'm just really confused.
I'm sorry.
[, um...
I'm really, uh... I'm really sick.
And I think I'm dying.
[softly] Jeez.
I have a kid, and I'm married.
I just thought this might change things,
you know?
I had a good time,
and I think you're a very nice person.
That is just the wrong thing
to say right now, Caden.
You should go.
[line rings]
[Hazel on recording] Hazel.
Leave a message or not. It's your dime.
[beeps]
[Caden] Hi. You know,
I haven't heard from you in a while,
and I just thought I'd call and say hi.
Hi, Hazel.
[Caden laughs]
[coughing]
[Madeline] Now. Now. Be here now.
[Adele] Olive wanted me
to ask you not to read her diary.
She left it under her pillow by mistake.
[Adele speaks in gibberish]
[knocking on door]
[door opens]
[mellow music playing]
[man] Dear Mr. Cotard,
it is my pleasure to inform you
that you have been named
a 2009 MacArthur Fellow.
It is our hope that you will use
your newly found financial freedom
to create something unflinchingly true,
profoundly beautiful,
and of unremitting value
to your community and to the world.
- So I got this MacArthur grant.
- Oh, Caden.
- Yeah, a lot of money.
- Do you know what
- you're gonna do with it?
- A theater piece.
Something big and true and tough.
I'm gonna finally put my real self
into something.
What is your real self, do you think?
Uh, I don't know yet.
The MacArthur is called "the genius grant"
and I wanna earn it.
That's wonderful. God bless.
I guess you'll have to discover
your real self, right?
Yeah.
I wanted to ask you, how old are kids
when they start to write?
There's an absolutely brilliant novel
written by a 4-year-old.
- Really?
- Little Winky by Horace Azpiazu.
- [Caden] That's cute.
- Oh, hardly.
Little Winky is a virulent anti-Semite.
The story follows his initiation
into the Klan,
his immersion
in the pornographic snuff industry,
and his ultimate degradation
at the hands of a Black ex-convict
named Eric Washington
Jackson Jones Johnson...
- Written by a 4-year-old?
- Jefferson.
Wow. Written by a 4-year-old?
Well, Azpiazu killed himself
when he was 5.
- Why did he kill himself?
- I don't know. Why did you?
What?
I said, why would you?
Oh, I don't know.
Yeah, I wanna bring
my production to New York...
Mm-hm.
...to get it seen by people,
you know, who matter.
- The sooner the better.
- This theater, centrally located.
Heart of the theater district,
so, you know, great for plays.
- Yeah?
- Oh, yeah. Absolutely. There it is.
- What was this used for?
- Plays.
- Like, theater plays?
- Mm-hm. Shakespeare.
King Lear.
The storm.
You see, the idea is to do
a massive theater piece.
You know, uncompromising, honest.
Uh...
Here's what I think theater is.
It's, um... It's the beginning of thought.
It's, uh, the truth not yet spoken.
It's what a man feels like
after he's been clocked in the jaw.
It's love in all its messiness.
You know, and I want all of us,
players and patrons alike,
to soak in the communal bath of it,
the mikvah, as the Jews call it.
Um, 'cause we're all in the same water,
after all.
You know, soaking
in our very menstrual blood
and nocturnal emissions.
This is what I wanna try to give people.
[waitress] Okay, here you go.
Here's your salad.
- Here's your soup.
- Thanks. Ahem.
- Thank you.
- [waitress] Enjoy.
- What are you doing?
- Salivating.
The biofeedback training.
- So I was wondering if you'd help.
- In your box office?
No, as, uh, my assistant.
I'm not sure I can work with you, Caden.
I'm kind of angry.
I just wanna normalize it.
Think we'd have a lot of fun together.
I miss you.
- Really disturbing.
- I know.
[somber music playing]
[Olive] Dear diary, thank you
for being my new best friend.
My name is Olive Cotard,
and I'm 4 years old.
I like chocolate,
and my favorite color is pink.
This is pink.
Yeah, that's good.
- [woman] Next.
- [man] Hi.
[Caden] We'll start by talking honestly,
and out of that,
a piece of theater will evolve.
I'll begin.
I've been thinking a lot
about dying lately.
- You're gonna be fine, sweetie.
- Well, I appreciate that, Claire, but--
You are, you poor thing.
Yeah, well, regardless of how
this particular thing works itself out,
I will be dying.
And so will you.
And so will everyone here. Ahem.
And that's what I wanna explore.
We're all hurtling towards death.
Yet here we are, for the moment, alive,
each of us knowing we're gonna die,
each of us secretly believing we won't.
It's brilliant.
lt-- It's everything.
It's Karamazov.
[woman] J' I'm singing this song ♪
- [Hazel] Stop.
- [Derek] I'm just asking.
- You're so obnoxious.
- [Derek] You're so obnoxious.
- You do not wanna cross me.
- [Derek] Don't 1?
[Hazel laughs]
Hi, Claire.
- Hi.
- Hazel.
Yeah. No, no. I know, I know. Hazel.
You're the box office.
- Yeah, I'm the box office.
- How are you?
Wonderful. You?
Yeah, yeah. I'm good. I'm fine. Thank you.
Actually, I'm meeting Caden here.
You know Mr. Cotard, right?
Yes, I recall Mr. Cotard.
Yeah. I'm waiting--
- Oh.
- [Caden] Oh, oh. Oh.
- Hey. Hey.
- Hi, Caden.
- Hi, Hazel. Hi, Claire.
Hi.
- This is Derek.
- Hi, Derek.
Hi.
Well, we'll leave you be.
It's nice to see you again.
- [Hazel] Take care.
- Why am I bowing? Okay, bye.
- That was awkward.
- Yeah, I guess.
Do you like beaver...?
So could you tell me maybe what it is
that you want from me?
Hm?
You know, like, from my character.
Oh. Uh...
Mmm.
Well, we'll build it over time together.
You know, try to find a real person,
maybe, to model it after.
That Hazel girl's
kind of interesting maybe.
- You know, like, why--?
- Although--
Why is she still, um, working
at a box office at her age?
I don't know.
Probably not that interesting.
Do you think that maybe she wanted to be
an actress, but she lacked the confidence?
Yeah, could be.
- We'll talk about it.
- I'm so excited.
Really? Why?
'Cause I think that it's brave.
And I just feel like I'm gonna be part
of a revolution.
I keep thinking about Artaud,
Krapp's Last Tape,
you know, and Grotowski, for chrissake.
I don't know what I'm doing.
But that's what's so refreshing.
Knowing that you don't know
is the first and the most essential step
to knowing, you know?
I don't know.
- Well, I'm proud of you.
- Thanks.
- [Hazel] Don't say that, not to me.
- [Derek] Oh, sorry.
My mother died last night.
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
What are you doing out?
- This is me.
- Well, um...
Well, it was nice meeting you.
Oh, God, did I just say "meeting"?
- I'm sorry. I'm so stupid.
- Slip of the tongue, is all.
Yeah, it's a Freudian slip, right?
I don't know how it's Freudian.
To meet, you know? Like, to meet.
Oh.
There she met Ralph Keene.
They fell in love, married,
and soon their first child,
Claire, was born.
I used to be a baby.
[priest] Claire Elizabeth Keene was
a joyous child.
- I'm sorry.
- [priest] The apple of her mother's eye.
She made her parents proud
with her politeness and gymnastic skills.
God, you're beautiful.
[priest] When she was 7, little Claire
was bitten by the acting bug.
She starred
in almost every school musical,
playing Ado Annie in Oklahoma,
Adelaide in Guys And Dolls,
and Maria in The Sound Of Music.
I have to fuck you. I have to.
[dramatic music playing]
There will be no other before you.
- I'd like to buy a ticket, please.
- Oh.
- Okay. Hold it. Ahem.
- [Claire] That'll be $40.
We're not really...
We need to investigate.
You know, to really discover
the essence of each being.
Uh...
You know, I think I need to work
with both of you separately.
Davis, I'll start with you.
[softly] I liked the beginning.
I don't wanna see a good scene...
"Davis, I'll start with you"?
There's a difference between favoring me
and pretending like we've never met.
I mean, we've had Ariel.
I think people know that we've fucked.
We'll talk about your character
after we put Ariel to bed, okay?
Okay.
[softly] I think I made a breakthrough.
- This character is so beautiful--
- Yeah, I have to go find my daughter.
- Your daughter's right here.
- My real daughter.
- Excuse me?
- I mean, my first daughter, Olive.
- I have to go find her.
- Please don't do this to us!
She's tattooed. She's tattooed.
Oh, everyone is tattooed.
Oh, I've never seen that before.
[Claire] You have responsibilities.
[Caden] Yeah, I'll be quick.
I'll do it quick.
[Madeline] Redundancy is fluid.
Life moves to the south.
There is only the now,
and I am always with you.
For example, look to your left.
Hi.
When you canceled, it freed me up,
so I'm traveling too. Yippee.
[laughs]
You know, I'm not sure
I'm getting the book.
Oh, but it's getting you.
You're almost non-recognizable now.
Thank you.
[Madeline] / show you my leg.
I stand close,
and you inhale my perfume.
I offer my ripe flower to you
and you deny it.
This book is over.
[woman speaking in German over PA]
[Caden] Hi.
I don't speak German.
Yeah, yeah. I may help you, mister?
I'm looking for Adele Cotard. Adele Lack.
We must not give addresses
or other personal informations.
- I'm her husband.
- No, you are not her husbands,
which is named Gunther und Heinz.
I'm the father of her daughter, Olive.
Oh, I see. I'm sorry, I cannot help you.
[Olive] Dear diary, Germany is wonderful.
So many friends here.
My new dads are great and handsome
and brilliant directors of theater.
[in German accent] Hello.
You're here?
Yeah. I live with Adele and Olive
and Gunther and Heinz
and Uschi and Birritt.
I'm everyone's nanny.
I wanna see my daughter.
Mmm.
- Yeah, they sent me.
- They?
Who are they?
Who the fuck are Uschi and Britt?
Yeah, they decided it's not time
to see you yet.
They decided? Who decided?
They had her tattooed.
Oh, I did that. Olive is my project--
She's a 4-year-old!
She's a fucking 4-year-old!
She-- She's almost over 11 now.
She's my muse.
I love her.
[Caden] You don't love her!
[Maria shouting indistinctly]
Where is she?!
What'd you do to my daughter?!
[sobbing]
[woman speaking in German over PA]
[monitor beeping]
Death comes faster than you think.
Dr. Williams, that was
your last patient for the day.
Jennifer, let's stop the charade.
[actress] I don't know you mean.
- [actor] The chemistry...
- You're actually having an affair off set.
- Palpable, huh?
- Oh, okay.
- Who told you?
- And it's not-- It's not good.
- Not good, oh, okay.
- You're actors playing actors.
You're in this scene, you're not just
filming it. You're in this scene.
[woman] Just like that--
As you're telling him this, you realize
that you're attracted to him also.
And how are you gonna let him know that?
And the guilt you feel about telling him
about somebody else knowing that.
[Ariel] Daddy, Daddy is mine.
Daddy can't play now, honey.
Daddy doesn't live with us anymore, baby.
He had to go find himself.
- [man] It had its moments.
- [woman] Yeah.
[Davis] They still feel tight in the toe.
Have an argument.
You're having an argument. Have it.
- I don't buy it.
- You, sir, are a horse's ass.
What? Just get the fucking shoe.
You gave me two sizes too big.
Tom, don't turn into another person
just because I say change your action.
- And this started just today?
- Mm-hm.
- It never happened before?
- Mm-mm.
Okay. Good.
You can get dressed.
I mean, you're a doctor, right?
Am I dying? Can you tell me that?
- No.
- No, you can't tell me?
- I can't tell you.
- No, you can't tell me
if you can't tell me?
- No.
- No, you can't tell me
- 'cause you're not allowed to?
- No.
[foot tapping]
- Caden!
- What are you doing here?
Oh, I... I...
I was wondering
if I was gonna bump into you.
- You look great.
- Thanks.
- Is that a new haircut?
- Yeah. For a while now.
What are you doing in New York?
Oh, I'm here with Derek and the boys.
A mini vacation.
- The boys?
- Yeah. I thought you knew.
- How old?
- Five.
Uh, twins. Robert and Daniel and Alan.
Aw.
Yes.
They're nice names. Where are they?
Derek took them to the Natural History,
so I could shop.
Ah.
It's so good to see you, Caden.
I-- How are things?
You know, I, uh... I was with Claire.
And we have a daughter.
But we're separated.
Um, how about with you?
Good. I have a great job at Lens Shapers.
Shapers. Great. You wear a lab coat.
- It's so good to see you.
- Oh, good to see you, Hazel.
[melancholy music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[man] Hey! What are you doing?
- I got you.
- [Caden] Let me go.
[Olive in German accent]
How I love Maria.
She is so much more of a father
than Caden ever was,
with his drinking and unfortunate
body odor and rotting teeth.
I could only loathe him
and perhaps pity him.
But Maria!
- [knocking on door]
- [door opens]
[Caden] I wanna come back.
I wanna take care of you and Olive.
Ariel. Ariel. Fuck.
Ariel.
[phone ringing]
[Claire] No, no, no, it's so late. Please.
No, no, no. Please.
[Caden] Hello?
[man speaking indistinctly on phone]
Okay.
[somber music playing]
My father died.
Oh, baby.
[Caden] They said his body was riddled
with cancer and that he didn't know.
That he went in because his finger hurt.
They said he suffered horribly.
And that he...
That he called out for me before he died.
They said that he said
he regretted his life.
And they said he said a lot of things.
Too many to recount.
They said it was the longest
and saddest deathbed speech
any of them had ever heard.
There was so little left of him,
they had to fill the coffin
with cotton balls
to keep him from rattling around.
I'm really sorry for your loss.
Thank you. Can you excuse me a moment?
- Of course.
- I need to use the bathroom.
- All right.
- Okay.
[woman] God bless you and your family.
[Caden] God bless you.
Will you excuse me?
[line rings]
[Hazel on recording] It's Hazel.
Leave a message or not. It's your dime.
[beeps]
[man on radio] It's left five people dead.
[Caden] Sorry.
- [Hazel] Caden?
- Hi, Derek.
Officials suspect arson.
In other news,
a German pharmaceutical giant
has won its libel suit against patients
claiming chromosomal damage
from use of the arthritis medication...
Will you, uh, just tell me what to do?
... 1.3 billion dollars in damages.
In Pakistan today, the government there--
Caden, everyone has to figure out
their own life, you know.
I just want you to look at me
the way you used to.
Oh, honey, I can't anymore.
You know I'm sorry.
I screwed everything up,
and I don't have any courage.
- And I'm sorry.
- Caden.
- I'm okay.
- I don't want you to be okay.
I mean, I do, but it just, uh...
It rips my guts out.
I'll help you through any way I can.
And I'll help you through too.
I'm fine.
I have Derek.
Okay, I'm going.
[melancholy music playing]
[Hazel] Honey, I'm coming.
[Olive] Dear diary, today I felt
a wetness between my legs.
Maria explained to me now I am a woman.
And being a woman is wonderful
with Maria to guide me.
Olive?
Olive.
Olive, it's Daddy.
Olive, it's Daddy! Olive, it's Daddy!
Don't fucking stare at me! Olive! It--
Get off! It's my daughter!
That's my daughter!
Get off! Get off!
I won't settle for anything less
than the brutal truth.
Brutal. Brutal.
Each day I'll hand you a scrap of paper.
It'll tell you what happened
to you that day.
You felt a lump in your breast.
You looked at your wife
and saw a stranger, et cetera.
- [man] Caden?
- What?!
When are we gonna get an audience in here?
It's been 17 years.
All right, I'm not excusing myself
from this either.
I will have someone play me,
to delve into the murky, cowardly depths
of my lonely, fucked-up being.
And he'll get notes too,
and those notes will correspond
to the notes I truly receive
every day from my god.
Get to work!
[dramatic music playing]
They fired me.
Uh...
- I caused an outbreak of conjunctivitis.
- [Caden] Oh, God.
I didn't wash my hands.
I had pinkeye hands.
- Oh, God.
- I'm such a stupid cow.
Fucking private Christian school is
killing us. You know, it's not cheap.
It's Derek's thing.
I don't believe in that shit, you know.
You try to be a good person.
I mean, that's all there is.
Do you have anything for me, Caden?
Uh...
I mean, I already have an assistant.
Um...
- I don't have a box office yet, but--
- Please, Caden.
Please, Caden. I...
Please, Caden.
Sammy Barnathan?
Sit. Sammy Barnathan.
[camera dings]
I don't have a résumé or a picture.
- I've never worked as an actor.
- Good. Tell me why you're here.
Well, I've been...
I've been following you for 20 years.
So I knew about this audition
because I follow you.
And I've learned everything
about you by following you.
So hire me
and you'll see who you truly are.
Peekaboo.
Okay.
Hazel, I don't think we need to talk
to anyone else. This guy has me down.
I'm gonna cast him right now.
And then maybe you and I can get a drink.
And we can try to figure out
this thing between us,
why I cried.
Because I've never felt about anybody
the way I feel about you.
And I wanna fuck you
until we merge into a chimera,
a mythical beast with penis
and vagina eternally fused,
two pairs of eyes
that look only at each other...
and lips ever touching.
And one voice that whispers to itself.
[somber music playing]
Okay.
Yeah. You've got the part.
[toilets flushing]
I've never seen your shit gray.
It's new.
That's a good boy.
- [indistinct chatter]
- [sirens chirping]
- When is it opening?
- When it's ready.
[man] We need to get in.
It's bad out here.
- Sorry. Ahem.
- [gunfire in distance]
[people screaming in distance]
You know, I was thinking
of calling it Simulacrum.
I-- I don't even know what it means.
Can I have a nickel if I doesn't play
with my pee-pee no more?
Yeah.
How about The Flawed Light
of Love and Grief?
I'm not sure.
[Caden] Claire, I want you
to play yourself.
Sammy's gonna move
into your apartment set as me.
It-- Uh...
It would be my honor
to play your husband, Claire.
You're an amazing actress.
No, I saw you do Bernarda Alba
last year at the Roundabout.
Yeah?
That was a fun play.
Emotionally, it was tough,
but fucking fulfilling.
Plus, I loved working
with so many strong female actresses.
I'm gonna start thinking about myself.
[gunfire in distance]
- Start, huh?
- [both chuckling]
[Claire] Who is Claire Keen?
Claire Keen. Claire Keen.
- Why did we leave Adele, Caden?
- [Claire] Claire Keen. Well...
She left us.
You know that better than anybody.
Except me.
An amazing artist though.
The best living artist.
I mean, there's no one who stares
the truth in the face like she does.
Sweet pussy too.
How do you know that?
Oh... l read it.
[Claire continues speaking indistinctly]
Anyway...
I don't know where she is.
[zeppelin horn honks]
[Sammy] Well, maybe she's got
a sublet in New York.
Maybe she's got a retrospective
at the Met. Maybe, baby.
[Caden] Why are you giving me this?
I wanna follow you there and see
how you lose even more of yourself.
Research.
You know, for the part.
Partner.
[mellow music playing]
[buzzes]
[door beeps]
[man] Hold it! Hold it, please.
Hold it, please.
I asked you to hold the door.
I'm sorry. I pressed the button,
but I think it was too late.
You didn't press it.
- Have a good night.
- Yeah, thanks.
- [woman] Are you Ellen? Ellen?
- What?
- Are you Ellen Bascomb?
I'm to give the key to 31Y
to Ellen Bascomb.
Yes, I'm Ellen.
She said you should just go ahead
and get started.
- And don't forget to change the sheets.
- Okay, thanks.
Oh, sweetheart.
[shower running]
[Caden] Adele?
Adele?
[Adele] Hi, Ellen.
Be a doll and do the sheets
and whatever's in the hamper.
[Adele coughing]
Your money's under the toaster.
Kisses, mwah, Adele.
P.S. Bag of stuff in bedroom closet
for Goodwill. Take what you want.
Went for a walk. I had to think.
[Claire] All night?
You smell weird. Are you wearing lipstick?
No.
What do I smell like?
Like bad? Like an old person?
I don't know.
Like mold and cleaning products.
Like you're menstruating. I don't know.
Menstruating?
You tell me.
I don't menstruate. So I don't know
how I could smell like I'm menstruating.
[Claire] I wouldn't know.
[Claire] I don't like the guy you got
to play you.
You don't like Sammy?
Why? I think he's good.
[Claire] You should fire him.
Fuck you. I'm 45 years old.
I don't wanna do this shit anymore.
I won't fire him. He's the best thing
in the play except you.
He's coming on to me.
He's grabbing my ass in rehearsal.
[man] Be quiet! Shut up!
- He's your husband.
- Good, Jimmy.
He's not my goddamn husband. You are.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
- I'm going to rehearsal.
- It's about the play.
- We're getting at something real here.
- That's great, you guys.
Beautiful, Sammy.
- Caden? Time-out?
- Yeah.
What's up?
Well, I feel we need a Hazel in here.
I mean, there's a whole side of Caden
I can't explore without a Hazel.
- I guess, yeah.
- [Hazel] I get to be a character?
- Yeah.
- Hooray.
[Adele] Hi, Ellen.
Crackerjack job last night.
[Adele coughing]
Would you do sheets again?
We had quite a fuck,
and it's musky and gross. Kisses, A.
[Caden] Hi, Adele. Relined the cabinets.
I just wanted to let you know
I won a MacArthur Grant.
And I'm mounting a play which
I think is gonna be pure and truthful.
Best, Ellen.
[Sammy] I went for a walk. I had to think.
[Claire] Caden,
what are you doing at night?
I have a right to fucking know.
I've been going to Adele's place.
And cleaning it.
Do you have any idea
what I've given up for you? For this?
[knocking on door]
For you? For you?
Could you please get that?
Uh-oh. This looks serious.
Am I interrupting?
What's going on, Hazel?
Just wanted you to know
that the actress playing me
is ready to start today.
That's great. That's all we need
around here, is two Hazels.
Okay, I'll take that as my cue.
- Maybe you could clean her toilet.
- Maybe I will.
This is over.
- No, Claire--
- I'm not talking to you.
I didn't say I was gonna
clean Hazel's toilet. He did.
But you thought it!
I thought it, but I didn't say it.
I got an offer to do
Needleman in a Haystack.
And I'm gonna take it.
I want you out of the apartment.
The real one. You can keep this one.
Claire.
- Jesus. Claire.
- [door slams]
[buttons beeping]
[Hazel] Hi, yeah, we're gonna need
a Claire replacement.
[Caden] Claire! I didn't say it!
[somber music playing]
I already put out a call
for a Claire replacement.
But I'm afraid I'm gonna have to move on.
Just like that?
You don't give a guy even a chance?
I'm not a chance-giving girl.
I'm a fun-loving girl, remember?
I try and be fun-loving, see?
[Claire laughs]
[Claire] Sorry.
My analyst says you have complexes.
Once you enjoyed Needleman's complexes.
- That's before my analyst taught me--
- [Caden] This is the last of my stuff.
- Bye.
- Bye. From the top?
Oh, Needleman, you had such potential.
But I'm afraid I'm gonna have to move on.
[Claire laughing]
[Claire] I'm sorry. Okay.
Oh, Needleman, you had such potential.
But I'm afraid
I'm going to have to move on.
[laughing]
[actor] Just like that?
You don't give a guy a chance?
[actress] I'm not a chance-giving girl.
I'm a fun-loving girl.
[actor] Once you enjoyed
Needleman's complexes.
[actress]
That's before my analyst taught me--
This is a lie.
[actor] Come here.
I try to be fun-loving, see?
- [actress] She told me your hatred...
- Will.
[actress] ...was a sign
of your latent homosexuality.
Wall it up. All of it.
[Sammy] Claire.
[Claire moaning]
[monitor beeping]
[Claire] Oh, Needleman. Oh!
All right.
[Adele coughing]
Good for you with your grant.
Listen, I fixed up the walk-in
as a sort of bedroom if you want.
We'd love to have you
and you wouldn't have to schlep
all the way to Queens.
[Adele coughing]
It's just a thought. Kisses, A.
[Olive] Dear diary,
I'm afraid I'm gravely ill.
It is perhaps times like these
that one reflects on things past.
An article of clothing
from when I was young.
A green jacket. A walk with my father.
- A game we once played.
- Pretend we're fairies.
I'm a girl fairy
and my name is Lauralee.
And you're a boy fairy
and your name is Teetery.
Pretend when we're fairies,
we fight each other.
And I say, "Stop hitting me or I'll die."
And you hit me again, and I say:
"Now I have to die."
And you say, "But I'll miss you."
And I say, "But I have to.
And you'll have to wait a million years
to see me again.
And I'll be put in a box,
and all I'll need is a tiny glass of water
and lots of tiny pieces of pizza.
And the box will have wings
like an airplane."
And you ask, "Where will it take you?"
- "Home," I say.
- Home.
This is to hear.
- So words-- English here, yeah?
- Okay.
[in German]
It's Maria. She did this.
Your mother and Maria took you away.
I've tried for years to find you.
I didn't leave you.
I'm not a homosexual.
Well, she's a liar. She's lying to you.
Maria is your lover?
You have no idea how evil she is.
I just want--
Can you ever forgive me?
For abandoning you.
I will, I'll say it.
For abandoning you...
to have anal sex
with my homosexual lover, Eric.
[both sobbing]
- Oh...
- [footsteps approaching]
I hope you are happy, faggot.
I'm not happy. I'm not happy.
[dramatic music playing]
[whimsical music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
I've talked to you before. This is not
a play about dating. It's about death.
Make it personal. Move along.
He doesn't need to yell at them.
[Caden clears throat]
It is a play about dating.
It's not a play just about death.
It's about everything.
Dating, birth, death, life, family,
all that.
- This doesn't look real.
- What?
- It's not real.
- l can't hear you.
[car horns honking over speakers]
- Morning, Haze.
- Hi, Caden. How was your night?
It was okay. Yours?
Ugh. Phillip was colicky.
I was up all night.
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
- Everybody here?
- Sammy's not here.
Jimmy called and, ahem,
said there's some subway problem.
Sorry. Sorry.
- Hi, Hazel.
- Hi, Sammy.
Sammy likes you.
I need you to build this.
This is just the facade.
It's Adele's place.
We'll be casting an Ellen.
I can get you the interiors later.
A few days?
[woman] Can I look again?
[man] A slight shift in perspective
on this one.
Millicent Weems?
- Caden, this is--
- Hazel, what do you think of this title?
Unknown, Unkissed and Lost?
Eh.
Anyway, uh, this is Millicent Weems.
[Caden] Have a seat.
How are you at cleaning?
- Very, very good at it.
- 'Cause this part requires a lot of it.
You'd be playing a cleaning lady.
I played Egga, the cleaning lady,
in Hedda Gabler at the Roundabout.
- Great. Okay.
- And, uh...
Mrs. Dobson in Scrub-A-Dub
at the Pantages.
You're weirdly close to what I visualize
for this character.
Glad to be weirdly close.
[man] Sorry, everybody!
- Maurice, what's going on?
- I'm sorry.
We have a couple of new guys on.
We're not in sync yet.
- We good to go?
- Yes, sir.
[coughs] I'm sorry.
Fuck.
Are you Ellen? Are you Ellen Bascomb?
Shit.
Line, please?
Ellen... "What?"
Right, right. What?
I'm to give the key to 31Y
to Ellen Bascomb.
Yes, I'm Ellen.
Oh, dear. It's the wrong key.
[Adele] I'll be in, in a second.
- Did you hear that?
- What?
- Uh, you're breaking the fourth wall.
- This is the wrong key.
No, I can open the--
- I'm supposed to open the door.
- Hold on.
[dramatic music playing]
- Are you in there?
- There's no one in there.
- Adele?
- Caden.
[Adele] I don't think it's...
It's not quite...
I'm jumping in the shower.
I'll be out in a second.
[shower running]
Do you want some coffee?
I can make a fresh pot.
Did you look at the new painting
on my easel? What do you think?
Hey, thanks for the fuck this morning.
- People don't walk like that.
- What? Is it too...?
No, just walk like yourself.
Watch. Watch this.
I gotta go.
Watch this.
Where's, uh, Hazel and Sammy?
[indistinct chatter]
Sammy.
Sammy. Sammy.
- Hi, Caden.
- What are you doing?
I was being you.
You know, you like Hazel, I like Hazel.
This Hazel doesn't exist for you.
If you wanna like a Hazel, like that one.
That's what I tried to tell him.
No harm, no foul, Caden.
It's equity break anyway.
Ten minutes, everybody!
- [Caden] Hazel.
- What?
- You don't like him, do you?
- [Hazel] Yeah, he reminds me of you.
[Caden laughs]
I'm me. You don't need someone
to remind you of me.
Oh, don't worry, Caden. I like you more.
I do. It's just, Sammy's fun.
[cell phone ringing]
- I'm fun.
- Oh, sweetie, no, you're not.
Hold on a sec. Yes?
- [man] Is this Caden Cotard?
- Yes.
This is Officer Melnin of Schenectady P.D.
I'm sorry to inform you your mother's
been the victim of a home invasion.
- What does that mean?
- She is dead.
Was my father standing with us?
[in English accent]
I don't know what he looks like.
He's dead.
- So he looks dead, I guess.
- Probably wasn't him, then.
He was a big guy.
Anyway...
Thanks for coming with me.
That's okay.
I asked Hazel,
but she was busy tonight,
and you're the next best thing.
I mean, it's not that you're
the next best thing,
but because you play her,
it feels comforting.
Does that make sense?
Although the thing is,
off-stage you're nothing like her.
But you play her very well though.
Did Hazel mention
what she was doing tonight?
Because I called her house before we left,
and her husband told me
she wasn't gonna be back till late.
And I just thought that was weird
because she said Phillip was sick.
She's having dinner with Sammy.
- That's interesting.
- He's supposed to like me.
I'll have another talk with him.
Will you excuse me?
I need to go to the bathroom.
- Don't forget your phone.
- Mmm.
Thanks, Yammy.
[line rings]
[Hazel on recording] It's Hazel.
Leave a message or not. It's your dime.
You can stay in my parents' room.
[dial tone beeping]
I thought
someone would have cleaned it up.
[Tammy] Who?
I don't know. Someone.
This is my room. Ahem. You can sleep here.
[Tammy] Where are you going to sleep?
- [sighs] The living-room couch.
- Don't you want to sleep with me?
- It's just sex.
- Okay.
If you think it's okay.
- How can you be like that?
- I get undressed every day.
[Caden] In front of someone is different.
I don't see why.
Maybe because
you have a beautiful body.
- Maybe that makes it easier.
- Yeah, I suppose it might.
Do you want to fuck?
I do. Um, do you?
- Take your clothes off.
- I'm sorry.
I'm very, very lonely.
I don't, uh...
know what's wrong. I just...
I'm sorry.
Do you understand?
I mean, can you understand loneliness?
Yeah. I mean...
I don't know. I feel okay, mostly.
Fucking might help.
Uh...
I'm sorry.
It's okay, I don't mind.
Take your clothes off.
- You're very pretty.
- Thanks.
Sometimes I wish
I could be pretty like that.
What, you wish you were a girl?
Sometimes I think
I might have been better at it.
Interesting.
It's kind of a drag in a lot of ways.
- Do you like guys?
- No. I only love women.
Well, I'm getting cold.
[mellow music playing]
You're pretty, Caden.
Thanks for saying that.
Come to bed, pretty Caden.
I shouldn't have drunk
so much fucking beer last night.
[man] What will you do about it?
[woman] Get lunch.
What will you do about it?
- [man] Oh, for chrissake.
- Good, Roland.
[man] Thanks, Caden.
We need to fire him.
We don't need to fire him.
[Sammy] Jeremy's playing to us.
Just tell him to simply talk to Donna
and we'll hear what we hear.
Sammy's explaining too much.
It feels expository.
It needs to be shorthand, like,
"Jeremy, big."
Caden, can we stop a second?
[Caden] Sure.
If Hazel's in love with Sammy,
and Caden's in love with Hazel,
there would be a big confrontation
where Caden turns to me and says:
"It's obvious he's a substitute for me."
Then I think Hazel would have
a good moment where she cries
or gets angry, I'm not sure which yet,
but I think it's dramatically sound--
- [Hazel] That didn't happen, Caden.
- No, I think Hazel would do that, Hazel.
- But Hazel hasn't done that, Tammy.
- Caden, what do you think?
I-- I feel like we could try it.
- Great.
- Fuck.
Let's try it. Maybe it could happen
at the director's table.
Ahem. Fuck.
You know, Tammy's right.
I don't understand why you're with Sammy.
He's nice, he's available,
he fucks me without crying.
Since when are you available?
Derek left because of you.
When? How come you never told me?
I don't know, Caden.
How come a lot of things, huh?
Fuck. I gotta let go of the actor
who played Derek. What's his name?
What?
That is such a romantic response.
- I am touched.
- It's not my response.
- Derek is played by--
- It crossed my mind.
- We have enormous budgetary concerns.
- Oh, oh.
- Joe.
- Stop. Okay? No, just stop.
I do not like Tammy,
and she's nothing like me.
- How can you like her, anyway?
- She looks like you.
- Joe Abernathy. No, she does not.
- She offered to have sex with me.
- Abernathy?
- Yeah.
- Was it good? Ugh.
- It was nice.
I'm just being honest. It was nice.
It wasn't earth-shattering.
- Did you cry?
- No.
You're making progress.
Okay, I cried a little before.
Hazel, you've been a part of me forever.
Don't you know that?
[dramatic music playing]
I breathe your name in every exhalation.
- What are we doing?
- I don't know.
Oh, this is the place I stayed
with Derek and the kids.
- We're almost finished with the terrace.
- Caden.
Caden.
- Caden. Caden, look at me!
- What are you doing?
Sammy, stay right where you are!
I'm coming up!
There's nothing to talk about, Hazel.
It's not your fault.
- What are you doing?
- I've watched you forever, Caden.
But you've never really looked
at anyone other than yourself.
So watch me.
Watch my heart break. Watch me jump.
Watch me learn
that after death there's nothing.
There's no more watching,
there's no more following, no love.
Say goodbye to Hazel for me.
And say it for yourself too.
- None of us has much time.
- Sammy! Come down!
[Sammy] Hazel, I love you!
[Caden] Sammy!
I didn't jump, Sammy!
A man stopped me before I jumped. Get up!
I didn't jump.
[whispering indistinctly]
I know how to do it now.
There are nearly 13 million people
in the world.
I mean, can you imagine that many people?
And none of those people is an extra.
They're all leads in their own stories.
They have to be given their due.
[actor] I know how to do it now.
There are 13 million people in this world.
Can you imagine how many people that is?
None of those people are an extra.
They're all a lead in their own story.
They have got to be given their due.
Do you see what I'm saying?
[Hazel] Come over tonight.
Please.
[Caden] You know,
we could get a place together.
- We could get a loft.
- God, Caden, that sounds nice.
I miss my daughter.
Maybe she could come live with us.
I miss Olive.
And the other one.
- I'm a bad person.
- Oh, no, you're not.
I am. I should never have
gone out with Sammy.
I was just trying to get to you.
You can't cause someone to kill himself.
He was very troubled.
God, Caden.
I wish we had this when we were young.
And all those years in between.
My heart aches so much for you.
We're here, Caden.
- I'm here.
- I'm aching for it being over.
Yeah. The end is built into the beginning.
What can you do?
- God, you're just perfect.
- I'm a mess.
- But we fit, don't we?
- Yeah.
[Caden] It doesn't always
happen for me now
because of the medication and everything.
- I take a lot of pills.
- It's okay.
Uh, I'm embarrassed. I don't want you
to think it's about you or me.
It's okay.
[tender music playing]
I have a title.
The Obscure Moon
Lighting an Obscure World.
I think it might be too much.
Yeah, probably.
[Caden chuckles]
[man] Sir, could you come up here, please?
Might be smoke inhalation.
[Hazel on recording] It's Hazel.
Leave a message or not. It's your dime.
- [beeps]
- I know how to do the play now.
It'll all take place
over the course of one day,
and that day will be the day
before you died.
It was the happiest day of my life.
And I'll be able to relive it forever.
See you soon.
So have you got any thoughts
for, uh, today's rehearsal?
- l have a new title, maybe.
- Oh.
Infectious Diseases in Cattle.
Oh.
The title means a lot of things.
You'll see, it means a lot.
[clock ticking]
I need a Caden for my Hazel.
I'd very much like to play Caden.
[, uh-- I know that--
I know
that it would be nontraditional casting,
but I think I could do it.
I think I understand him.
I don't understand him.
Well, Caden Cotard is a man already dead.
He, um... He lives in a half world
between stasis and antistasis,
and time is concentrated,
chronology confused.
Yet up until recently,
he's strived valiantly...
to make sense of his situation.
But now, he, uh...
He's turned to stone.
- Okay. Sounds good.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
- She's right? [stammers]
I didn't see that at all.
I saw it as much more hopeful.
None of those people is extras.
They're all leads in their own stories.
No, this is tedious. This is nothing.
[whispering] Hi, your scene's over.
Would you leave the stage?
- What is she doing?
- He's directing.
Can I get you down at the coffin there?
[Michael] She not getting
the feel of you, Caden.
You don't move around like that.
You don't talk to people.
Sit on the ground there.
Okay, everybody, let's run it.
Everything is more complicated
than you think.
You only see a tenth of what is true.
There are a million little strings
attached to every choice you make.
You can destroy your life
every time you choose.
But maybe you won't know for 20 years,
and you may never, ever trace it
to its source.
And you only get one chance
to play it out.
Just try and figure out your own divorce.
And they say there is no fate,
but there is, it's what you create.
And even though the world goes on
for eons and eons,
you are only here for a fraction
of a fraction of a second.
Most of your time is spent being dead
or not yet born.
But while alive, you wait in vain,
wasting years for a phone call
or a letter or a look
from someone or something
to make it all right.
And it never comes, or it seems to,
but it doesn't really.
So you spend your time in vague regret
or vaguer hope that something good
will come along.
Something to make you feel connected.
Something to make you feel whole.
Something to make you feel loved.
[gospel music playing over speakers]
And the truth is...
I feel so angry.
I feel so fucking sad.
And the truth is, I've felt
so fucking hurt for so fucking long.
And for just as long,
I've been pretending I'm okay
just to get along, just for...
[mourners sobbing]
I don't know why.
Maybe because no one wants
to hear about my misery...
because they have their own.
Well, fuck everybody.
- Amen.
- Delightful.
- Thanks.
I'm out of ideas.
I'm dead.
Well, I could take over as you for a bit
until you feel refreshed.
I think you're tired, Caden.
All these years of creative work.
I think you just need some time
to regroup.
- I need to keep my hand in.
- Well, Ellen needs to be filled.
- What do you mean?
- Her role. Just for a bit.
It's a choice role.
I do like to clean.
Ellen?
- Yes?
- Caden asked me to give you this.
You're to keep it in all the time.
[Millicent on radio] So touched
by the sadness of Adele's neighbor
so close to death.
Say, "Thank you," to Adele's neighbor.
Thank you.
You're very welcome, young lady.
- Now say, "Have a very good day."
- Have a very good day.
I will indeed.
Reach for the toilet paper.
Wrap some around your hand.
Wipe yourself.
[monitor beeping]
There was supposed to be something else.
You were supposed
to have something, a calm.
Love.
Children.
A child, at least.
Meaning.
Everything okay, Eric?
- Everything is everything.
- [Ellen] He hates me.
I disappointed him, and he hates me.
Everyone is disappointing
when you know someone.
[Ellen] I remember having that picnic
with my mother. Look at me.
Ellen, what is it?
I was so young.
I'm going to remember this moment
for the rest of my life, Mama,
and in exactly 20 years,
come here with my daughter
and have exactly the same picnic.
There was so much hope.
Baby, that's the loveliest thing
I've ever heard.
Oh, God. Sorry, Mommy. I'm sorry.
Where is my little girl?
Look at the night table
for a note from Adele.
[computer reading on-screen text]
Stare out the window.
Remember the time she got you
to pose for one of her paintings?
How she told you how beautiful you were?
How she made you feel pretty again
for a little while?
Think how you'll miss her.
Stand up.
[explosions in distance]
Now it is waiting, and nobody cares.
And when your wait is over,
this room will still exist...
[crowd clamoring]
...and it will continue to hold shoes
and dresses and boxes
and maybe someday
another waiting person. And maybe not.
- [woman] What do we want?
- [crowd] Freedom!
The room doesn't care either.
[clamoring continues]
[explosion]
- [Millicent] Hello?
- [static buzzes on radio]
[door opens]
[groans, then sighs]
There's nobody running
the elevator anymore.
[man screams]
[dramatic music playing]
[Millicent] What was once before you,
an exciting and mysterious future,
is now behind you,
lived, understood, disappointing.
You realize you are not special.
You have struggled into existence
and are now slipping silently out of it.
This is everyone's experience.
Every single one.
The specifics hardly matter.
Everyone is everyone.
So you are Adele,
Hazel, Claire, Olive.
You are Ellen.
All her meager sadnesses are yours.
All her loneliness.
The gray, straw-like hair.
Her red, raw hands. It's yours.
It is time for you to understand this.
Walk.
As the people who adore you
stop adoring you,
as they die, as they move on,
as you shed them, as you shed
your beauty, your youth,
as the world forgets you,
as you recognize your transience,
as you begin to lose
your characteristics one by one,
as you learn
there is no one watching you,
and there never was,
you think only about driving.
Not coming from anyplace,
not arriving anyplace,
just driving, counting off time.
Now you are here. It's 7:43.
Now you are here. It's 7:44.
Now you are... gone.
[Caden] Where is everybody?
Mostly dead.
Some have left.
Would you sit with me for a moment?
'Cause I'm very tired and lonely.
I feel like I know you.
Well, I was the, um,
mother in Ellen's dream.
Yes.
You seem a bit older than I remember.
That dream was quite a while ago.
[static buzzes on radio]
[Millicent] Apologize.
I didn't mean to say you looked old.
[somber music playing]
There's everyone's dreams
in all those apartments.
All those thoughts I'll never know.
That's the truth of it.
I wanted to do that picnic
with my daughter.
I feel like
I've disappointed you terribly.
Oh, no. I am so proud of you.
Ask her if you can put your head
on her shoulder.
Can I lay my head on your shoulder?
Yes.
I love you.
I love you too.
I know how to do this play now.
I have an idea.
I think if everyone--
Die.
♪ I'm just a little person ♪
♪ One person in a sea ♪
♪ Of many little people I
♪ Who are not aware of me ♪
♪ I do my little job ♪
♪ And live my little life ♪
♪ Eat my little meals ♪
♪ Miss my little kid and wife ♪
♪ And somewhere, maybe someday ♪
♪ Maybe somewhere far away ♪
♪ I'll find a second little person ♪
I Who will look at me and say ♪
♪ "lI know you ♪
Jd You're the one I've waited for ♪
♪ Let's have some fun" ♪
♪ Life is precious every minute ♪
♪ And more precious with you in it ♪
♪ So let's have some fun ♪
♪ I'm glad I've found you ♪
♪ Like hangin' 'round you ♪
♪ You're the one ♪
♪ I like the best ♪
♪ Somewhere, maybe someday ♪
♪ Maybe somewhere far away ♪
♪ I'll meet a second little person ♪
♪ And we'll go out and play ♪