No...
Mom...
[loudspeaker] Silk scissors,
ham knives.
Ladies, the knife sharpener
and the umbrella repairer are here.
- Hello.
- Mm... Hello.
Listen, but... Did you have nightmares again last night?
- Why?
- I don't know...
You got up, I thought.
- Oh, no.
-Ah.
Well, anyway, we have to tell
the doctor about this, okay?
I have to go now,
Chiara will give you a ride.
No, I want Dad.
- Silly girl!
- See you tonight.
- Bye.
Good morning, sweetheart.
Are you still like that? And late.
Come on, you'll skip breakfast.
No, I don't think I'll be going in today.
I feel terribly nauseous.
You know that if you eat, it'll go away?
Come on, I have to be at the ward at nine.
- Didn't they give you your scooter back?
- No, since you're giving me a ride.
At least close the door
since you don't knock, okay?
[Chiara] Hurry up, we're late.
- Don't run, it's wet.
- Yes, I saw.
Sofi?
Hey, Sofi?
Are you there?
- What's wrong?
- Oh my God...
- You gave me a fright.
- Sorry.
That bitch
gave me the flu.
- Who?
- Chiara.
She was sick yesterday and drank
from the bottle. She's disgusting.
I'd say so.
Then this morning I told her I felt like this
and she made fun of me.
- Did you throw up?
- No, I'm just nauseous.
- Are you feeling any better now?
- Yes.
[girl] We have a test tomorrow.
[boy] I'm not coming...
Let's go.
- Hey!
Weren't you in the hospital?
Well, you could say that...
I wasn't feeling well, so I came back.
Are you staying for lunch?
No, I'll just get the horse's things and we'll go.
I'm coming.
- Hi, Dora.
- Hi, Sofia.
- How was your day?
- Relax...
- Fine.
- Good.
- Do you ride too?
- No, I just accompany them.
- Don't you like it?
- No.
- [Sofia] Dora, where's the cap?
- I haven't seen it.
Honey, I put it in the closet
because it was on the floor.
- Shall we go?
- Let's go.
Anyway, everything's ready.
If you want to stay...
No, leave it for dinner.
- You won't be here, will you?
No.
Okay. Bye. Let's go.
Goodbye.
Have fun.
Bye, Sofi.
[woman] Softly and watch the distance.
Okay, Sofia, very good.
The leg close, the leg close.
Okay, come on.
The exercise was good, everything was fine.
Stand up a little straighter.
Look where you're going. Go, Alice, go.
[Sofia] How was it?
[woman] Easy turn...
[boy] Pretty cool.
[woman] Okay, make a circle...
Listen, but... are you sure
your house is free tonight?
Silvia told me
there's a party at Acrobax.
What can I say? Do what you want.
Do you think I'd go without you?
[woman] Girls, see you on Wednesday.
[Pietro] I have an appointment now,
then I'm going to play paddle tennis.
- [Chiara] Is dinner canceled?
- No, we'll finish early.
I'll take a shower at the club,
then I'll stop by the house to change.
If you're feeling better, we can go together.
I still feel a little nauseous,
but I'd like to try to come.
Okay. Sofia?
- Bad day.
- Did you argue again?
Not really, but... I always feel like
I'm bothering her, I don't know.
And now...
I don't know, maybe it's just me being anxious.
Okay, we'll talk about it together tomorrow.
Don't worry about it now.
- I'll call you later.
- OK
- Bye, honey.
- Hi.
I can hold her for a moment because
Banchi Vecchi, outdoor space...
- I mean, you understand that...
- [woman] We'll let you know.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Are you still feeling like that?
I don't feel well.
At lunch you said you were going.
I know, I was hoping I'd feel better, but...
Manuel is coming over for dinner.
We had planned it.
Sorry, I'll go to my room.
You can't see me.
Sooner or later, everything will fall apart.
[Sofia] All week she kept saying
that her house would be free on Friday.
Now that Friday has come,
there's no way it's free.
- [boy] Just forget about her...
- No, she's just a bitch.
She has the ability to make me lose it
with that little voice of hers...
“I'm sweet, pretty, and kind.”
Fuck you.
- See you at Acrobax, okay?
- Okay, see you later.
- I'm not staying alone with her.
- You're right.
- Oh well, come on. Bye.
- Bye.
Damn.
Well done!
Sofi, honey, could you turn
the music down a little, please?
I have a headache.
[Chiara] At least a little bit...
- Is the scrub finished?
- [Chiara] Yes.
You used it all. How am I supposed to do it?
[Chiara] I'll call the United Nations.
Could you turn it down a little, please?
Is the conditioner finished too?
- Bye, see you on Tuesday.
- Bye.
- Why don't you come too tonight?
- I wish I could.
They brought me some scampi
that are alive, they're moving.
I have to be in court at eight tomorrow.
Say hi to Chiara for me.
- Bye. Thanks for the game.
- Bye.
[Pietro] Hi, honey, I'm leaving now.
I'll be home in ten minutes.
- Bye, Pie', see you later.
- Bye.
Honey, I made roast beef.
There are tomatoes with rice too.
- I'm going out.
- But you didn't eat anything for lunch.
It's not good for you, you're too thin.
Come on, stay for dinner, keep me company.
No, wait.
Here, use this.
Come on, stay, so we can chat a bit.
If you come by after school tomorrow,
we can grab a bite and chat.
Yes!
Let's go to the place that makes delicious tacos.
I'm messing with you, don't you get it?
- Why are you acting like this?
I was just here making a sandwich
and you had to come and bother me.
- You always want me to talk.
- It's normal, people talk.
About what?
Look at the mess you're making.
You're making me nervous.
I don't know, you're always angry.
Anyway, nothing happened.
I enjoyed spending some time together.
For you, but not for me.
You repeat things to me a hundred times
to get them into my head.
- Sofi...
- Don't call me Sofi.
Because you're not my mother.
- No, of course not.
- “No, of course not.”
- I don't know what's going on.
- Nothing's going on!
You're driving me crazy with your little smiles,
your roasts, but not the knife.
- You're driving me crazy.
- I'm calling Dad.
- Don't you dare.
- You're hurting me, Sofi!
- I understood you right away.
- What are you talking about?
Five years after
Mom died, what are you doing?
Looking for a house, and where do you end up?
Is that what you think?
-I was looking for a studio apartment downtown.
- Right in Dad's agency.
Unbelievable, what a coincidence!
Do you think we're stupid?
That's how it went. I thought
your father could help me.
Liar! You're a liar!
You know what? He can't stand you either.
He just fucks you.
Enough!
- Please!
- But do you think
that I don't hear you panting
and moaning at night?
You spy on us. We love each other.
- Only you wanted this family.
- I'm not your mother. I never will be...
- Don't talk about her.
- She was wonderful,
- Very strong.
- Don't talk about my mother!
And you managed to kill her!
- What are you saying?
- You didn't do a damn thing to help her.
- You didn't do anything with your IVs!
- There was nothing we could do.
- You were happy!
- Are you crazy?
You're a bitch!
Chiara?
- Hi.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Chiara?
Chiara!
Sofia?
Girls, you left
the door open, huh?
Chiara?
Chiara...
Girls, where are you?
Come on! Sofia?
Sofia...
Oh my God...
Chiara!
Sofia!
My God...
Chiara...
- [man] Did you call?
- [Pietro] Yes.
Get away from the knife
and stand up. Come on! Hurry up!
- What happened? Is that your wife?
- [Pietro] Yes...
Sofia...
- Who is Sofia?
- My daughter.
- Was it Sofia?
- No, she's gone.
- Is there anyone else in the house?
- No.
- Was it you? Let's go.
- Let's go!
- There's no one here.
Stay inside.
Patrol car 27, an ambulance
at 235 Pietro Frattini Street.
We have a woman
who is dead.
Sit down here.
The neighbor saw something.
- Go talk to her.
- I will.
- Down.
- I don't understand.
Don't worry,
we'll explain everything at the police station.
I don't understand...
Sofia? Is that you?
Okay, I'm coming closer, okay?
Come here.
Don't worry, come towards me.
Come on, come on. Put your hands down.
Don't worry... Put them down, come on.
Okay. Come on.
Go.
[man] The lady was
your wife's nurse
and came to assist her
at home, is that right?
[Pietro] Yes.
Did your daughter get along with her
or were there problems, did they argue?
What's wrong, are you feeling unwell?
- It's strange.
- What is?
- She usually answers me.
- Who?
My daughter.
She always answers me.
You have to help me.
Did she have plans tonight?
I don't know, sleep over at a friend's house...
- Does she have a boyfriend?
- Yes, she does.
- Her number?
- Her name?
- Do you have his cell phone number?
- No.
At least his name?
Manuel... Manuel, yes.
YES.
- Inspector, they found the girl.
- My daughter?
- Did you find her?
- She's fine.
- Sit down.
- Stay still.
- No, I want to see her!
- Sit down!
- Stay down!
So we don't get along, huh?
- Okay.
- I'll let you spend the night here.
- Sit down.
- Can I see her later?
- When I decide.
[woman] You have to take everything off,
even your panties.
Come on!
Come on, up.
Good girl.
Turn around.
Come on, on the wall.
Hands.
Lean. Do a squat.
Come on! Have you ever done a squat?
Like at the gym. Up and down, come on.
Good job.
Get up. Up and down. See how good you are?
Come on, get dressed, so we can take you
for a nice photo shoot.
Go on.
Sofia... Sofia. Sofia!
Sofia!
Sofia! Sofia...
I have an appointment with Attorney Statini.
- Good morning.
- Pietro.
I'm sorry.
Come in.
- [Statini] Did they tell you about CPA?
- CPA?
Yes, I don't even know what it is.
It's the reception center.
If they took her there, the prosecutor ordered
her arrest as a precautionary measure.
Why?
We have to wait for
the judge's decision.
What does that mean?
Do they think she did it?
Are they crazy?
We have a colleague here who is really
good with juvenile criminal cases.
I'll call him, okay?
No,
why does it have to be someone else?
I don't deal with minors.
Please, you do it.
Okay.
So...
The judge has a minimum of 96 hours
to decide whether to validate the arrest.
Okay, then what?
I don't know what to tell you right now.
I'll know more tomorrow.
Is that okay?
What are you going to do now? Do you have somewhere to go?
If you want, you can stay with me for a while.
No, thank you. Stefano has
a spare room. I'll go there.
Okay, I'll take you there.
[Katia answering the phone] Yes, lawyer?
Katia, what time is my appointment today?
At 4 p.m. with Mr. Manzi.
- Good morning, lawyer.
- Good morning.
[woman] Those too.
All right, we're done. You can get dressed.
[Pietro] It's like a nightmare.
[Statini] Can you manage on your own?
I'd like to go back to the office and
request access to the files.
[Pietro] Yes.
[Statini] But for anything,
call me, okay?
- Anything, anytime.
- [Pietro] Yes.
[Statini] The news will be out tomorrow.
Avoid going online.
They'll say a lot of nasty things.
It's useless.
You shouldn't read it, it'll only hurt you.
You need to get some rest.
Take one of those.
They're light, really.
Hey...
Take care.
Call me if you need anything.
You need to relax. Is this your first time?
You'll see, somehow
everything will work out.
Would you like some more water?
There are cookies in the room.
Here I am.
I took...
I took the pill
and I'm a little dazed.
I'm not used to it.
No, no, I'm fine.
Why, have you heard something?
They've removed the seals from the house.
If you need anything, I'll take you there.
I don't know when I'll get Chiara's body.
I asked, her sister will take care of it.
I called her.
She didn't seem to want to talk to me.
Hello? Yes, it's me.
She's my daughter, yes.
I don't know, I don't know him.
- I don't watch those programs...
- Give it to me.
I'm her lawyer. Tell me.
How did you get my client's number?
He has no intention of participating
in any program.
Thank you. We will contact
the press ourselves. Have a good day.
Pietro, don't talk to anyone.
If they call you, give them my number.
Why? Maybe it makes sense
for him to talk to us, maybe I have to explain.
What do you have to explain and to whom?
Things are more complicated than that.
Today there will be a hearing
to validate the arrest.
Come on, come up to the studio.
You have to go to the judge
and be clear-headed, you know.
When minors are sent
to the CPA, minors like Sofia,
if there are doubts, they don't do it.
Please, Pietro, you have to listen to me.
I don't understand how you feel,
but you have to listen to me.
Tomorrow the arrest will be validated.
He had Chiara's blood on him.
So? I had blood on me too,
and they didn't do anything to me.
I'm here like an idiot, while she...
Do you realize how crazy this is?
Sofia confessed.
She confessed?
Yes, it was her.
- Tomorrow at the hearing...
- I won't be there.
- You won't be there?
- I won't be there anymore.
Please, you have to listen to me.
Listen to me, please.
Chiara was expecting a baby.
Adequacy, minimal offensiveness,
and destigmatization.
I request that she be placed
in a community.
Sofia, would you like to say anything
about this request?
I'll wait for Dad.
Anything else?
"The judge, having regard to Article 23
448-88, validates the arrest
of the minor Sofia Battisti and taking into account
the principle of residuality
having assessed the seriousness of the facts
and the evidence of guilt,
orders her to be held in custody
at the juvenile detention center
in Rome Casal del Marmo
with immediate transfer order."
They're taking me... They're taking me to prison!
- Please!
- It's only temporary.
Please... call Dad! Please!
I'll request a meeting right away.
Don't worry.
Call Dad!
Please... Please!
[Sofia] Please... call Dad!
- [radio] It took place this morning...
- [man] Car wash €15.
[radio] The hearing involving
17-year-old Sofia Battisti.
The judge has validated the arrest
for manslaughter.
The victim, Chiara Bonelli,
was the partner of Pietro Battisti, the father.
[radio] The murder took place
in the home in the Portuense neighborhood.
The young woman has been transferred
to the Casal del Marmo juvenile detention center.
They're taking her away.
I'm in the car, I can't hear anything.
I can't hear you, please.
- Tell me where you are.
- No, look...
I have to hang up now.
- Stop, stop...
- She asked for you...
Stop it! Stop it!
Profile.
The other one.
Spread your legs, arms forward,
bend over and cough hard.
Good.
Turn around.
Come closer.
Open your mouth.
Raise your tongue.
Lower your head and shake your hair.
Good, you can get dressed.
What should I do?
What do you want to do? Make your bed
and make friends with these.
- When will they give me my phone back?
- They didn't give it to you?
- I'll go ask them now, but come on in.
- Thanks.
Hurry up.
Bro, he was messing with you.
Do you understand that they've put you in jail?
They've put you in jail.
Drina, come here. You tell him,
maybe he'll understand you in Romani.
- This?
- Eh.
They've put you in jail, understand?
Now go and make the bed.
Go on, make it.
- Where is he from?
- I don't know.
As long as he doesn't bother us.
- Floria.
- Want a cigarette?
Oh... Oh!
- What is it?
- Will you be quiet? Go to sleep.
- What did she do?
- She doesn't want to sleep.
Hey, what did you do? Huh?
Be good, let us sleep.
Don't bother us! Oh!
If you wake me up, I'll give you
something to cry about, understand?
Do you understand? Go to sleep.
Don't make me get up.
I'll pull all your hair out if you start again.
Oh, you have to get up.
Get up.
[TV] How cute!
How nice, he waved at me.
Guys, so...
Thanks.
Sofia?
Sofia...
What's wrong?
Come on, get up.
Can you do it?
Come on.
Good girl.
Are you feeling sick?
What's wrong?
Why didn't you go to the cafeteria?
You don't participate in group activities,
you hardly talk to your classmates.
What's going on?
You cry and sleep.
Are you stuck?
This isn't good.
You're always sick.
- Are you going to get a move on? Mm?
- Yes.
The psychologist told me
that the nightmares are continuing.
Is it because you're here?
Since before?
Since when?
- Since Mom died.
- What's wrong, Sofia?
- I don't want to... I don't want to be here.
- What's wrong?
- Please...
- Breathe.
- I want to get out!
- Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay. I'm okay.
- Look at me. Look at me, stay here.
- I want to get out, please.
Breathe with me.
Breathe with me. Good, that's it. Good.
Good, breathe, good.
Good, that's it. Relax.
It's just noise.
Pietro!
- Can we close?
- Yes.
[priest] The road is uphill.
Beyond your mistakes
you must also hope
when the road is very steep.
- You meet many people during the day.
- Yes, the guards every day.
Fabio, come on.
We say “mine,”
the Lord says “ours.”
He loves everyone.
[boy] Oh my God, heaven...
Are you blowing me a kiss?
[man] Come on, guys.
You look down on someone
only to help them up.
- Don't lock the evil inside yourself.
Talk about your pain with the people
who are helping you on this journey.
[Fabio] Remember your panties.
- [man] Quiet, Fabio.
- [priest] You stumbled and fell.
Asking for help is never a sign of weakness.
Let's take the kids to get their food.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, walk. Come on, guys.
Come on.
- Your panties, baby.
- See you later.
- Come on.
- Come on!
You're so beautiful, little one.
My goodness, you're so unpleasant.
You could have sent him a little kiss, couldn't you?
She's a lesbian, she's a lesbian, she's a lesbian.
You like pussy, you could have told me.
Now I'm going to give you a double cut.
I'll cut them like yours.
No.
I'm tired of doing hair
on plastic heads, I'll use yours.
Yours is plastic too.
- Walk, shut up!
Little one!
- I'll be right there.
- How beautiful you are!
- Get the fuck out of here.
- What did you do?
Go! What's wrong with you? Get out of here.
Come on. Come with me.
You're really beautiful.
Come on, let's go. That's it, it's over.
- Really?
- Yeah, really. Let's go.
We're taking the girls back
to the building.
There was a bit of a mess,
we're coming. Come on, let's go.
I saw how you looked at him.
- What the fuck do you want?
- You were eating him up with your eyes.
- What are you talking about?
- Are you fucking with me?
- What the fuck do you want?
- What the fuck do you want!
- Oh, please.
- Shut up, you!
Talk to me, not them.
What the fuck do you want!
Do you understand? I'll kill you!
You have to stay still!
Look, the zipper won't close anymore.
Oh, you're laughing? Look, it's your fault, huh?
Oh my God, I'm going to become a boat.
I love you.
Hey, you. Looking for your stuff?
Go inside, I put it away for you. Go on.
What did you tell the teacher?
Nothing.
What did you go and say?
What did we do to you?
You kill people and you're afraid
of me because I go stealing?
Go! Go, go.
[man on TV] Do you see a pathology
behind this girl's actions?
[woman on TV] I don't see
premeditation, but cruelty
even taking into account
the impetus.
The girl didn't warn anyone,
leaving the woman to die.
What justifications can we
find for this murder?
No psychiatric disorders were detected.
Not to date, but...
They're putting them on trial.
They're all phenomenal when they're on TV,
those pieces of shit.
“He's a monster,” come on!
[woman on TV] I never use
that term, but no half measures.
These kids need
help. They're asking us for it.
[man on TV] Chiara's parents are asking for it too.
They'll mourn her forever.
They will mourn her forever.
I thank Dr. Grimaldi,
and now we go to commercial break.
Eh, commercials. Fuck off!
Pietro, I'm going to Sofia's.
First I'm meeting with the social worker
who's in charge of her. Call me.
Please call me if you want
me to send her a message.
She always asks to see you,
she always asks about you.
Pietro, at his age in prison.
Are the clothes I sent you okay?
- Mm.
- How are you? Are you able to sleep?
The educator called me.
Why aren't you participating in the activities?
It's essential
in order to help you.
They need to see that you're participating.
Would you like to request probation?
Not right away, within a year.
There are possibilities.
You will be placed in the care of social services.
You should go through a long process
with them to make amends
but outside of here.
After three years, if everything goes
as it should,
if you don't do anything stupid,
you'll be free, you understand?
What did he say to you?
In the meantime, anyway...
I'll request your transfer to the community.
I'm sure I'll get it.
I've filed a petition with the court.
You'll just have to talk to the judge.
Have you talked to Dad?
It's not easy for him right now,
but I'm sure
things will work out slowly.
- Do as you wish.
- Dad will come.
No, he's right not to want to see me anymore.
Right now, just focus on the hearing
and what you're going to say to the judge.
If he doesn't care,
I don't care anymore.
Sofia...
What is it?
Oh, Dri', are you asleep?
- What the hell is she doing?
- I don't know, I want to sleep.
Oh! Drina!
She hanged herself!
Oh my God!
Call the assistants! Stay up! Stay up!
What the hell are you doing?
Call the assistants! She hanged herself!
Help! Help, please!
Stay up!
What the hell are you doing?
Don't let go, don't let go!
- Let go, let go!
- Don't let her go! Don't let go!
- How is she?
- Fine now.
- How did it happen?
- A sheet.
- Didn't you have paper ones?
- We switched to regular ones.
- She needs to be kept under observation.
- We need to call her father.
That's where the mess is.
- How is she?
- Fine,
but she's been vomiting and feeling nauseous.
- Why is that?
- I spoke to her,
she said it's been happening a lot lately.
- Do you think...
- I don't know, I'll have her do a beta test.
Probably when she came in
and took the test, it was too early.
Okay, let's check it out.
In the meantime, I'd like to talk to you...
- to understand how to help you.
- Yes, come in.
Here. Yes.
Now a legible signature.
- Anything else?
- Yes, now you have to listen to me.
- The social worker called me.
- Me too, a hundred times.
But you didn't answer.
Sofia isn't well.
- You have to go see her.
- Leave me alone!
My daughter no longer exists for me!
Do you understand? She's gone!
Pietro, Sofia
tried to kill herself last night.
Is she okay now?
“Okay” is a difficult phrase
to use in a prison context.
However, she is better.
She has all the assistance she needs.
- Maybe you could meet her.
- No, I don't want to see her.
Your daughter has a long road ahead of her.
She is currently in protective custody
but in the future, there may be
several possibilities,
such as suspension of the trial,
probation.
It's difficult, but we can work on it.
Sofia will have to come to terms
with what happened
and face up to what she has to do.
It won't be easy,
- she needs you...
- I have to go, excuse me.
That's not true!
- Stay calm.
- That's not true!
- Nothing happened.
- Liars!
Stay still! Calm down, you have to stay still.
- Why are you saying that?
- Be quiet!
- It's not true!
- Nothing happened!
So you're almost three months pregnant.
Yes, I didn't notice anything.
Well, how did you do it at the beginning?
But now you have to make
an important decision.
- I know I shouldn't have it.
Why?
You can have a baby like everyone else,
but you have to be sure.
When...
When they told me,
it felt like a nightmare...
but this makes me think
about what I'll do next.
So anyway, it makes me think about him,
that I'm...
That I'm useful for something, right?
I'm not thinking about myself right now. That's all.
These are positive thoughts,
but it's an important decision
and it's good to talk about it
with the psychologist, okay?
Do you know whose it is?
Do you want to tell him?
Haven't you heard from him?
Okay. Shall we go to the courtyard?
The girls are doing activities.
It looks real. I thought it would be worse.
It's not bad, it's okay.
[man] Sara, come and continue with the stems.
- They turned out well.
- You're kidding me.
No.
This place used to be full of cats.
Now there are a few.
- Good morning.
- Good morning to you.
Do you like animals?
- Yes, I used to ride horses.
- Really?
That's important.
We can link the project
for the trial to horses.
We have to think about it... Oh well.
Listen, but now you have to
do some activities.
Did you see how nice that is?
It's the girls with the volunteer.
He's very good. Do you want to try?
[man] Come on, keep going,
you're doing great.
Mado, this thing stinks.
- Paola, get out of here.
- No, I'm staying.
- Was she born here?
- Yes,
She belongs to the director,
but we all take care of her.
- She also had a litter.
- Really? Here she is!
- [Paola] Have you seen these masterpieces?
- [Sofia] Hi.
[Paola] Who could do
something like this, come on!
- Can I have some?
- Sure, it's delicious.
Hi... Oh my God, she’s beautiful!
Can I take her back to my cell?
I’d say definitely not, but...
you can do something for her if you want.
Really?
Hey...
We have to go to mom now, come on.
Oops...
Doc...
Doc!
We’re done here.
[girl] They still haven’t fixed
the shower? It’s been a month.
Are they afraid we’ll wash too much?
Is it moving?
I don’t... I don’t really understand.
- How many months are you?
- Four and a half.
- Yeah?
You can’t tell whether it’s moving or not?
Oh God, maybe yes, I don’t know.
You’re really an idiot.
- Can I?
- Mm.
- Look here.
- [Sofia] Oh my God...
My God, that’s intense.
How beautiful!
Hi, guys.
You know I’d like that too?
- Really?
I’d like to have a child when I get out of here.
Drina already has two.
Where are they?
Her mother takes care of them, they’re not in here.
You’re not allowed to have
kids in prison.
I really don’t like that.
- Sorry, can you pass me the bathrobe?
- I’ll pass it to you.
Look how much I spoil you.
- Thanks.
- Then don’t say I’m not nice.
Good, I like it.
I like how it’s turning out, I’m happy.
Remember the wood glue...
and to put on the clamps.
What did you name the cat?
- Gray.
- Wow, such imagination!
If you have a girl, will you call her Rosa?
Oh, did you make the kennel yourself?
- Really?
- Yes.
Make me a ladder, will you? At least I can get out of here.
- They won’t let me make one that tall.
- No?
One that reaches the second floor?
I’d be living like a queen in the men’s wing.
Chief, we’re bringing the girls back in
for visitation.
Girls, visitation!
Sofi’, your father’s here too.
Your father is coming in
for the visit, got it?
You’ve got an hour, move it.
- Good morning.
It’s 10:40.
You have one hour.
Thank you.
Hi.
- [Statini] Who is it?
- It’s Pietro. Come down, please.
- What’s wrong, you want to come up?
- No, you come down.
Pietro, what happened?
Why didn’t you tell me?
For a month you’ve been hanging up
when I talk about Sofia.
Why didn’t you tell me she’s pregnant?
She was supposed to tell you.
- We have to take the baby away from her.
- Take it away?
Yes, you have to get custody for me.
There’s no way she can have a child,
she’s not capable.
And you are? You show up like this,
storm into my house and attack me.
Me?
Of course I’m capable.
What did I do, huh?
What did I do?
I know how to be a parent!
I understand everything. We’ve been friends forever,
but on this I can’t follow you.
Sofia has to pay for what she did,
and she is paying,
and she’ll pay for the rest of her life.
Do you think she’ll ever
shake off what she did?
What she did, she did to me!
You can’t understand, you don’t have children.
You’re right.
I don’t understand. I don’t have any.
But I won’t let them take her child away.
I won’t do that.
I’ll request custody for you,
but she has to stay close to him,
otherwise I’ll step down from the case.
Come to my office tomorrow morning.
We’ll see what can be done.
Here, it’s perfect. Beautiful.
With this hairstyle I’ll get you
a full acquittal.
Oh, tell that to the judge.
Sharon Catalucci, hairdresser.
Maybe he’ll reduce my sentence.
Sofia, I’ve read the report
your counselor sent me.
Now it’s your turn.
Are you aware that what you’re asking
is extremely important?
Yes, of course.
[judge] I don’t need to explain
the seriousness of what you did.
What do you want to tell me to convince me
that the people here with you—
the social worker, the lawyer—
are right in saying
that you deserve to move
from prison to a community?
I don’t know.
Even though it’s what I want most,
I can’t go back,
and…
I can’t even apologize to anyone,
because how do you apologize
for what I did?
I’ve had a lot of time to think.
I’ve never thought this much in my life.
Prison changed me.
Anna, my counselor,
changed me, and…
this child
changed me more than anything.
I’d like you to trust me
and allow me to raise him
in a home, not in a cell.
That’s what I want: for him to be okay.
If that’s not possible, then maybe…
maybe my father should take care of him.
That’s all.
All right, Sofia.
Please wait, we’ll retire
to deliberate.
“The court, pursuant to Article 299,
replaces pretrial detention
with placement in a community.
Entrusts Sofia Battisti to the social services
of the Ministry of Justice,
which shall identify a suitable community.
Authorizes transfer to the facility
under escort.”
Sofia, get ready to leave.
Stop by Intake to collect
your personal belongings. Congratulations.
You’re getting out! I’m so happy.
Drina, come here! Sofia’s leaving today.
- She’s leaving!
- My love.
- You’re leaving?
Good for you!
How wonderful! Hi, little one.
I’m happy.
There are girls here with serious problems.
Some are in therapy,
some taken away from their families.
- Are we all together?
- Yes, of course,
but you’re under pretrial supervision.
You’ll have different rules and schedules.
You’ll be able to go back to school,
attend classes.
And soon you’ll be able
to go out sometimes with your father.
This is a huge opportunity.
If you’re granted probation
and you don’t mess up,
in three years you’ll be free
with a clean criminal record.
But if…
If I mess up, do I go back to prison?
Why would you mess up?
We believe in you.
The judge also seemed very confident.
Come on, everything will be fine.
Yes, but you won’t be there.
There’s someone better than me
at the community.
Hey, I’m not abandoning you.
Sofia, you have to go. Do you want to stay here?
Uh…
[woman] Soon you’ll start the project.
Everyone liked it.
Bringing horses together with troubled kids
is a great idea.
You’ll need to follow it closely,
behave well, commit to it fully.
I want them to say that no one like you
has ever been there.
Remember…
Hold the reins.
Good, with both hands.
- You’ve gotten really good.
- Thank you, Sofia.
Go on, go on.
Let’s do another lap. Want to?
- Okay.
- Can I touch her?
- Yes.
- Does it bother you?
- Go on, go ahead!
She’s grown so much!
How much longer?
Not much, about a month.
- Will you keep coming here?
- Of course, I’ll bring him too.
Maria, come here!
I have to go, I have to go!
See you Wednesday.
Bye!
- Wait, go.
- Go on, there—oh!
[woman] You took the girl away from her family
to keep her here,
with crazies on medication,
ex-prostitutes, and a murderer!
- What’s going on, Carolina?
- My mother is crazy.
- You’re brainwashing her!
- Calm down, ma’am.
- I will not calm down!
- Request a revocation of the measure.
- I’ll report you!
- We were calm
- and I mentioned you.
- I’m taking her home!
- Do as you wish.
- I’m going to file a complaint…
- Watch your tone.
- …because you’re crazy and incompetent!
- You don’t know who I am.
- I don’t care.
- I’ll report you!
- Learn to listen.
Do whatever you want,
but let us do our work.
Goodbye, ma’am. Excuse me.
- Don’t worry, nothing happened.
- They should give *her* the medication.
Come on. Marta, you come too, let’s go.
- I’m going, see you later.
- Yes.
Here you go, hot and fresh.
What’s wrong with her? Why isn’t she eating?
She’s… she’s upset.
She had a breakdown
and they put her back on medication.
Today she went after Livia.
She scratched her all over.
- She won’t last long.
- How dare you?
- Mind your own business!
- Enough!
- Look at the state you’re in.
- What the fuck do you want?!
I’m sick of your shit!
Enough… enough!
Girls, what’s going on?
You pissed her off, you idiot!
- What’s going on here?
- You’re a piece of shit!
- Shut up!
- Girls!
- What’s going on?
- Nothing.
- Nothing’s going on.
- What’s going on is that she never shuts up.
Come on, try to sort it out.
Sofia, are you ready?
- Hurry up, you’ve got the ultrasound.
- Will you come with me?
No, they gave permission to your dad.
He’s taking you today.
Girls, relax. See you later.
Thank you.
Dad.
Sweetheart… good afternoon.
Thanks.
Hi.
How are you?
Fine. Fine…
- How is it there? Are you settling in?
- Fine, fine, yes.
- Let’s go.
[doctor] You’re going to feel a bit of cold now.
Now I’ll poke him a little.
He’s moving a lot.
There we go.
So, did they tell you the sex?
No. Can you already tell?
- Of course, she’ll be born in a month.
- What is it?
It’s a… it’s a beautiful baby girl.
[Sofia] Oh my God…
- Do you know when she’s due?
Based on the last menstrual cycle,
around October 20th or 22nd.
- Okay.
- [Pietro] Like Chiara.
- Like who?
- No… no, nothing.
What’s wrong? Are you feeling unwell?
No, just a little…
A little dizzy.
I’ll wait outside.
Are you worried?
No.
You don’t have to be scared, okay?
Babies are simple when they’re little.
You feed them, bathe them,
sing them a song,
and they’re happy.
I used to do that with you too.
You’ll see, you’ll be a good mother.
- Dad.
- Yes?
Earlier you mentioned Chiara.
No.
What time do you have to be back at the facility?
Soon.
[TV] Damn it.
I think I’ll never have one.
- Are you sad?
- No.
Marta? Come on.
Go help Livia unload the groceries.
She can’t do it alone.
I love you very much.
[Marta] Girls, come help me with the groceries?
Come on, Sofia’s tired.
- [man] Heating?
- It’s independent.
Here’s the control unit,
but it can also be operated remotely.
- Condo fees?
- Average, about 120 euros.
Air conditioning in every room,
and here we have this beauty.
There you go.
Southeast exposure, swimming pool, daycare,
and behind us is one
of the biggest parks in Rome.
Perfect for a child.
We should make a substitution next time,
otherwise they never win.
Do you feel like grabbing something
at the bar with Stefano?
Yes!
I don’t want to ask for custody anymore.
- What do you mean?
- She has to stay with Sofia.
What can I say, I’m happy.
It’s the best thing.
The other day I saw an apartment and…
I thought it would be perfect.
They could live there with me as soon as…
As soon as she’s granted probation.
So I can go ahead with the request? Are you sure?
I’m not sure of anything anymore,
but she’s my daughter and…
she’s expecting a baby.
What else can I do?
Livia! Livia!
- What’s happening?
- Livia…
- Yes, tell me.
- Sofia is having nightmares again!
- I can’t do it! Please, come!
- Let’s go. Stay calm.
- Help!
- Why are you screaming?
Stop it! I want to sleep.
- Stop it!
- No!
Help! I can’t do it…
- I can’t do it.
- Everything’s fine.
Do what we told you.
Oh God, she’s slipping… she’s slipping!
I can see the head. Do you want to feel it?
It burns!
Come on, now you have to push, Sofi’.
Come on, take a deep breath.
- Come on, just a little more. Push, Sofia.
- It burns!
There she is. Push!
There she is! There she is!
Oh God…
There she is!
Push again,
you need to expel the placenta.
Good job, Sofia.
Congratulations, she really is a beautiful baby,
truly beautiful.
Thank you.
My baby girl.
- Good morning.
- I’m Sofia Battisti’s father…
- Ah, Sofia, yes.
She’s being discharged.
Do I need to sign anything since she’s a minor?
No, there’s no need, don’t worry.
And in any case, Sofia has chosen
to stay another 24 hours.
- We informed the community.
- Oh.
- Is there a problem?
- No.
The younger ones often do it to learn.
We show them how to change her,
how to feed her, things like that.
- Ah, okay. Can I see her?
- Of course. You know where she is?
- Yes, thank you.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Yeah, I understand.
Don’t worry, it’s nothing.
Hi.
- Hi.
- How are you?
Fine.
I brought these for you.
I’ll leave them here.
The nurse told me that…
That you want to stay
one more day in the hospital.
Everything okay? I can help you
with the baby if…
Where
is she?
She’s in the nursery.
- I’ll go get her.
- No.
I need to take care of my baby myself.
Of course… of course, obviously.
I just wanted to…
Listen…
It was supposed to be a surprise, but…
I got an apartment
near a nice park, for the three of us.
So you can keep studying and…
maybe go out with your friends.
- I’ll take care of the baby.
- No.
Chiara’s nausea
wasn’t the flu, was it?
That day at the gynecologist…
What?
Was Chiara expecting a baby?
Yes.
You’ll always think about it,
because I did something that…
I did something only a monster would do,
and if I stayed with you, I’d always be one.
- No.
- That’s not true. That’s not true.
- Yes.
Before, yes, before it was like that.
You’re right, but…
Everything has changed.
I’d do anything
for our baby girl.
She’s not ours, she’s mine.
Of course. Yes, she’s your daughter.
What should I do?
Tell me and I’ll… I’ll do it.
You have to leave, Dad.
Please.
She and I will grow up on our own and…
I have to do it this way, please.
Dad…
I need to ask you one more thing.
Tell me.
[Statini] Of course, I’ll speak to the head physician
and let you know.
- All right.
- Goodbye.
Here comes Grandpa!
I’ve got some good news for you.
Within a year the judge might
approve probation,
so Sofia and the baby
could come live with you.
No, sorry, I can’t…
I’ve changed my mind.
- I don’t understand.
- I can’t do it, I can’t…
I really can’t. I don’t want
to take care of Sofia and the baby.
- So?
- I talked to her and she understood, so…
I think it’s the best thing.
She’ll spend the next few years in the community,
- All right.
- With her daughter.
- With Rosa.
- Her name is Rosa.
Yes.
- It’s a beautiful name.
- Yes.
Sorry, I have to go.
[Pietro] After every disaster,
life presents itself again and starts over,
and that’s what you’re looking for, my daughter.
Every wound heals,
mine will heal too,
and if a day comes
when you need something,
or you want to fall asleep
under the gaze of someone who loves you,
know that I will never stop waiting for you.
A child must stop being a child one day,
but a parent can never stop
being a parent.
Whatever happens.