Liz?
Yes, Doctor?
Run the scan on Alpha and Genesis.
I need the safety analysis.
Scanning now.
Scan complete.
Safety percentage 82.7%.
That'll have to do.
Prepare the trial.
I don't think
that's a good idea, Doctor.
Prepare the trial, Liz.
Yes, Doctor.
Preparing trials now.
Are you ready? Kayla?
Yes. Dr. Jane?
The mouthpiece.
This might hurt a bit.
Initiate the program.
Lights.
Amp up the dosage.
The dosage.
No, we're hurting him.
Who do you think you're talking to?
Amp up the dosage or you lose your job.
Now!
Dr. Jane, we need to stop.
Can't you see? He's in pain.
Shut it!
Stop it. Stop it now.
♪ To me it's all night for you ♪
♪ Say it, put out the vibes ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ Money will talk,
got it all right for you ♪
♪ Got me on my back, yeah ♪
♪ Got on my hands, yeah ♪
♪ All I do is, all I do
is, all I do is, all I do is ♪
♪ All I do is dream of you ♪
♪ Ooh yeah, love you,
love you, tell me, baby ♪
♪ Make that heart beat fast ♪
Baby!
Oh my God.
When did you get here?
Why didn't you tell me?
I missed you.
I almost don't recognize this face.
I miss you.
Let me look.
Somebody gained some weight back there.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
Scott gains baby.
I got a new PT and she's a beast.
Yeah, I'm
not complaining at all.
Okay, come on, let me down.
I dunno what I'm gonna do with you.
Hey?
Hey.
I really missed you.
Me too.
You missed you too?
I mean, I wish you would've
warned me you were coming home.
You know, I would've done
something special like shower.
I'm here. I really miss you.
Thought about you every day.
What'd you think about?
Well, you wanna show me?
♪ So let me change your
mind about your situation ♪
♪ Forget your ovulation ♪
♪ Like some altercation ♪
♪ Let me go and make some ♪
♪ Never touch your patience ♪
♪ Make something out nothing ♪
♪ You a home magician and that ain't okay ♪
♪ And now you got toxic traits ♪
♪ But at the end of every day ♪
Hey, what's this?
It's just a scratch from work.
Oh, it's just a scratch from work.
Baby, you're a black cops.
A scratch can be anything.
Look, it's nothing serious.
Just a nick for blood.
Nothing serious.
What? You don't believe me?
Should I?
I mean, you never let me in that world.
Yeah, because I don't want you to worry.
I love you. I'll always worry.
I know.
So...
Is there anything you wanna tell me yet?
Oh shit.
It's Imani.
- I gotta take this, baby.
- Really?
Okay, I need
your help with something.
- Is this Vicky...
- Imani.
Hey look who is here.
Hey Terrance. Hi.
- Hey, Imani.
- What?
Look, by the way, you
have impeccable timing.
Who me?
Oh wait, why?
Did I interrupt something?
- No.
- Yes.
Stop it.
- So, hey, come here.
- Girl, you're fine.
- What's up?
- Be nice.
- Oh, babe.
- Oh snap.
- TJ.
- What up? What up, boy?
What's up my boy? You back, huh?
- Yeah.
- Hi Chris.
What's up with your face, man?
Why the look?
I may be quite possibly
may have interrupted them.
- Yes, exactly.
- Oh.
You interrupted the man.
- We, no.
- Yes.
- We weren't even that far in.
- Yes, you did.
Stop.
She did.
Close enough.
No.
Yeah. Actually, let me take
the phone away from you.
I'll be sure to call y'all
next time y'all in the bed.
I just threw up.
Threw up what?
Some sort of acid I think.
How are you feeling?
I had stomach pains at
first, but I'm better now.
Just thought it best I call you.
Your body is just
purging post the procedure.
So that means it's working.
We wouldn't have sent you
home if we had any concerns.
That's reassuring.
That being said, you
remember the package I gave you?
Can you grab it for me.
Got it.
Open it.
What is this stuff?
It's a new organic drink
that hasn't hit the market yet.
It contains all the ingredients
needed to combat any negative side effects
you might experience while you're at home.
You should have one a week
or more if you're not feeling well.
It's like a coffee replacement.
I don't even drink coffee, Doc.
You know, you were the first soldier
to ever receive the GFT
chemical enhancement.
So I know it can be scary,
but our trials were a huge success.
You have nothing to worry about.
As long as you stay on top of your meds,
drink plenty of water,
and most importantly,
stay away from alcohol.
After 30 days your body will be acclimated
and you can have yourself a drink.
But there's always mush rush.
If you start to get in your head at all.
Just think about the
advantages you'll have in combat.
You'll be faster, stronger,
invincible,
guaranteeing your safe
return from every tour.
When you make it through this,
your family will be set for life,
and think about what you can provide
for your soon to be wife, your future kids.
I really appreciate you, Doc.
You know, if your father was still alive,
he would be very proud of you.
You're right.
I just wanted to make sure
it was safe for me to be around Alice, so.
I know I don't have to remind you
that what we are doing here is classified.
You are under restriction.
I know. I signed the paperwork, Doc.
Now did I know what I was signing?
Maybe, maybe not.
Nobody does.
Yeah.
Also, I just pulled up to the pharmacy.
So I'll text you the location.
Prepare the holding room.
Yes ma'am.
I got him, I got him.
I spoke to Dr. James.
He's ready to send in test patient 04.
Hold him tight.
Got him. Got him.
Are you even trying?
Take this to Dr. Thomas.
Yes ma'am.
Here you go, Doctor.
Stand back and take notes.
Of course.
Whoa, it's too bad you're strapped down.
Whatcha doing?
Talking to my girls.
What y'all talking about?
Just girl stuff.
But we need to talk.
I thought we were talking.
Oh my God, I'm being serious.
Really, we need to talk.
I'm sorry, baby. Okay,
what's up? Talk to me.
I want a ring.
I'm sorry. What?
That kind of talk.
Baby, we talked about this.
I know, but I really
want to be engaged, daddy.
Don't, don't do that.
Baby stop.
What? You don't like it, daddy?
Daddy?
I don't...
I do like it.
I just don't like, I mean I do but I don't.
So what are you gonna do, daddy?
Daddy's gonna get the ring.
Exactly.
- Yo.
- What up, man?
Hey man, I'm
here for the, the special.
Alright? Yeah, yeah. Gimme
a second. Lemme grab D.
Yo, D!
Come here.
Y'all getting on my nerves.
This guy wants to buy your product.
You trust that white boy?
I mean my pockets do.
Besides he's already paid.
Whatever.
Just make sure I get my cut.
We're in the middle of nowhere
and they didn't even have roasted Doritos
at this gas station.
Like what does this country become?
You look so cute.
Ain't nobody watching.
- Shut up.
- Who asked you?
Take it easy.
It's okay, guys, just ignore him.
Let's go.
All right, ladies first.
All right finally.
I'm riding shotgun.
God. Thank you.
You're welcome.
This place is beautiful.
Here's your last bag, sir.
- Thank you. Thank you, man.
- Alright.
- Hey, say hi.
- What up? What up? What up?
Description is insane.
- Oh my God.
- Hey.
I'm so sorry.
You're so cute. I'm sorry.
Gimme, gimme, gimme.
Okay, got this. You good?
- Okay, good.
- Okay.
This place is so nice.
It's nice.
Babe, oh, we're definitely
getting the master bedroom.
What?
Why you looking at me like that?
'Cause you're beautiful.
Boy, can you help me up, sir?
Ooh, you're strong.
Do you think we could live here?
Yeah, I
mean this is really nice.
♪ How many more times
do I have to tell you ♪
♪ She's with me and I
love her like she is, baby ♪
♪ And I don't ever want
to lose control over you ♪
♪ And I don't ever wanna lose you ♪
♪ So I gotta do right for you, baby ♪
♪ I'm gonna sing it till my heart says ♪
♪ Yes, you know that ♪
♪ You know that every time
I do this shit for you, baby ♪
♪ I do it off of me and you ♪
♪ You know all of the struggles ♪
♪ And pain we gone through together ♪
♪ But we still come through
and they won't ever love ♪
♪ No, they won't ever love me like I do ♪
♪ Like you do ♪
♪ Baby, it's just me and
you till the world falls apart ♪
♪ She's with me ♪
Fuck.
Really?
I'm gonna kill this nigga.
Oh shit.
- Why is your phone phone ringing?
- I dunno.
Why your phoning?
Who is this calling you?
Oh.
Hey girly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm coming down.
Okay, see you.
I'm gonna break that damn phone.
You might wanna hold back 'cause...
Yeah.
This is bullshit.
You made it.
Oh my God, there's a hot tub.
Alright, let's go, let's go.
Right down.
Let me take off my skirt.
Yo.
Get some the bell boy in
this motherfucking place.
God damn.
Damn.
Stupid ass fucking bags.
Why the fuck you got all these bags?
It's three days.
Yo.
What's up, man?
What's up man? I got you.
What's going...
Oh God damn.
What's up, man?
Put some muscle on you, ain't you?
Shit, not much. It's like 20, 30 pounds.
You just gonna say like that ain't a lot.
I mean I told you to come train with me.
Just be pulling your back out and shit.
Nigga, stop playing.
Ain't that God damn old.
I blow backs out all the time.
You know what I'm saying?
I blow Imani back out every night.
Yeah, man.
I been throwing backs out since I was 13.
Get your ass...
Let me help you with these bags.
You gonna have some fun.
Well come, here muscle
man, grab that shit too.
Get that shit.
So you just going to pick
it like it don't weigh shit.
Don't do that. Don't do that to me.
Don't do that to me.
This right here weighs more than all that.
Yeah, so how was the trip?
It was good, uneventful.
But I have something to tell you.
Mm, with C?
Yeah, so I maybe possibly
might have invited some friends.
Imani, what are some?
Just like two or three.
Four, five. Five.
Imani, that's a lot.
I know, but I, we need
more people to drink.
Have fun. Make it a party.
We are still young, Ali, remember that?
Are they cool?
Mad, cool. Promise.
Okay, well you have to tell, TJ.
So I was also thinking
that maybe you could tell him
and kind of...
Imani,
I know you do not pit
me up with your a plan.
I did. I did.
But my plan your man.
What? It's fine.
Look, we'll worry about it later
because they're not
gonna make it too obvious.
What's up, ladies?
Whatcha all talking about?
Nothing. Just girl stuff.
Oh shit.
Get it.
Atrocious. Just fucking ridiculous.
What y'all wanna do tonight?
We need to play
spades. You already don't.
Damn, why do y'all
always wanna play spades?
What the fuck? What?
I mean, come on.
See, we literally at a lake house, man.
- Honestly...
- Motherfucking talk then.
- Shit, what y'all know about that?
- No one knows anything about that.
Wait, who talked? Who? Who? Who's she?
The fucking dinosaur.
Shut your ass up, you
fake ass Sade looking ass.
That's better than a dinosaur.
You too over there, Griselda Blanco.
Come around, find out.
- Now...
- Don't come for her.
Like I said, what's up with these spades?
First, first of all, if we was playing top,
TJ already know what it is.
Tell, tell 'em.
That was the game that
we played during deployment.
You retired for a reason, bro.
Oh wow.
Babe, tell him, tell him
why you retired again?
Yeah, tell us, C.
Y'all making jokes but it's not funny.
- Let the people laugh.
- All right.
Listen to this.
Because one of my arms
is shorter than the other.
How? Wait, how? How's that possible?
The fuck.
- You okay?
- Show him.
All right.
Well stop laughing then. It's not funny.
Be nice, his feelings are vulnerable.
Sit your arms down.
I should not. I should not.
Stupid.
That's your man. That's your man.
Working for the gov.
- Put that shoulder down.
- That shit worked for me though.
I bet it did.
- You a fool. You know that?
- Whatever.
- He's not joking.
- It's not.
And one of my hands is
shorter than the other too.
Honestly, throw the whole guy away.
Yeah, see.
Yeah, that's what
I'm talking about, baby.
Shit, back to these spades.
Oh my God.
Like I said, there is
no way on this earth
at this fucking lake house
we're gonna play spades.
Bang!
Ha! Give me that book.
Get it here. Yes. Oh baby.
Shit, I'm booking so many books,
you should call me booking.com.
Mwah. Mwah.
Yeah, that's my little
good luck charm right there.
- I need a drink.
- I suck at that.
You sure you haven't been prison?
That is crazy. You just give up.
Don't know.
Yeah, you damn right I won.
Babe, you won. Come drink.
That's what I'm talking about.
What you drink, baby?
Oh, I can't this week.
The fuck you mean you can't?
Stop fucking with me.
Come on, what you drinking?
No, I'm serious. Like I, I can't.
I'll talk to you about it later.
- For real?
- Yeah, man.
You got it though, big dog.
It's gonna be a long fucking weekend.
Got that water.
- Which one?
- The one with the low milk?
Man, stop playing.
- Cheers.
- Cheers to that.
- Cheers to my ring.
Get your ass outta here.
Yeah, that's bad luck, babe.
Spanking me like I'm your child.
Sit down, son, sit down.
I mean, you know, I do get
called daddy a lot so it's okay.
It's okay.
- This is strong.
- Excuse me.
You gonna let him say that to you, babe?
You gonna let him do that?
- I thought that was what she was.
- We can fight.
She boxes, son. She'll box you up
Baby, it's...
- I'm a diplomatic.
- She's just a girl.
- I'm a diplomatic?
- Just a gal.
She got papers. What she do?
Alright, here we go.
All right, Fuck, marry, kill.
- Okay.
- Hmm.
Fuck, marry, kill.
Come on.
Biden.
Simon Cowell.
Don't know who that is.
The American Idol, dog.
Oh, okay, okay, okay,
okay. Okay. Third person?
Justin Bieber.
I'll fuck Justin Bieber, duh.
Definitely fucking Justin Bieber.
Sorry, babe.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Who is that?
Was that the door?
Baby, go open the door.
What you mean?
Don't you see this motherfucker right here?
Why would I go get the
door? Go get the door, man.
Why?
So you can put them 40 pounds to use.
Babe, stop, someone's knocking.
It's people.
People?
Imani invited some friends.
Cool friends,
Cool friends, babe.
- Cool friends.
- Sorry.
- Imani!
- Bitch.
Literally in the middle
of nowhere. I saw a deer.
Say what? You guys hit a deer.
Hello, Kitty,
you guys look so cute.
What's up, G?
What's up, big man?
Okay, not a big talker.
What's up, Imani?
- How are you?
- Hi Brock.
- So good to see you.
- You too.
Thank you for inviting us again.
- This is Fire.
- Hi, I'm Brock.
Guys, isn't this house so pretty?
Look at all the snacks and all the drinks.
Gonna be here for a
weekend party. Live it up.
Don't be jealous.
Damn, you must be TJ.
Yeah, you are?
- Mia.
- Alice.
TJ's, fiance
Oh my God. Hey girl.
Yes, I heard so much about you.
Oh, I see you guys have met.
- Getting to know each other.
- So much.
Great. Okay, I want
you to meet Chris, so.
You must say TJ. Ah. Ah.
Please stop.
Fucking Gen Zers.
It's okay, babe. It's
okay, don't kill her.
Hold me back because I will kill her.
I know. I know.
♪ All out hustling ♪
♪ Me and my buddies ♪
♪ Who getting money yet ♪
♪ Me and my buddies. ♪
♪ Who out here tripping yet ♪
♪ Me and my buddies, me and my buddies ♪
♪ Who out hustling ♪
♪ Me and my buddies ♪
♪ Who getting money yet ♪
♪ Who out here tripping yet ♪
♪ Me and my buddies, me and my buddies. ♪
♪ Remember late nights just children ♪
♪ Smoking on the block ♪
♪ Just chilling, reminiscing ♪
♪ Missing that feeling ♪
♪ Free styling them sessions was healing ♪
♪ Talking about bitches ♪
♪ Revealing pictures of titties
and talking about making ♪
♪ Everybody knew we was
them niggas always focused ♪
♪ Real gold diggers, yeah ♪
♪ All about the money broke niggas ♪
♪ Started looking funny ♪
♪ Stacking, all my bitches love me ♪
♪ Laughing like - ♪
Baby, come dance with us.
I'm gonna get some
drink and be right back.
Mm. Okay.
♪ Somewhere in the cuddy ♪
♪ Got caught in the
classroom getting cuddy ♪
♪ Lean, yeah, yeah, the cups is muddy ♪
♪ The niggas get me, get
my buddies, we concrete ♪
♪ They built they walls with putty ♪
♪ They know our future looking sunny ♪
♪ Who out hustling ♪
♪ Me and my buddies ♪
♪ Who getting money yet ♪
♪ Me and my buddies. ♪
♪ Who out here tripping yet ♪
♪ Me and my buddies, me and my buddies ♪
♪ Me and my buddies
getting their money yet ♪
♪ Me and my buddies getting them baby ♪
♪ Me and my buddies getting them ♪
♪ Me and my buddies, me and
my buddies, me and my buddies ♪
- And you weren't there.
- Yeah, you weren't there.
Imani.
I'm sorry.
Pour me another a drink.
Wait, did you bring the Bacardi 151?
Yeah, shit's nasty.
Yeah, it's nasty, it's nasty.
But it gets you fucked
up. And that's the point.
Listen, I can make that
shit taste like straight juice.
No way, Not Bacardi
151. That's pure jet fuel.
Girl, watch me.
Show them. Show them
Not strong for me.
Mia can handle it.
Gotcha.
Fuck. Fuck.
Fuckedy fuck.
Eeny, meeny...
Fuck it.
Tastes like juice to me.
There you go.
Ooh.
Damn, Soph, this shit is delicious.
Bitch.
Fucking blueberries.
I told you.
Boy, whatever that military got you on,
I need to get on that shit.
You know what I'm
saying? Hold up, swollen up.
Look at your arms, man.
Them shit's as big as my thigh. Pause.
It's the same shit you used to do, man.
So I heard...
I heard rumors.
You know, that they, they doing experiments
and shit, you know?
Yeah, you know, trying to create
like some sort of super
soldier or some shit.
So what's up?
What you talking about, man?
I mean,
I wish they would.
I'd probably be the first one to sign up.
Shit, I'd signed for
that shit in the heartbeat.
You know what I'm saying?
Get some like super
enhanced eyesight or some shit.
'Cause these, these, these seeing glasses
fucking up your boy's swag.
You become a super soldier,
and the first thing you think about
is prescription eyeballs?
What the fuck?
Fuck you, TJ.
How's that?
Fuck you.
No, no, just fuck and you.
You know what I mean?
I'm just saying. But look,
I, I get your point. I do.
- I get your point.
- Alright.
So what's up?
Is it true?
It's rumors, Chris.
Just rumors.
I'm gonna get my juice.
Mm. Okay.
All right, I'm just saying.
I'm gonna get more than some eyesight.
Yeah.
Super dick.
Fuck yeah, you know what I'm saying?
Just fly around, just
dicking 'em down and shit.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, just swing that
motherfucker like a bat.
Just be fucking up
motherfuckers with my dick.
Like pow.
That's the party.
You wanna taste it?
Here drink some.
- No, no, I'm good.
- "No, no, I'm good." - Just one sip.
You fucking party pooper.
Sure. Sure.
- Did she put her mouth on it?
- Yes she did.
It's mine.
Nevermind.
Not just have one sip. It's really good.
Too bad.
Here, you can have more, though.
Thanks.
No, let her drink some.
It's okay. Here, take one sip.
It's really good. Just try it.
Sip it. Sip it, Sip it. Sip it.
Don't worry,
it's not like I put sugar
or something in there.
Come on, grandma.
- Yeah.
- Good, right?
- It's good.
- Yeah, drink some more.
Doctor, we need help.
The soldiers are
Jane, don't.
Code blue. Get in here now. Code blue.
Victor.
See, I'm a bad man.
Scared me.
So how you been?
I've been good. You know me.
Yeah.
I'm always good.
- Hey.
It's good. What you doing baby, girl?
Making us a drink, daddy.
Thank you, baby.
- Enjoy.
- Mm.
Damn, it sure look good, don't it.
- Right.
- Hm mm.
That was fucking rhetorical.
I'm gonna go back to a party.
You do that.
Vic, you're not gonna be a little bitch
and chicken out tonight, are you?
Fuck you.
Gimme that shit, fool.
Oh, okay.
Bro, yo,
how do you even know if
that shit's like good, man?
What if that shit's laced?
Do you trust your dealer?
Fuck it, I'll test it right now, fool.
Oh shit.
This shit is good.
Fuck yeah.
You you want some?
No, I'm good, I'm pretty tired.
Oh, you're a pussy.
Fuck man.
Oh, you going for a sec? Oh.
- Hot tub. Hot tub.
- Hot tub. Hot tub. Hot tub.
Hot tub. Hot tub. Hot
tub. Hot tub. Hot tub.
Fool.
That not for the hot tub.
That's a hot water string
for the whole house.
The blue one is cold water.
Whichever one you fuck with
turns out that temperature
for the entire house.
Bro, how do you know this, man?
I'm Mexican, not mommy's way.
- Alright man.
- Whoa!
It's good, man.
Yeah.
Whoa!
You gonna get in?
I think I should go and check on TJ.
Boo, We just got started.
But what if it was you that
was sick and I had to help?
Well that's different.
I scratch your back,
you scratch mine, right?
Yeah, you're funny.
But I get it, go do
what you gotta do, wifey.
Is Chris okay with Victor being here?
Yeah, of course. Why wouldn't he be?
I don't know, 'cause you guys, you know?
Oh my God. Yeah, sure.
But that was like decades ago.
Plus he's my childhood
friend and he was my first love.
But we're just friends now, so it's cool.
Okay, cool.
Love it.
All right, girl, go get your man.
We'll be here.
I have rum
- Don't fall.
- It's not that deep.
Wanna play a game?
What's the game?
Yeah, let's play a game.
- Never have I ever.
- Oh yeah.
Okay.
Fuck man.
I'm tripping.
Yo, bro, bro, bro, you good?
Yo bro, you good, bro?
Yo, chill.
What the fuck?
You good?
Bro, you good?
Chill, man.
Fuck.
Geez, man, you good?
Yeah, I'm good, G.
Hey yo, man, I think
you need to lay off that coke.
What you tell him, fool?
I don't know what the fuck I was thinking
messing up with fool.
Oh. Oh, whoa bro, I'm
gonna need you to back up.
I need you to brush your teeth before you
My bad, G, my bad, my bad.
Lemme brush up and
I'll be right back, all right?
I got you.
- I'll see you upstairs, man.
- See you, bro.
- Hey, babe?
- Yeah?
You like your egg sunny side up, right?
Yeah, you know how I like it, daddy.
Daddy? I'm your papi.
Mia, you want some coffee?
I don't drink coffee, Kai.
I'll take some.
Bro, you doing too much?
What's up, Alice A? You hungry?
Nah, I'll get something
later. Have you seen TJ?
Uh uh, I thought he was with you.
Thank you.
Do you want some juice or something?
No.
What's up, girl?
Name's Alice.
Damn, Alice, why are you so hostile?
Just trying to see what's up, Pena.
Look, I don't know
what your angle is, but I
I don't have an angle, I'm just trying
Yeah, you're just
a little too close to me.
I'm just trying to get to know you.
Is that okay?
Oh, hey.
Morning, baby.
Morning.
Can I help you?
Oh, what do you mean?
I, I was just having a conversation.
Yeah.
So talk.
I mean, it's kind of awkward now.
Why?
Because Alice and I were
having a one-on-one conversation.
I think you were talking to yourself.
Don't be a bitch about
Apologize.
For what, man?
- Say it.
- Let me go!
Just apologize, motherfucker.
He not gonna let you go until you do.
- Brock say, "I'm sorry."
- Bro, let him go.
What you want? You want some?
Because you could be next.
Okay. I'm, I'm Sorry.
I'm, I'm sorry.
You good, bro.
Get the off me, Vic! Huh?
Fucking Walmart Channing
Tatum looking ass motherfucker.
That nigga got some nerves.
Hey TJ, you good?
Better be glad your boy left when he did.
Yeah, I was about to get in that ass.
You know what I mean?
You motherfuckers, you young bucks,
y'all gonna get tired
of trying to talk to other people's women.
Yeah, see, it seems like you,
you don't know what a ass whooping is.
Yeah.
Seems like you suffer from FAFO.
Fuck around and find out.
You better ask somebody.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, he'll behave now.
I mean, it was kind of hot.
Tired, aggressive, sure.
But very, very hot.
Yeah, salty.
I'm gonna go change, okay?
Okay, I'm gonna grab some coffee.
- Okay.
Anybody want some coffee?
Me. Extra cream and sugar, please.
- Thank you.
- There you go.
Imani, there's a lake.
Stop. Let me see.
- Yeah.
- Let me see.
Look.
This is so pretty. We should go.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, let's go right now.
- Babe?
- Hmm?
There's a lake. Can we go
Where? How far is it?
- Half a mile.
- Seven minutes.
Girl, let's do it.
You have a two?
- I have the cutest swimsuit with me.
- So do I. - You gonna freak out.
Let's compare.
Bro, you need to calm down, man.
Don't tell me to fucking calm down, bro.
Relax bro. Relax.
What are you gonna do?
You gonna fight me now next.
I should. I should.
- You didn't do shit.
- Why? Why?
I didn't do shit?
You were fucking groping
all up on that girl, bro.
She has man.
What the fuck were
you expecting to happen?
I get what the fuck I want, Kai!
Apparently not. So.
What the fuck did you just say to me?
Bro, you need to calm the fuck down, bro.
You need to step off them
fucking blow that you're taking.
You really wanna fight somebody.
Go fucking fight, dude.
Your bitches just got chucked the fuck out.
For real
I got something for him.
What you got, homie?
Yo, check me.
Let me talk to you about something.
What's up?
I might have a business proposition.
- Nah, nah.
- No, come on. Come on. Don't do
First of all, why you say it like that?
Because the last time you said that,
it started with, "I need."
It ended with, "some money."
Yo, don't disrespect
me like that, don't do that.
Come on now, you know me better than that.
Come on.
You right. My bad.
What's up?
I might
kinda sorta need an investment.
Now, now notice how I said kinda and sorta.
So basically your ass needs some money.
Nig, first of all, again
with the fucking disrespect.
Why you, how you gonna
play me? I don't need shit.
Me personally, no.
The business needs the investment.
I'm, I'm gonna say this
in the nicest way possible.
Hell to the fuck no.
That was nice?
Yes, nigga.
What happened to the
other money I gave you?
I mean, I'm almost in the black.
You was in the black a year ago,
and then two years
ago you was in the black.
By now, nigga, you should be in the purple.
Michael, black in their
ass black, stand in the dark,
close your motherfucking eyes,
ain't nobody see your black, nigga.
But here we go, asking me for
another stupid-ass investment.
First of all, it ain't stupid.
Second of all, it fucking worked.
- How, nigga?
- Because it's planted, motherfucker.
Planted where?
The weed, motherfucker.
The shit don't grow overnight.
Nigga, it don't take two years either.
See, see that's your fucking problem.
Nigga, you my problem.
You and these stupid-ass investments.
Ain't gonna be stupid
when you making some money.
Huh.
How about that?
Talk to me when you making
us some motherfucking money.
Now let that sink.
- All right, nig.
- Yeah, all right, nigga.
- All right, nigga.
- All right, whatever, nig.
- Whatever then. God damn.
- Yeah, whatever.
Hey babe. What's up?
Is TJ okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- He, he, you know, he still pissed off
about what happened with home boy earlier.
Didn't have shit to do with me.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Well, you wanna get ready to go?
Yeah, yeah, I just gotta finish up this.
I'll be right there.
What the fuck?
- Bro, what are you doing?
- Yeah.
Where did you even get that?
Homie at the gas station sold it to me.
What the fuck for?
Why would you even
buy something like that?
We are at the lake. We not hunting deer.
That is not cool, bro.
Let him sneak me like that again.
We'll see what happens.
Bro, please point that away.
Put that away before you
shoot us or shoot yourself.
I'm not a fucking idiot!
Bro
Vic, I know how to
use one of these pieces.
Homie, can you at least hide it for now?
So at least the girls don't see it.
You want me to put the gun away?
Hide it, bro, so
at least the girls don't see it.
Please.
Pow!
Yo. Relax.
- Come on.
- Just a joke.
The gun's going away.
Hey, hey, hey, what's wrong?
Is it the thing that Brock said?
Baby, what's going on?
It's everything.
We came here so we
can have time to ourselves.
And now I'm dealing
with this punk-ass frat boy.
Chris keep asking me for
money, and like, I forgot my meds.
And it's like everything I'm trying to do
What medication?
It's nothing.
No, it's not nothing, TJ,
you don't take medication.
What's going on?
Can I just shower first?
We can talk about this later.
Okay.
You know I don't like when
you hide things from me.
I know, but it's just a lot right now.
Baby,
you have me.
We're the only thing that matter.
I just...
I just want you to relax.
You know, you've been gone for six months.
I need you.
Can you see that? I need you.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Just...
Just take a hot shower.
You know?
And you can meet us at the lake
and everything will be fine.
Okay.
He usually not like this, bro.
Fuck.
Yo, listen, I don't really care,
but yo, keep him away from me, bro.
I don't want no blood on my hands, man.
You know you can tell me anything, right?
Okay.
Stop it.
You so angry.
I'm sorry.
All right, we'll see you in a few?
Okay.
Yes, we go.
- Let's go to the lake.
- Hey, are you guys coming?
Yeah, we'll be right down.
No competition, bro.
Don't worry about it.
Pinchy, bro. What the fuck, man?
- Hell yeah, bro.
- Talk to me about that.
But if you
You ready, bro?
Alright, let's go.
You saw mami how she was looking at me?
Yeah, bro, she was.
I forgot something.
One sec.
What the fuck did he forget?
Fuck it.
Yo, I'm ready.
You ready?
Let's go catch the girls.
Yo, wait up.
Oh, James, thank God.
Oh God, what is this?
What are we gonna tell their families?
Hey, come help me up.
Let's go to my office, we'll,
we'll call the paramedics.
And the police.
And the Police.
Yeah, and the police.
Hey.
I'm surprised TJ never came.
Yeah, me too. Let's just go back.
All right.
Guys, you coming?
Sophie, let's go.
Catch up with you guys.
Soph, are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure. I'll catch you later.
Okay.
- Come.
- What?
Get over here.
For what?
Don't ask stupid questions. Carry me.
Ah. Ah. Kai, I think I hurt my leg.
Can I ride on your back too?
Sure. Yeah, of course.
Whoo.
Liz, find them.
Due tracking has now begun.
What the hell
is going on over there?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Baby?
TJ?
Something feels wrong.
What do you mean?
Chris and TJ aren't here?
None of that's weird to you guys?
They probably went
for a walk or something.
In the dark, Imani?
Come on.
Can you guys stop?
It's fucking crazy that you
guys are flirting right now
in front of all us,
us knowing you're in a relationship.
Who the fuck are you
to tell me what to do?
A friend? I thought.
No, I can do whatever I want.
All I'm saying
is we have to fucking go.
Something's weird.
What's up?
What's up, motherfucker?
Stop relax.
What are you doing?
You guys relax.
- I told you.
- You gonna learn today.
You're the one that
bitch in front of your mami.
She's supposed to be my bitch.
Hey, who you calling a bitch? You relax.
Shut the
Puta, mother, do something!
Any fucking time. I told you.
Liz, bring me Omega.
Omega, I need you to retrieve subject 001.
Exfiltration only. Do not damage the asset.
Liz, begin pairing.
Pairing initiated.
Pairing complete.
Go.
TJ.
Run.
Watch you step. Watch
you step. Watch you step.
Watch you step.
I got the gun. I got
the gun. I got the gon.
Where the fuck did you get that?
Brock had it. He bought
it on the way here? What for?
Great, great, great. Can
you shoot? Can you shoot?
Yeah, I know how to shoot.
Don't point that fucking thing at me.
It's on safety. It's on safety.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I was just trying to
show you. It's on safety.
All right, look, so about
a mile down the road,
that's the main road.
How do you know that.
Baby, because that's
where I got lost when
I was trying to make my
way back to the house.
Look, are we walking or fucking dying?
What the fuck are we doing?
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
- Can we just go.
I thought, I thought I heard something.
I thought
We got six fucking bullets.
Save your fucking ammo.
I almost shat myself, dude!
Get your shit together,
motherfucker, all right?
You wanna fucking die?
Oh no I don't want to fucking die.
Because I'm not fucking dying out here.
I don't wanna
die, baby. I don't wanna die.
We're not gonna
die. I didn't mean that.
We're not gonna die. We're not gonna die.
Turn on your flashlights.
Turn your phones on so we can fucking see.
Turn 'em on. Turn 'em on.
All right.
- You got it?
- Okay,
Let's go.
That way. That way. Let' go.
Fuck! What the fuck?
It's a log. It's a log.
Alright.
All right, fuck it, fuck it, fuck it.
Fuck it, it's just us.
It's just us. It's just us.
Fuck him. Fuck him.
You okay? You all right, babe?
Let me see.
We're gonna be okay. We're gonna be okay.
Ssh, be quiet.
Smile!
I don't know what to do.
Fuck.
I'm gonna fucking die.
Where the fuck is everybody?
Guys, I'm really scared now.
I don't wanna die.
Fuck.
Mia. Oh my God.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, Mia.
Mia, fuck, fuck.
I'm so sorry. I swear to
God it was an accident.
I'm such a fucking idiot.
I'm so sorry. Mia. Mia.
Oh my God. Save your breath.
- What?
- Behind you?
What are you saying?
Behind you.
No, no, no, no.
Oh God.
Omega, the operational
parameters have shifted.
Secure the package. Sanitize
the scene. Leave no trace.
This never happened.
We are not gonna die.
We're not gonna fucking die.
I can't believe Victor's dead.
Really?
That's what the fuck you
thinking about right now?
He's dead. We've seen it. We all seen it.
What'd you do?
What did you do?
Huh?
What'd you do?
Because, 'cause I know,
I know a random ass
motherfucker gonna just show up,
and then you just hop on
his fucking back like that.
What'd you do, Imani?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry for hurting you.
Fuck. Get the fuck off me.
Baby.
Please.
- Don't...
- I'm sorry.
- Please...
- I get the fuck off me.
Fucking...
I'm sorry.
After all I fucking did for you.
This is...
Motherfucking joke.
Just don't, don't fucking touch me!
Baby. Baby.
Breathe. Breathe, baby.
Baby, breathe. Breathe.
Come on!
Come get some, motherfucker!
No, no, no, no.
No. No!
He needs to be terminated.
Subject 001?
Yes.
I need you to finish this.
Whatever you need, Doc.
I love you.
♪ You must be a hero ♪
♪ You must be a superman ♪
♪ 'Cause every time I see
you I can't feel the rain ♪
♪ You must be a hero ♪
♪ You must be that kind of man ♪
♪ Who can make me realize
my dreams deep inside ♪
♪ And every time I see
you I can't feel the pain ♪
♪ They can say not good enough ♪
♪ I'm not the one for you ♪
♪ We belong together ♪
♪ And then can tell you anything ♪
♪ To put you away from me ♪
♪ My heart belongs to you ♪
♪ You must be a hero ♪
♪ You must have been sent by the gods ♪
♪ And everything I'm
with you love ain't fantasy ♪
♪ I wanna share with
you till the end of my life ♪
♪ They can say not good enough ♪
♪ I'm not the one for you ♪
♪ We belong together ♪
♪ And then can tell you anything ♪
♪ To put you away from me ♪
♪ My heart belongs to you ♪
♪ You must be a hero ♪
♪ You must be a superman ♪
♪ 'Cause every time I see you ♪
♪ I can't feel the pain ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ Wait, had enough ♪
♪ Now it's time to show up ♪
♪ And you'll never fall ♪
♪ I know you wanted to do something new ♪
♪ Sink your teeth in ♪
♪ Think you had enough ♪
♪ But you never had it rough ♪
♪ We just having fun ♪
♪ Someone told you not to run ♪
♪ Told you I come on like ♪
♪ When I drive through the woods at night ♪
♪ It's fine line ♪
♪ This is yours and this is mine ♪
♪ Wake your hunter's mind ♪
♪ Tear apart what you can find ♪
♪ Umbrella ♪
♪ Bet you Cinderella ♪
♪ Show me how you get 'em ♪
♪ Wait, had enough ♪
♪ Now it's time to show up ♪
♪ And you'll never fall ♪
♪ Let's all spin ♪
♪ Let's kick in ♪
♪ Shed your skin ♪
♪ And take you leash off ♪
♪ You are a hunter, Know who you are ♪
♪ If you want to show you mascara ♪
♪ I can see what you've seen,
if you know what I mean ♪
♪ That's the reason we made it so far ♪
♪ Umbrella ♪
♪ Bet you Cinderella ♪
♪ Show me how you get 'em ♪
♪ Wait, had enough ♪
♪ Now it's time to show up ♪
♪ And you'll never fall ♪
♪ All you hear him say ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ All you ever say ♪
♪ Show me how you get 'em ♪
♪ Wait, had enough ♪