Show yourself!
I know you're dying!
It's over.
The Americans are almost here
they will string us up.
Please don't.
The war is over.
Run northeast, you will
get out of the valley
further northwest,
you'll find farmhouses
you get yourself new clothes!
Take me with you.
Clear off!
Just go northeast...
Run...
Run!
Show yourself!
I know you're dying!
I won't hurt you
I just want to rest...
You're bleeding to death...
Can you get the bullet out?
Please...
Have you deserted?
You can finish eating.
Are you a doctor?
My father.
I wouldn't stay here if I were you
the Allies are close, almost to Brenner.
I don't know what you're doing up here,
but I would run.
The alm belongs to my aunt
she says I'm safe up here.
So I'll stay here until it's all over.
Listen
an SS unit is stationed very close by.
Near Padaun.
They block the passage.
The SS unit is scattered,
they will be wiped out.
Once the line has fallen, the
Allies will be in the high valley
do you understand?
Take your aunt and head north.
I must go now.
Where are my weapons?!
I have taken care of your wound
then let me keep the pistol.
I did not force you to do it.
I must be able to defend myself!
You?
You cannot kill anyone.
Your wound will open up...
Where are they?!
Let me have
Leave the pistol with me
Please
please stop.
please...
My weapons!
Now!
You can have this one.
Just take it!
Take care of yourself.
Show yourself!
I know you're dying!
It is yours!
Your family?
I could help...
Just stick to our agreement!
I'll nurse you back to health,
and you let me keep the pistol!
The blonde girl
who is she?
A neighbour girl from the high valley
her father died in the war.
She brings me food.
Is she up here a lot?
Does your aunt send her?
Depends!
This is Marie... my older sister.
She married a pastor in Rosenheim.
That's where I'm going...
How can I tell that the
wound can no longer open up?
When you can do hard work again.
Like what?
Wood chopping?!
Then you have to show me how to chop wood.
What do I get in return?
I will teach you how to shoot.
Fine...
How did you find me, anyway?
Now pull it over
You know, when you shoot, it's loud...
Do you think I'm dumb?
You don't want to be found, do you?
You are sleeping over there!
Have you forgotten how
to eat during the war?
I am Anton
I'm from Munich.
I'm also from Munich.
My father, my mom...
My father has a factory in Landshut.
My family
committed Nazis.
That's how I came to join the army.
Where are your parents now?
Haven't heard from them in a long time...
Me neither...
Who is he?
He shot me...
You don't have to be
afraid, I won't touch you.
I'm not afraid of you!
Can I get fresh water?
Dream on
You could fix the roof,
or fetch water from the trough.
Make yourself useful.
Then you will also get fresh water.
Done!
Your turn...
My God
what are we doing here?
Let's get the hell out of here!
You can eat,
and then you show me how to shoot!
I'm low on ammo for the pistol
only five bullets left.
This is how you load them...
Magazine in
magazine out.
Safety off
safety on.
Loading
aiming.
Now you.
Aim for the tree trunk.
Eye on the target...
Rear sight, front sight.
Now you guide the hand
with the gun from top to bottom.
Easy...
You stop when you reach
the middle of the tree trunk.
Breathe in...
Breathe out...
Again from the start!
Breathe out,
and shoot.
Go!
Good. Now by yourself!
Load the gun!
How many people did you kill?!
I did not count...
Were there innocent people?
Safety on!
Would you like to try again?!
Where did you live in Munich?
Schwabing Giselastrasse.
Do you know the Schwabinger Bucht?
Yes, I do.
And your father was a doctor?
Yes... In the hospital on Maistrasse.
You know, I also wanted to become a doctor.
I admire women who study.
Can't be enough smart women in Germany.
I can't figure you out!
You're getting better.
If the SS sees this, they'll hang you!
Hold on...
Let me help you!
You'll be rid of me soon...
Wash yourself properly tomorrow morning!
You stink!
Can't you smell it?
Mom didn't want me to bring the sausage.
Who is he?
Looks good!
A soldier, I helped him.
Mom will be furious.
He will be gone soon.
Mom says the jewelry is worthless.
She scolded me last time
I came with the bracelet.
She wants money!
Now go Lotte
we'll sort it all out next time, okay?
Mama says if you can't pay
you have to leave!
How much do you get?
20 Marks...
So cheap?
Not a word... to anyone!
Business is business!
After all, the alm belongs to my family!
We decide who gets hidden and who not!
No matter if it's a deserter or a Jew!
You look pathetic!
You're from the city, right?
Don't be so cheeky, I'm injured!
Are you going to get naked again?
You get slapped around a lot, don't you?
If I steal something,
my brother beats me up.
Why are you hiding her?
It pays well.
But if you get caught,
you'll go to Mauthausen
are you not afraid?
We need the money
people in the village
look the other way.
People know there's a Jew up here?
Some people like it and some don't
we often share...
But you have to look after yourselves.
Mom says you have to help a
person when they are in need
she helped you too, right?
Where are you going?
Rosenheim...
Are you two together?
With a Jew?!
Do you want to make another deal with me?
Thank you for paying Charlotte.
Do you have a problem with me being Jewish?
Not with you...
But?
It is war...
You are a deserter.
Why did you all not
just leave our country?!
Would have been
better if I had let you die!
You should have told me!
All these years I've been
going from hideout to hideout!
I was always afraid,
always had to be careful!
Why do you think I have no money left?
Do you think anyone would
have hidden me for nothing?
To be a Jew in Germany is to be subhuman
that's what they taught you!
You are not subhuman...
Just as I became of age
when I thought,
now I can start living
you came and took everything from me!
Yes, you are right!
They taught me! My parents,
at school, everyone said it!
What?!
That you are to blame for everything!
That is a lie!
I know!
I was no longer allowed to study
then my father was
no longer allowed to work.
I had to watch kids on the
street spitting in his face...
There were children, he
helped bring in to this world.
And now I ask you, why?
You have made us a
scapegoat for all your problems.
My father used to say
it will get better.
With each new harassment, we
thought it couldn't get any worse!
But it got worse and worse...
My parents went to Amsterdam.
I was privileged, but my
sister and her husband
they did not want to leave their home.
I'm sorry...
What for?
What you have done is inexcusable!
I'm sorry I couldn't
do anything about it...
Sometimes you just cannot see the truth
out of fear
it's like you've gone blind...
You can stay...
Come on over.
You fool
that's not going to work.
That's how it's done,
but costs extra!
Have you got my clothes?
My brother caught me and beat me up.
I don't have much time.
You'll get your clothes.
You're smart, aren't you?
Do you know anything about the Allies?
Down in the valley, they
say the Italians are dug in
waiting for the Americans,
they are almost here.
Some young lads have
already blown up the streets,
so that the American
tanks can't go further.
Are you afraid of the Americans?
And the SS, what about them?
So... that needs to soak.
Blood hardly ever comes out.
Now get lost.
I'm sleeping here tonight.
Anton
Hannah, show Anton your hair!
Isn't she pretty?
Your necklace?
Belonged to Selma, my sister
just like the blue dress.
Selma was five years older than me
she was engaged to Otto.
The two of them lived
in our house, in Munich.
They often went out together.
My sister also, to the
clubs on MÈullerstrasse.
Yes!
Selma always smelled so thrilling
when she came home at night
of sweat, alcohol, cigarettes
of being a woman!
And she taught me how
to dance... Charleston!
Please Hanna, show us!
I dare you, you coward!
My father died early in the war.
But my brother, Wilhelm, he came back.
They shot him... through here.
Now he can't raise his right arm.
He became wrong in the head,
but the left arm... he
still has strength for two!
When he slaps me, I
can hear the angels sing.
What will you do when the Allies get here?
The Italians won't get me!
I'm good at hiding...
And even if they did,
mama told me to play dead
just lay still and it
will be over quickly.
Now tell me
have you ever shot anybody?
I've been to Italy
to Russia... and I have seen Paris!
That's where I want to go!
Hitler once wanted to
climb the Eiffel Tower
that's when the Parisians
cut the ropes to the elevators.
So you had to climb the 765 steps by foot.
Of course, Adolf did not do that!
But I did!
You can see everything
up there, Charlotte
Trocadero... èlle de
la Cité... Notre-Dame...
Champs-éElysées Sacré-Cuur
That's a sight you won't
forget for the rest of your life!
We are finished...
One time, we were in Chazlau
the SS strung up Partisans.
There were also children
a girl just about
the age of Charlotte...
When they pulled her up
she started to struggle...
kept kicking and jerking,
and she shook off her pants,
and there she hung... naked!
The soldiers died laughing as she slowly
suffocated in agony.
Do you want to know what
happened to your parents?
I saw one of the work camps of the SS...
In Treblinka, in the east...
If your parents were in Amsterdam
they were detained not later than '43,
and were brought there.
I have seen how the Jews
how they arrived in train cars...
The SS had built a set...
The barracks had been freshly painted
everything was decorated
with flowers, signs everywhere
everything looked
like a normal train station!
They drove the Jews out of the wagons...
The SS soldiers were
firm, some even friendly.
I heard one who said:
The Jews should hurry up, otherwise
the water will get cold, for showering...
But they burned them all!
Even in the villages miles
away, it still stank of death!
They killed them all
the old, the young, the children
3.000 people at a time!
When the war is over, the
world will know the truth!
We will not be forgiven...
Not in a thousand years!
You can leave, looks good...
I wonder if my sister
will still recognize me.
Show yourself!
I know you're dying!
I will get your clothes
don't worry.
When?
Tomorrow...
Very good
do it again.
When are you leaving?
Once Charlotte arrives...
I got something...
A farewell?
Bleh
How can anyone like that?
I would love to see
you in the blue dress...
I have to tell you something...
It's starting!
The Wehrmacht is near Wipptal
and seals it off to the north
that is the central
thrust of the Allies.
But you can bypass via Padaun.
The SS is waiting there
Now that the Americans are
here, the SS will be wiped out...
Then the advance goes via Vals...
I can't wait for Charlotte...
I'm leaving in the morning!
What do you think? Are the
Americans already near Vals?
When are they going to attack?
In a day or two I think
then they will also search
everything up here in the mountains
just like the SS.
If I don't go now, I'll
end up behind the line...
You got five bullets, not one more!
Take care.
Come with me.
What is that?
What do you mean?
I wanted to tell you...
You were with the SS!
My family has been murdered
my friends!
I refused...
Get out!
Get the hell out of here! You murderer!
You won't kill anyone else! Get lost!
I hope you die out there
or the Italians find you!
I'm coming in!
Anton
Sit down!
Keep going!
I did not think you would survive...
We should have looked for you longer.
You know, Anton, I've been
I've been thinking deeply!
For example, why you became a traitor.
This is my best friend
I've known him all my life!
I always looked up to you
have always been in your shadow.
But in my moment of success
when my achievements were
appreciated and I was promoted
you betray me?!
It's not about you,
or us!
It's about the atrocities we
were supposed to carry out!
You weakened our unit with your compassion!
My friend. We would have put
anyone else in front of a firing squad!
But your father's position
always protected you
Where are you going?
To disinfect...
What do you want?
I need something to disinfect.
Damn it, it was war
and terrible things happen in war!
But you have to remain human!
Don't make a wrong move, friend!
You and I, we joined the SS voluntarily...
And you have to keep your word after all!
To treat people like animals...
You know that was wrong!
You will be held accountable!
I've seen you grabbing
kids by their feet
smashing their heads against trees!
Like a fashion!
In 1940 it was fashion to
beat little children to death!
And a year later it was
fashion to tear them apart
in pairs, each at one end...
And then I knew, you are evil...
And this war was no longer my war...
And that is what it is all about!
You're not from around here, are you?
You patched him up, right?
You knew he was a deserter!
Why did you not just let him die?!
I made her!
She was my hostage!
But this morning somehow
she got hold of my gun,
and the bitch shoots at me!
Of course she thought, you were me!
She probably thought I was
trying to get the gun back!
All right
But
Why did you come back?!
Come here...
Kneel down...
Georg!
Stay down!
You're a pretty thing...
You know, the alm is well hidden,
and if I hadn't heard the gunshots
I would never have found you.
So you're lucky...
You have a protector now!
And for that I deserve a kiss...
Please stop...
Don't you think?
Did you see that?
Being nice grants you a kiss!
Drop it! Now!
What are you doing here?
Answer me!
Damn it Georg, she's just a child...
Shut your mouth!
Why are you here?
Now talk!
She just brought me some clothes
For whom is the food?
Why are you bringing this up here!
I am counting to three now...
You...
You are telling me everything!
One
Two
I am a Jew, I am in hiding...
Out
everyone!
Halt!
In the name of the German
people, I sentence you to death!
First the girl for behavior that is
harmful to the German people...
Then the Jew, as an enemy
of the German people...
And finally you... for treason!
Georg stop it...
Stop right there...
Let them go...
You can do what you want with me...
But leave Charlotte and Hannah alone.
Kill me!
Shoot me!
I won't make it that
easy for you, my friend!
Don't die on me...
I told you, the Jew comes first,
and I still want to watch you die...
You understand why I need to do this?
You and all your kind, you are vermin
like doves...
Individually you might be quite a sight
but if you become too many
then you shit all over everything!
Destroy the roof... spread diseases,
and that is why we have to wipe you out!
But not only the adults
also the females, the chicks,
the eggs, the nests, just everything!
And then there are
people, again and again
like that little girl out there
they feed the little doves!
But you have to keep your house clean!
Am I right?
You are nothing more than sadists
who take pleasure in
torturing other people...
You are monsters!
Who were just waiting for the
right moment to crawl to the surface!
You... and all your friends...
You will burn in blazing flames
And no one... will help you.
And be aware...
That the angels will
take your souls to Sheol
and your souls will suffer...
And endure a severe trial
In darkness
shackles... and burning flames!
When I'm done with you
I will string you up!
Charlotte
Charlotte, if you are still
here, please help me...
If you want to help Hannah,
you have to help me first...
Charlotte... I've always been
afraid to do the right thing...
Rather saved my own skin...
But you told me
if a person needs
help, you have to help him!
Charlotte
Hide!
You must not leave me alone!
Damn it Charlotte, you are good at hiding!
I can help you!
Keep behind me,
and if something happens to me, you run!
Come!
Run around
throw a rock through the window, hurry!
I'm staying...
You really won't die!
Georg it's enough...
You've seen the clothes...
Put them on and then
we'll set off together...
Marie will be delighted...
You're not going anywhere, my friend...
You can do this!
I'll get this fixed...
You'll be back on your
feet in a few days,
and then you can be on your way!