What about Asta?
He'll have to go in
the baggage car, won't he?
Why should he have
any special privileges?
He'll ride with us
in the day coach and like it.
But those are the rules,
aren't they?
Well... we'll camouflage him
under your coat.
Out of sight, out of mind.
It's a cinch.
Uh, two to Sycamore Springs,
please.
[whining]
Oh! Nick! Asta!
Catch him!
Here.
You get them.
Asta!
Asta?
Alright, come on.
[growling playfully]
Here, here.
What's going on?
Nick Charles.
Hiya, Clancey.
Nick, I'm surprised
at you.
I thought you could
handle a stout.
I tripped.
I was chasing my dog.
Oh, sure.
Clancey, I've had nothing
but a swig of cider all day.
Nicky, are you hurt?
I think he hurt
his head, Mrs. Charles.
He's been saying
something about
not drinking nothing
but cider.
And it's true.
He's going down
to visit his folks,
and they don't like
drinking.
Let's get down to the train
and get comfortable.
Ha! Camouflage,
you know.
Oh, yes.
Thanks, Clancey.
[train whistle blowing]
Pardon me.
It's cozy, isn't it?
C'est la guerre, madam.
C'est la guerre.
That's French
for "bottoms up.”
Tickets, please.
Nicky, you really
like cider?
Like it?
I love it.
Why, just the pure,
natural juice of the apple.
What could be better,
for instance?
A dry martini,
for instance.
That horrible stuff?
Almost took the lining
off my stomach.
Why do you care?
It didn't show.
Good gracious!
Nicky!
Blockbuster.
Ooh. Yes.
Uh!
Upsy-daisy.
[clears throat]
Oh!
Tickets, please.
You know, mammy,
I don't think
you're taking
this reform movement
of mine very seriously.
Not very.
Well,
you just wait.
A couple of weeks
on this cider,
and i'll be
a new man.
I sort of liked
the old one.
Why, darling,
that's the nicest
thing you said to me
since the time
i got my head caught
in that cuspidor
at the Waldorf.
That wasn't the Waldorf.
That was the Astor.
Astor?
Astor.
All animals must go
in the baggage car.
Oh, that's
not an animal.
That's
my fur coat.
If it can wag its tail,
it goes in the baggage car.
So, it was going
to be a cinch, eh?
Very well.
Credit me with an error.
Hey. Hey, mister.
When you pass
the kitchen,
will you ask the chef
to warm this up?
I don't
dance, bub.
Body
temperature.
Good grief!
Are you on milk now?
I'm warming this up
for a friend.
Oh!
Oh, I beg
your pardon.
Why, if it isn't
Nick Charles.
Where did you
drop in from?
You sure are a sight
for sore eyes.
Hiya, Brogan.
Well, cut off my legs
and call me shorty.
It's a small world,
ain't it?
Ain't it?
Where
are you going?
We're off on
a little vacation,
Sycamore Springs.
I getit. I get it.
I'll play dummy.
Oh, you're on
the wrong horse, Brogan.
This is Mrs. Charles.
Oh, sure, sure.
[sarcastically]
How do you do, Mrs. Charles?
So, uh, what are
you doing these days?
Traveling
in postcards.
Pardon?
Postcards. Postcards.
Seasonal greetings.
Say, I cover
Sycamore Springs.
I'll look you up
on the way back.
That will be nice.
Well, so long.
So long.
Nick,
how am i doing?
Oh, swell.
Stick close to me
in Sycamore Springs.
Right. How's
my postcard chatter?
Alright,
but look,
don't those
greeting cards
have some poems
or mottos?
I think so.
Yeah. Well,
memorize a few.
You mean like,
"Roses are red
violets are blue
a happy birthday is
what i'm wishing you?"
Yes, that's it...
roughly.
I get it.
[train whistle blowing]
"Willa Wanna,
Desdemona,
"Minnetonka,
Nippewana."
How far is that
baggage car, anyway?
Oh, imagine
it's somewhere
between Pocahontas
and Sitting Bull.
Well.
Any suggestions?
Make like
an eel, mama.
[train whistle blowing]
Woman: More people.
[people groaning]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, my cigar.
And that was my
last one, too.
Excuse me.
Would you please
let me pass?
Why should i?
Oh!
Well!
How'd you like to be
married to that type?
Oh, excuse me.
Oh, my word.
I'm so sorry.
Why don't you look
where you're going?
Darling,
are you sure
you're rubbing these people
the right way?
Uh-oh.
The blockbuster.
Woman: Isn't
that terrible?
Ow! My foot!
My foot!
Will you please
let us through?
Well!
Oh, certainly.
Make way for this lady
and her baby.
Make way. She wants to get
to the dining car.
Make way for the mother.
Follow me.
[train whistle blowing]
[goats bleating]
[Asta barking]
[ducks quacking]
[barking]
[quack]
[whimpering]
Ha ha!
Bad strategy, Asta.
You forgot to protect
your rear flank.
Nicky?
Hmm?
I still
don't understand
what gave you
this sudden desire
to go back to Sycamore Springs
after all these years.
Well, it'll make
a nice vacation, won't it?
A chance to see
mother and dad.
I'll bet they're
anxious to see you,
and not just
the family.
The whole town
will probably turn out.
After all, you are
the local boy who made good.
Oh, now, darling,
come, come.
Oh, don't be
so modest, Nicky.
Won't it feel
good to get
a pat on the back
from your old man?
A pat on the back?
What would i do with it?
Ah, don't kid me.
If your father
ever gave you
a pat on the back,
you'd pop your vest buttons
all over the parlor rug.
You just don't know
my vest buttons.
Look!
Darling, see it?
The old windmill.
It's still there.
You know, when i
was a little punk,
that was
my secret hideaway.
Good heavens.
What secrets
were you hiding
in those days?
Oh, corn silk,
detective stories.
And look, right there was
the little old schoolhouse.
Ha ha. You know,
once on Halloween,
I burned it down...
slightly.
That must have handed
your father a big laugh.
Yes. He just roared...
all the way
to the woodshed with me.
Nicky, you never
got along,
you and your father,
did you?
Never got along?
I wonder what ever
gave you that impression.
Oh, he's never come
to see us in New York.
Well, he's pretty
busy, you know.
Of course, there is
one other little thing.
He, uh... he thinks
i play too hard.
Indeed?
And drink too hard.
Wonder what ever gave him
that impression.
[train whistle blows]
Sycamore Springs.
This is you, folks.
Well, we're very much
obliged to you.
Buy yourself
a little smoke.
Thanks, but...
Compliments
of the pup.
Spitz?
No, just growls.
[goat bleats]
Ha ha. That's funny.
I wonder if they
got my letter.
Of course they did.
There's your
reception committee.
Oh.
It's Crazy Mary.
She's a town
character.
Hello, Mary.
Remember me?
Yeah.
Nick Charles.
Yes, that's right.
Darling, this is Mary.
- Hello, Mary.
- My wife.
Poor woman.
Where's the baby?
I heard
you had a baby.
Baby. Oh...
baby. Baby.
What's he
going to do now?
I don't know.
Desdemona!
That's crazy Nick.
He was always
like that.
[growling]
[barking]
Asta, no.
Let's surprise them,
huh, sweet?
- Uh!
- Shh.
It's a surprise.
The doctor
isn't in.
No?
But you can go to
Dr. Clayworth.
He's just down
the street.
Is Mrs. Charles in?
She's
in the kitchen.
Shh.
What's
cooking, ma?
Oh, just making
a little tea.
Nick! Nick,
my darling!
Oh!
Hiya, ma.
How wonderful
that you could
get here for
your birthday.
Wasn't it?
Nora!
Hello, dear.
What a lovely suit.
Why didn't you tell me
you were coming?
Didn't dad
get my letter?
Why, no. He didn't say
anything to me about it.
Wait a moment.
That's what he must have meant
when he said there would be
two extra for dinner.
Oh, your father.
Where's junior?
Oh, we didn't want to
take him out of school.
He's going to kindergarten
now and loves it.
Oh, he must be
simply huge by now.
Hello, Asta.
Oh, I'm so excited.
Come along.
I'll get you two settled.
You know something?
I believe the plan
is going through.
For the hospital?
Yes. Isn't it
wonderful?
You know, Nora,
they're going to build
a hospital
for the doctor
with a laboratory
for his research work.
It's something he's
dreamed of all his life.
Why, good heavens, Hilda.
What are you doing there?
Take the bags
upstairs.
Are you alright?
Why, of course
i'm alright.
This is my son,
the famous detective.
Oh!
What is the matter
with you, Hilda?
Detective?
Now, this is
all your fault.
Mine?
Yes. It only behaves
like this
when there's excitement
in the house.
Do you mean
to tell me
that this table
hasn't been fixed yet?
Well, if you want
to make yourself useful,
you can fix it.
There's a screwdriver
in the kitchen.
I don't need
a screwdriver.
I've got a little gadget
right here in my pocket
that will do anything,
from manicuring to safecracking.
Safecracking.
Nicky.
Now, how did this
get in here?
Come along. Come along
and help me with the tea.
And take off your pretty hat.
Oh.
[clang]
Just a little
elbow grease.
[growling playfully]
Here we are.
Now, that's the last time
that'll ever come down.
[whimpering]
Uh-oh.
Nora: Oh, doctor.
Oh, Nora, dear.
I'm so sorry
i missed you
at the station.
Oh, that's alright.
I managed to get him here.
Yes,
so i see.
Hiya, pop.
Hello, son.
Well...
let's get him
on his feet.
Come on.
Up you come.
You know, I was just
fixing this table...
Yes, I know,
and i suppose that's
furniture polish??
That, dad, is cider.
- Uh-huh.
- Taste it.
Oh, I don't have to.
I believe you.
Come on,
just one little swallow.
If you say it's cider,
it's cider.
Please,
Dr. Charles.
Oh, well.
Why, Nick,
this is cider.
Oh, what a dinner.
What a dinner.
Mmm! Ha ha!
Oh, ma, I'm glad to see
that you still have
that same old magic touch
with the skillet.
Nora: It was
delicious, mother.
Oh, it was just sort
of thrown together.
Sure. Just
thrown together.
She's been over that stove
for hours.
Now, don't pay any
attention to him, Nick.
Hilda, bring
the coffee in here.
Well, dad,
that certainly is
fine news
about the hospital.
Yes. Sam Ronson's going
to make a recommendation
at the next meeting
of the board,
and a recommendation
from him
is as good
as an order.
Nora:
Who's Sam Ronson?
He's the town banker.
He has a hand in everything
that goes on here.
I suppose he's what
you'd call a typhoon.
Don't you mean
tycoon, mother?
Typhoon is a sort
of a big wind.
Well, that's
Sam Ronson.
[chuckles]
Nick, tell us something
about your work
in New York.
Nora:
Yes, Nick, do.
Have you
gone to work?
What are you
doing?
Oh, same old thing.
Oh, so you're
still a policeman?
Well, I'd hardly
put it that way.
No. How would
you put it?
I'd say that Nick
was more of a genius.
My Nick?
You see,
Nick doesn't actually
work with the police.
In fact, people
call on him
who think he's better
than the police.
He's paid
very large fees
because his work
is important,
extremely important.
My dear Nora, I didn't say
it wasn't important.
You implied
that you didn't think
it was
very important.
You gave the impression
that you thought
that Nick walked up
and down the street
swinging a club.
Oh, well, if i gave
that impression,
I'm heartily sorry.
Oh, sure.
A very handsome apology.
If Nick thinks it's important
to be a policeman,
that's all that
matters... I suppose.
But you don't know
what he does...
Darling, why don't you
pop out to the kitchen
and speed up
the coffee, hmm?
Some of the cases
Nick has solved
were considered
absolutely impossible.
Darling,
let me show you
the view from
the front porch.
Oh, it's beautiful
in the moonlight.
What about
the Wynant murder
or the fingers
O'Toole case
or the slaughterhouse
mystery?
Or take
Stinky Davis.
Who's Stinky Davis?
Stinky Davis?
The Stinky Davis
case illustrates
what i mean
about Nick.
Yes, I'm sure
it does, Nora.
Do you still
take two lumps
in your stinky...
I mean, in your coffee?
Just imagine...
four murders,
all strangulation,
no fingerprints,
no clues.
The police
were baffled.
Yes, of course.
All they had
were four bodies.
So, what
did they do?
They dumped the whole
thing in Nick's lap.
I see.
Nobody
suspected Stinky
because
he'd been a cripple
ever since
some nitro went off
while he was cracking
a canister in Salt Lake.
Everybody thought it was
Rainbow Benny,
but Nick knew
that Rainbow
was an expert
with the shiv.
Strangling was
out of his line.
Oh. Smart Nick.
Then they turned the heat
on Slasher Martin,
who ran a dice joint
down in Chinatown,
but Slasher
had an alibi
with Squinty Burke
and Studsy Greene,
so that
took care of him.
But all the time,
Nick was certain
that Stinky Davis
was the Killer.
Why? Because he had
him pegged right away
for a two-timing,
double-crossing rat.
Nora: Would the police
listen to Nick?
No. They told him it was
a Hophead theory,
wild as loco buttons,
because Stinky
was a cripple
and couldn't navigate.
So, Nick got the brush-off
from the police.
They cold-shouldered
him right out,
but did that
stop him?
Nora: No, sir. He knew
the case was hot,
and he was all set
to start cooking
on the front burner.
He said, "Stinky,
"you're the two-timing,
double-crossing rat
"who strangled
Knobs McLure and Greasy Joe
and Horsefaced Dan
and Denver Mike."
And then he turned
his back on him,
and the trick worked,
because Stinky got up
out of his wheelchair
and tried to strangle Nick
with a piece of wire
he had hidden
in his mouth,
but just in time,
Nick turned around,
gave him
the old one-two,
and knocked Stinky colder
than an ice flounder.
Whew.
Stinky wasn't
a cripple at all.
He was just using it
to cover up his crimes.
Now, what do you
think of that?
Well, if Nick
suspected
that Stinky
wasn't a cripple,
why didn't he have him
examined by a doctor?
The whole thing's
so silly.
Dr. Charles...
you are impossible.
Now, you see?
You've
upset her.
[chuckles]
Spirited little thing,
isn't she?
Mm-hmm. Well, you know
how women are.
No. How are they?
[chuckles]
Mother, come here.
Nora: Isn't he beautiful?
[laughing]
Mother,
what's wrong
between Nick
and his father?
Well, hasn't Nick
ever told you?
No. He's very seldom
talked about it.
Well, it seems
rather silly,
but the doctor
had his heart set
upon Nick becoming
a doctor, too,
so that they could
work together.
That's how
the whole idea
for the hospital
first started,
but Nick had
a mind of his own.
And became
a policeman.
Yes. That's
about it.
I wish he could
do something
to impress his father
while he's here.
I don't suppose there's
any crime in Sycamore Springs?
Gracious, no.
The only excitement
we ever had
was a runaway horse
last Christmas.
There's nothing in the world
Nick wants more
than a pat on the back
from his father.
If he got that, I think
he'd pop a vest button.
Did he admit that?
No.
You know Nicky.
We were married
three years
before he told me
he loved me.
Well, all
i can say is,
if you're looking for crime
in Sycamore Springs,
you'll have to
commit it yourself.
I wonder...
Nicky always says
that there's a skeleton
in nearly every closet,
and if you rattle
it hard enough,
something
always happens.
But would Nick
like it
if you went around rattling
people's skeletons?
Oh, he'd be furious,
but if some crime
did break,
it would be
a wonderful chance
for him to show
his father
what a great
detective he is.
Hmm.
Studying hard,
Junior?
Hmm?
Ha ha. Oh, hi.
Ahh.
Guess i must have
dropped off.
Would you like
to lie here?
No, no. Stay
where you are.
I don't want to
disturb you
while you"re working
on your lessons.
I'll pull up one
of these chairs.
Can't i help you?
No. You've made
enough effort.
Hmm.
I was just thinking
about a little gal
by the name
of Alice Brody.
We used to come out here
on hot summer nights
and play
on her banjo.
Oh?
The boys used to
write their names on it.
She married a brewer
from Milwaukee.
What did he play,
the bull fiddle?
Nick: Oh. No, she was
very fond of beer.
Are you sure i can't
help you with that?
No. No. You might
get all sweaty and die.
[slurping]
Man: Well,
hello there.
Hmm?
Nick, you old
son of a gun.
Why didn't you let me know
you were in town?
Oh, hello,
Bruce.
Hello, Nick. Well, it looks
like the old days.
Yeah. Ha ha!
Oh, uh, darling,
meet an old schoolmate...
Bruce Clayworth.
Mrs. Charles.
How do you do,
Mr. Clayworth?
Mrs. Charles?
Well, I'm certainly
glad to meet you.
Now i know the secret
of Nick's success.
Yes, if it weren't
for her money,
I probably would have had to
go to work, like you, Bruce.
What do you do,
Mr. Clayworth?
Oh, I'm just
a small-town doctor.
Always will be, I guess.
Nick had
the right idea...
get out where the money is,
and it'll come to you.
- That's what he always said.
- Did i say that?
Well, he was always the smart
one anyway, Mrs. Charles.
What are you doing now, Nick?
You here on a case?
No, no, no. We're
just visiting the folks.
Let's see something of you
while you're in town, huh?
I got to run along.
I'm going to have a baby.
Drink plenty of milk.
Oh, not me.
Down at the hospit...
he was always a clown,
Mrs. Charles.
He used to put us
in stitches. Good-bye.
- Good-bye.
How would you like to put me
in stitches, papa?
Hmm.
Ahh...
Woman: Well, if it isn't
little Nicholas Charles.
Nick: Huh?
[softly]
Old home week.
Oh, it's Mrs. Peavy,
isn't it?
Hmm...
Nick: Well, hello.
You've grown.
Yes.
In all directions.
You remember
my young nephew, Willoughby.
Oh, yes, of course.
How are you?
How do you do?
He seems to have
grown, too.
And i suppose
this is Mrs. Charles.
Yes.
I'm Mrs. Charles.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
This is my
old schoolteacher Miss Peavy
and Willoughby Peavy.
- How do you do?
Willoughby is working
out at the plant now.
Are you in town
on a case, Nicholas?
No. I'm just trying
to get a little rest.
I daresay there's
plenty of evil
in Sycamore Springs,
and it's your duty
to ferret it out.
Oh, ha ha.
Well, I daresay.
Hew to the line.
Let the chips fall
where they may.
[barking]
Asta. Asta.
Asta, no.
What a nasty
little dog.
Come along,
Willoughby.
Oh, don't
hurry away.
I hope i see you
again, Mrs. Charles...
without your dog.
[growling]
Darling, is that
why you burned
the schoolhouse
down?
What did you want to
shoot your mouth off
about me for?
Oh, hush up.
I just told them
you were working
at the plant.
I didn't tell them
what you were doing.
Having trouble
with that?
Very funny,
I'm sure.
Oh!
[laughing]
Mother: Children.
[laughter stops]
Hello, mother.
I saw all those people
stopping, Nicky.
You're getting to be
quite a public character.
Yes. I feel like
a public something.
It's funny.
They all assume
he's working
on a case.
Woman: Mind if i come in?
Not at all, Laurabel.
Come along.
- Don't be long.
- No.
Who's this?
It's Laurabel Ronson.
She's the daughter
of that typhoon
i was telling
you about.
You're Mrs. Charles,
aren't you?
Yes.
Oh, I knew it.
I knew it
when i saw you
from the car.
I felt it
here, inside.
Laurabel goes
to dramatic school.
Oh, I see.
And this is your
famous husband.
Nora: Yes. He
looks alright
when you get him
dressed up.
You're here
on a mystery,
a deep, deep mystery
in Sycamore Springs.
I feel it
here, inside.
Well, I'm sorry
to disagree
with your insides,
miss, uh...
Just call me
Laurabel.
[stammering]
But i'm really just here
for a little rest.
Mother: You must
pardon Nick, Laurabel.
He's been working
very hard in the city,
and he's tired.
Oh, yes, I know how
these geniuses are...
all nerves.
But i realize you
can't talk about it,
even if he is
here on a case.
No. We mustn't
talk about it.
In fact,
we don't have to.
Everything is so frightfully
hush-hush these days,
but i know, and i think
it's wonderful.
[horn honks]
Good gracious. Who's making
all that racket?
[honking horn]
Oh, that's
Tom Clayworth.
I promised to drive him
to the train.
He's leaving for Boston.
Oh. Has he got his discharge
from the army yet?
Yes, but ever since
he came back
from the south seas,
he's been
as nervous as a cat.
Mother: Poor boy.
And so jealous.
Why, he won't even let
another man talk to me.
I haven't said
anything.
I must take
my leave now,
but we're going to see
a lot of each other.
I'm sure.
I feel it here...
Inside?
Yes.
And don't forget,
Laurabel,
we mustn't
talk about it.
Oh, I understand,
Mrs. Charles,
and your secret
couldn't be in better hands.
[instrumental music]
But it's all over
town, Mrs. Charles,
that Mr. Charles
is here on a case.
If you can only give me
a little statement.
I never discuss
Mr. Charles' activities.
He happens
to be out now,
but Mr. Charles
is in town,
Mr. Charles
is a detective,
and you can draw
your own conclusions.
Thank you!
"In an exclusive interview
with Mrs. Charles
"by the Sycamore Springs
"Evening News,"
"she raised
an eyebrow and said,
"I never discuss
Mr. Charles' activities
but you can draw your
own conclusions.”
Now, that's
a lot of malarkey.
Why, I've known
Nick Charles for years.
If there was anything
going on in this town,
he'd be the first
to let me know.
Look at that.
Nick Charles is in town.
The paper says he's here
on some investigation.
That means
he's after us.
We got to
get that painting
and get out of here.
But the painting
hasn't come in yet.
I was at Crump's
this morning.
I can't
understand that.
Are you sure
you asked Crump
for the painting
of the windmill?
Of course i'm sure.
Well, then, why...
Now, Edgar, calm down.
We'll get it.
I don't like
that flatfoot
snooping
around town.
We'll go
down there now.
Alright,
alright, alright.
Mister?
Huh? Oh,
how do you do?
How much is this?
This? Oh, you
don't want this.
Oh, gracious me, no.
But i do want it.
No, no.
I can't sell that.
That's by one
of our local boys.
It just came in.
I have a standing offer
for all of his work.
Some crazy woman
thinks he's a genius.
But i happen
to like it.
That old windmill
has a certain
sentimental association
for my husband,
and i'd like to
give it to him
for his birthday
tomorrow.
How much did
the other woman pay you?
$50. She buys
all of his work.
I'll give you 60.
I beg your...pardon?
I said
I'd give you $60.
But you'll never
make any money
paying $60
for a $50 painting.
But i don't want
to make any money.
My husband spent
his whole youth
in that windmill,
and he's sentimental
about it.
Tomorrow
is his birthday.
Can't you
understand that?
Yes, but i
promised her.
She'd be awfully
mad at me.
Oh, don't worry
about that.
Yes, but i like
to keep my promises...
if i can.
10, 50...
I wish i'd gone into
some other business.
60.
There you are.
Oh, don't worry
about that.
Thank you.
Good day.
And happy birthday.
Has it come in yet?
Yes? Has what
come in yet?
The painting.
Painting? Oh, I have
a lot of paintings.
There's the "Barefoot Boy,"
"The Stag at Dawn,”
and "Waiting for
the Robert E. Lee,"
and all of them bad.
No, no, no.
Don't you remember me?
I'm the woman
who collects Bertons.
You were expecting
another one in today.
Oh, that. Well,
I just sold it.
Sold it?
To whom?
That woman who was just
in here with a birthday.
Oh!
You...
you old fool!
I knew she'd
be mad at me.
There goes
your painting.
Well, somebody's
going to pay plenty
for that picture
before we're through,
and it isn't
going to be me.
Oh, good evening,
Willoughby.
Mr. Charles.
You, uh, looking
for clues?
Oh. No, I'm not,
but my pup seems
to have found something.
Yeah.
Well...
Come on, Asta.
You've had enough botany
for one night.
"I never discuss
Mr. Charles' activities.
You can draw
your own conclusions.”
Hmm...
Oh, there
you are.
I thought you were
never coming.
Something happened?
Nothing.
I'm just glad to
see you. That's all.
Oh, well, has papa's
little hunchy-punchy-bunchy
been having
a busy time?
Well, I...
We mustn't tire
ourselves out, must we?
What have you got
behind your back?
Hmm?
Oh, the paper.
I couldn't find it.
Father, does
the old woodshed still stand
in its sheltered nook
amongst the trees?
Father: Yes, Nick.
Mm-hmm. And does
the trusty razor strop
still hang
behind the door?
No. I use
an electric razor now.
Oh, oh.
Well, necessity is
the mother of invention.
Now you're going
to get it.
You're going to get it
where Nellie wore the beads.
No, Nick!
Not here in front
of your parents!
Oh, stop it!
But you can draw
your own conclusions.
[growling playfully]
Nick: This will teach you
the power of the press.
[laughing]
A fine son
you brought up!
A wife beater!
A brave boy.
I wanted
to do that
to mother
for 40 years.
I dare you.
[doorbell buzzes]
Who can that be?
Well, one way
to find out.
Are you
Mr. Nick Charles?
Yes.
I wonder if i could
talk to you for a few minutes.
You see, there's something
i've got to get off my mind.
Uh!
He's dead, Nick.
[Asta growling]
[barking]
Don't move him, dad.
Man: Is that you, Nick?
- Brogan?
Brogan: Yeah.
- Where are you?
Brogan: Here in the bushes.
- Did you hear a shot?
- No.
That's funny.
Neither did i.
Why? Something
happen?
Nora: Nicky, what is it?
Oh, darling, it's Mr. Brogan.
Do you remember?
Nick: He was just coming
to call on us.
What's he doing
in the bushes?
Why, I... I... I...
He was lighting
a cigarette.
Will you come up
to the house with us?
A man's
just been shot.
Oh.
Nick: The bell rang,
I opened the door,
he keeled over.
Oh, mother, dad, this is an old
friend of mine Mr. Brogan.
How do you do,
Mrs. Charles?
doctor?
How do you
do, sir?
Time and tide
wait for no man.
Tsk tsk tsk tsk.
Nick, you better phone
Bruce Clayworth.
He's the official
coroner in this town.
He lives
just down the street.
Yes.
What's his number?
148.
You know, doctor,
this is just typical of Nick.
Wherever he goes,
you always find bodies.
It's just typical.
Is Dr. Clayworth there?
Just a moment.
Dr. Clayworth?
Man: Yes?
Phone for you.
Man: Alright.
Thank you, Miss Harling.
- Hello.
- Hello, Bruce.
This is Nick Charles.
A man's just been
shot over here.
What?
Well, who is it?
I don't know.
Would you notify
the police?
Sure, I will, Nick,
and i'll come
right over, too.
I'll be through here
in just a minute.
Now, Nick, I don't want
to seem too personal,
but if you're
going to tell me
you don't know anything
about this thing,
all i can say
is baloney.
Mac, it happened
just as i said.
The bell rang.
I went to the door.
The boy started to say
something and was shot.
- Did you ever see him before?
- No.
The name's
Peter Berton.
Yes, I know.
I know that, Dr. Charles.
Well, I was
just telling you.
He lives
at Tom's Auto Court.
I know that, too.
Just because you've gotten
used to me, Dr. Charles,
doesn't mean
i haven't got any brain.
I can handle more than
traffic problems, you know.
Then handle it, and
let's get it over with.
I'm not used to policemen
in my living room
or people messing around
in my laboratory.
I like peace and quiet.
Brogan: Good for you,
Dr. Charles.
Tennyson says,
"Peace shall pipe
on her pastoral hill
a languid note
and watch
her harvest ripen.”
"Thanksgiving."
MacGregor: Nick, did it
ever occur to you
that somebody might
have been trying
to take a potshot at you
and hit
the boy instead?
Well, that's
an angle.
You know,
he might have taken
a shot
at you and missed.
And a miss
is as good as a mile.
Mr. Brogan, if it isn't
too much trouble,
would you mind telling
me where you came from?
Why, I'm a friend
of Nick's. Get it?
And i was just
passing by. Get it?
So i thought
i'd just stop in.
Nora: Get it?
Do you usually
drop in the bushes?
Well, can't a fella stop
to light a cigarette?
If Mr. Charles can be
of any help to you,
Mr. MacGregor,
I'm sure he'd be
only too glad.
Oh, I'm
on a vacation.
Besides, you
can't just barge in
on another man's
case.
You could be called in
as a specialist.
- Couldn't he, father?
- Well, I'm not so sure.
Mother: Of course a man could be
called in as a specialist.
You told me so yourself.
Well, if i need any help,
I'll ask for it.
That's
the right spirit.
And the safety
of this community
couldn't be
in better hands.
Who'd like some cider?
Nick? Oh, Nick.
Here's the bullet.
I don't know much
about such things,
but i imagine that
was fired from a .45
or something
in that general field.
Hmm... well,
give it to Mac.
It's his show.
Thanks.
I'll send this
to a good
ballistics expert.
Nora: Nick's a good
I'm a ballistics expert
who's on a vacation.
Who'll have cider?
Very little water
in mine.
Is the cider in here?
Yes, sir.
- Hilda.
- Yes, sir?
How about
some glasses?
Umm...
- Hilda.
- Yes, sir?
Suppose you do
the honors.
Yes, sir.
Man: Oh, thank you, sir.
- Yes, sir.
What's the idea?
We ain't had
a vacancy in two months.
You have now.
Peter Berton's
just been shot.
been shot?!
It's number 19
with a bath and shower.
I want to ask you
a few questions about him.
Know nothing
about him.
The less you notice
in this business,
the better it is.
Mum's the word
around here.
Mum's the word.
[door closes]
Well, I always said
something would
happen to that boy.
Yes? Why?
Bad-tempered and ornery.
He had a fight
the other night.
A fight, huh?
With whom?
Don't know the name.
The other fella ended up
with two black eyes,
like a raccoon.
What was
the fight about?
Can't say for sure,
but like as not,
it was over
that Laurabel Ronson.
She was traipsing
over here all the time.
[door opens]
I said
mum's the word.
Mum's what word?
[telephone rings]
Yep.
Nope.
- Was that MacGregor?
- Yep.
- Is he on his way?
Okay, because
when he comes,
- I'll be in number 19.
- Oh.
I hope you haven't
touched anything in there.
Nope.
We clean once a day
in the morning.
You two had better
stay here.
Woman: Yes, sir.
And remember,
mum's the word.
[door closes]
[dramatic music]
Nick: "Cubana Perfecto.”
[intense music]
Nick: "Boston Children's Home."
Hmm...
[intense music]
[thudding]
[clanging]
[winding clock]
Why don't you girls
go to bed?
I'm worried, Bertram.
Something might have
happened to him.
Nonsense. Nick's old enough
to take care of himself.
To think that i fell
for that cider routine.
He's probably got the case
half solved by now.
But where can he be?
He's probably turning
that auto camp upside-down.
Don't you think
it's possible
he might be turning
a drink upside-down?
Not on your tin time.
When Nick puts
his mind on a thing,
he never makes a false step.
[crash]
That's my boy.
Well, let's see,
Asta.
Where shall we put it?
I really shouldn't give him
a birthday present at all,
sneaking off like that
and getting drunk...
without me.
Hmm... running into
an old sweetheart.
If all his old sweethearts
were laid end to end,
I could use them
as a sidewalk.
[sniffing]
But he's
a pretty good guy.
He keeps us
in dog biscuits.
I hope he likes it.
"Ah. Nora, darling,
what a lovely surprise.”
Nick: Darling,
what time is it?
Uh, it's almost 11:00.
Whoo!
Oh, boy,
I am late.
♪ I've got a date ♪
[Kissing]
♪ Deep in the heart of Texas ♪
♪ Choose a tie ♪
♪ Then i must fly ♪
[Kissing]
♪ Deep in the heart of Texas ♪
[Nick continues singing]
Darling, where's my belt
with the gold buckle?
Buckle, buckle.
Who's got the buckle?
♪ Buckle down,
winsockie ♪
down, down ♪
There it is,
right in front of you.
Hmm?
[chuckles]
[Kissing]
♪ Deep in the heart of Texas ♪
Some detective.
♪ Deep in the heart
of Texas ♪
[Nick continues singing]
♪ Good-bye, mama ♪
♪ I'm off to Yokohama ♪
[Kissing]
♪ Deep in the heart... ♪
Nicky, what is this sudden
epidemic of kisses for?
For my birthday.
Remember?
[laughing]
♪ Deep in the heart of... ♪
Uh-oh.
You know what that is?
Remember that old mill
i pointed out to you
from the baggage car?
Well, that's it.
Ooh, what a pain in the neck
that turned out to be.
Full of snakes, skunks,
poison ivy,
and a truant officer.
Gives me the shudders
just to look at it.
[Nick singing]
Hilda, take this out
and burn it.
- Don't you like it?
- No.
Can't say i blame you.
Why, Hilda, what are you
doing with that picture?
Mrs. Charles
told me to burn it.
Oh, let me see.
Why, I think
it's very pretty.
It's just
the thing to give
to the bazaar
at the hotel.
It's alright with me.
I'll tell miss Laurabel
you're here.
Thank you.
Maid: Miss Laurabel.
Miss Laurabel.
I hope i'm not
disturbing you, Miss Ronson.
No. It's alright.
You came to talk to me
about Peter Berton, didn't you?
Yes. And you're
very brave to see me
at a time like this.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
People are born.
People die.
Life goes on.
Poor Peter.
"At least he's outsoared
the shadow of our night.
Envy, pain, and hate
can touch him not."
That's Shelley.
I always turn
to the poets
for comfort
in all my sorrow.
Yeah. Me, too.
Now, about Peter...
I just wanted to ask
you a few things
about his friends,
his family.
He was alone.
He had only me.
Oh. Well, uh...
he must have talked
about his family, though,
his childhood.
He talked of nothing.
Our souls
and spirits communed.
Words would have been
empty, meaningless.
Yes, I can
understand that.
Cigarette,
Mr. Charles?
Oh, thank you,
no.
A cigar?
I rather lost interest
in cigars.
Oh, father has
some very good ones...
a special brand he
keeps all for himself.
Oh, a special brand.
Yes. Won't you
try one?
Nick: "Cubana perfecto.” Hmm...
Well, yes, yes.
This does
interest me.
[sniffs]
Thank you.
You and Peter saw
quite a good deal
of each other, huh?
Yes. Fellow
artists, you know.
That fight he got into
recently must have been
rather distressing
to you, wasn't it?
- Fight?
- Yes.
He gave somebody
a pair of black eyes.
I know absolutely
nothing about that.
Is that so? Hmm...
Your father didn't
approve of Peter, did he?
Poor dad.
So provincial,
you know.
He just didn't
understand.
Oh, I tried again and again
to explain to him
how platonic
and beautiful it was,
but he just
made scenes.
I thought
he was going to have
a stroke or something.
Oh, it was awful.
Nick: You poor child.
Oh, and it wasn't
only dad.
No one understood what Peter
and i meant to each other.
Why, Tom Clayworth made
such a fuss if i even...
Oh, well, you wouldn't
be interested in all that.
On the contrary.
What about Tom?
Well, you know
what an emotional type Tom is,
and so jealous.
Why, if he heard
i even spoke to Peter,
he'd hit
the ceiling.
Did he ever
hit Peter?
Oh, no.
Were you afraid
he might?
Well, you see...
Oh, Mr. Charles.
Tom had nothing to do
with Peter's death.
I know that.
Mm-hmm. But the last time
you went out to see Peter,
wasn't it to warn him
that Tom was jealous,
perhaps made threats?
You're quite wrong,
Mr. Charles.
Was it to warn him
against your father?
My father?
Yes. He didn't want
you to see Peter.
He made violent
scenes about it.
You told me so.
You... you tricked me
into telling you that.
Tricked you?
Say, what do you think
this is, Miss Ronson,
a parlor game?
A man has been
murdered.
Your father threatened
Peter, didn't he?
No, that isn't true.
You must believe me!
I swear it!
- I believe you.
- No, you don't.
You're just trying to trick me
into telling you more.
Well, I won't!
And i won't listen
to your accusations!
Get out!
Go on! Get out!
Oh!
I'm sorry if i upset her,
Mr. Ronson.
What do you
want here?
I wanted to talk to Laurabel
about Peter Berton.
What about
Peter Berton?
Well, for one thing,
he's dead.
And you think
my daughter killed him?
Well, no, but, uh...
I wanted to ask her
a few things about him...
who his friends were
and who his enemies were.
Why did you object to him seeing
your daughter, Mr. Ronson?
- Who says i objected?
- Your daughter.
I'm not responsible
for what Laurabel says.
She's a girl with a very
vivid imagination.
Why should i
object to him?
That's what i
would like to know.
Now, look here, Charles.
I'm just as interested
in seeing justice
done as you are,
but i think you
ought to be careful.
I know that you don't want
to hurt innocent people.
You don't want to damage
good reputations needlessly.
That might be harmful
to the whole community.
Your own family,
your own father
might have
ambitions and plans
that could be ruined.
You mean my father's
ambition for a hospital
might be blocked?
Just think
that over, Charles.
Yes.
I will think it over,
Mr. Ronson.
I will, indeed.
And i'll also
think over
what you were doing
in Peter Berton's cabin
the day he was killed.
Good day.
[door closes]
Well, how are you, Mac?
Right on the job, I see.
Say, that was a dirty trick,
changing those numbers.
I didn't find out i
was in the wrong cabin
till this morning.
That was just
the Halloween in me.
Well, this
isn't Halloween.
Say, I thought you
were on a vacation.
Oh, I just thought
i'd help a bit.
Well, you didn't happen to
run into anything, did you?
Are you keeping
an eye on Crazy Mary?
Why Crazy Mary?
Well, as i remember,
she used to go
on the warpath
at times, didn't she?
Say, how does anybody
ever get into her shack
to talk with her?
Nobody ever does,
except Doc Clayworth.
Last time
i was out there,
I got conked in the head
with a coffeepot.
- No?
- Say, talking of the devil.
Bruce: Hello, Nick.
- Hiya, Bruce.
- Hello, Mac.
- How are you, doc?
I was just telling Nick
you're about the only one
could get him in
to talk to Crazy Mary.
Oh, sure.
Anytime, Nick.
Thanks. How did
the autopsy come out?
We found that that bullet
entered the boy's back
through the large
rhomboid on the left
and was stopped
by his sternocostal
joint on the right.
Hmm...
That tells us a lot,
doesn't it?
Yeah. Does it?
Well, Mac, keep pitching.
Bad ones. Always gave me
his bad pictures to sell,
never his good ones.
Just...higgledy-piggledy,
that's what he was, yes.
You know, artists
are all like that.
They keep their good pictures
and sell their bad ones.
It seems a good artist
is just naturally...
higgledy-piggledy.
Maybe that's why
he's a good artist.
Or maybe it's reversed.
How much did you usually
get for his paintings?
Whose paintings?
Well, the boy we're
talking about...
higgledy-piggledy.
Oh, yes. That one.
$50 a picture.
Could you have gotten
more for his better ones?
Oh, gracious me, yes.
Twice as much.
Three times.
I guess the boy
was loaded, huh?
He was what?
He had no economic
problems, hmm?
Or else maybe he was
just, you know...
Uh...
Yes.
Higgledy-piggledy,
huh?
Yes, I'm sure
he must have been.
Well, thank you
very much.
Good-bye now.
Beg your pardon?
I said
good-bye now.
"Good-bye now?"
There's no sense to that.
Obviously it's now.
I mean,
you wouldn't say,
"Good-bye tomorrow"
or "Good-bye two hours ago."
You've got hold of
something there, brother.
I've got hold
of something...
I haven't got
hold of anything.
And i'm not your brother!
If he's here
on official business,
why doesn't he let
somebody know about it?
Why the mystery?
Besides, we have
a perfectly good
police department
of our own.
Well, what do you
want me to do?
I just want to give you
a word of advice.
I have reason
to believe
that Mr. Ronson is
not at all pleased
with his interfering
in people's lives.
It's upsetting
the town.
It might be better
if you asked him to leave.
Leave?
But he's my son.
He's just
a meddling fool.
That's what he is.
Did Ronson say that?
No, no, no.
That's my opinion.
Have you talked
with Ronson about this?
No, but i have
reason to believe...
What you believe
doesn't interest me.
I think
i'll be leaving.
I think you're making
a great mistake, doctor.
You've been working on
that hospital project
of yours for years.
I know your heart's
set on it,
and it's practically
a reality now.
It would be a shame
if, at the last minute,
it fell through.
Tatum, I think
you're a stinker.
[crying]
I think Tatum is a two-timing,
double-crossing rat.
Now, now, now,
mother. Mother.
We mustn't spoil
Nick's birthday.
Now, you must smile.
Now, smile.
No, no, no.
Nice, pretty smile.
That's right.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday,
dear Nicky ♪
♪ We're glad to see you ♪
Oh! That's
beautiful, ma.
Thanks, dad.
Oh, that's
lovely, mother.
One, two, three, four...
Ah. Don't be a cad.
Why, this
makes me feel
as if i were
in short pants again.
That i want to see.
[chuckles]
Here goes.
Oh, make a wish.
Oh, yes. Alright.
Here's luck
to dad's hospital.
You shouldn't
tell your wish.
It may not
come true.
Well, this one will.
Hang onto your hats.
[Hilda screaming]
A man!
There was a man!
- Where?
- In your room!
Who was it,
Hilda?
Hilda: It was dark!
I couldn't see!
I walked in,
and there he was!
Oh...
Oh!
[crash]
[screaming]
What happened?
It was the table you fixed.
It's fainted again.
[Asta barking]
Come out of there.
It's me, Nick.
For the love of...
Did you see anyone?
No. I just stepped
into the bushes for a minute.
- Why, Brogan...
- Why? What's up?
Somebody's been
casing my room.
Gee, I must
have missed him.
You certainly did.
I'm sorry, Nick,
but i got the dope
from Boston.
You were right
about the kid.
I got it all
written out here.
Nora: Nick.
Nick: Oh, it's
Mr. Brogan, dear.
I can let you have this lot
at a dollar a dozen.
Good evening,
Mrs. Charles.
Lighting
a cigarette again?
Well, no, no.
I was just going to
ask him to have
some cake with us.
Of course.
He can't stay
out here
in the bushes.
Well, there's tricks
to every trade,
as the saying goes.
I had
3,000 maternity cards
announcing the birth
of a baby girl.
All of a sudden,
everybody starts having boys.
Here i am,
stuck with a lot of cards.
It was practically impossible
to sell boys' cards
for girls' cards,
especially when the picture
was of a stork
wearing a high hat
with a diaper
in his mouth.
The diaper was what we call
a breakaway. Get it?
[laughing]
Nicky, how long have
you known Brogan?
Darling, did i tell you
how pretty you look
for my birthday dinner?
No, you didn't.
Nicky, has Brogan
got a police record?
Well, I meant
to tell you.
Honey, your hair
is tinged
with the russet shades
of beautiful autumn.
Look, you're holding
something back about Brogan.
He's a definite
criminal type.
I can tell by the shape
of his head.
Well, yes, there was
a little something
about an old lady who was
found in a trunk once.
Uh-huh!
And your ears are like
the twin petals
of a budding rose.
Later, darling.
Now, look.
I've got this
all figured out.
Brogan was in the bushes
the night the murder
was committed.
Check?
He was in the bushes
again tonight
when our room
was ransacked.
Double check.
Nicky, he's our man,
and something's
got to be done.
And that's not it.
Not even on my birthday?
Oh, well.
Oh, darling,
don't you see?
He'll get away
if you don't get busy.
I'm on my vacation.
Oh, Nicky, you're
driving me crazy.
This case
is serious,
and all you do is fuddle around
and guzzle cider.
I'll switch
to prune juice.
Alright. If you're going
to neglect your duty,
I'm not.
Brogan is
mixed up in this,
and i'm going to
find out how and why.
Bertram: Mr. Brogan,
have you any greeting cards
for a man going to bed?
No, but...
Well, you better
start working on them,
because that's
where i'm going.
I guess i'd better
mosey along, too.
Excuse me.
Must you go,
Mr. Brogan?
There's still
some cake left.
Thank you,
Mrs. Charles,
but you know
the old saying...
a man's eyes are often
bigger than his belly.
[laughing]
Good night.
What a nice man.
I didn't mean to talk business
at your party, Nick.
But you know
there's many a slip
twixt the cup
and the lip.
Nora knows who committed
the murder.
- Yeah? Who?
- You.
Me?
Boy, that is
interesting.
Look, I think she's
going to trail you, see?
So, give her
a little exercise.
Take her for
a nice, long walk.
I've got something
i want to do.
I get it.
Nicky, I think i'll go
for a little walk.
Want me to go
with you?
No, no. I'm just going
to the drugstore.
Good night,
Nicky.
Oh, good night,
darling.
Now, try to get
to bed early.
You know me.
Hello, Bruce?
Nick Charles.
Uh, busy?
How'd you like to take me
out to Crazy Mary's?
Nick, remember when we used
to come up here fishing?
Yeah.
Boy, you sure
caught the big ones.
It's all in the flick
of the wrist.
I guess i never did
flick right.
You better stay in the car
till i call her.
You're liable to get
conked on the head.
Oh, Mary.
Yoo-hoo. Mary.
It's me, Dr. Clayworth.
Hello, Mary.
I just want to
talk to you for
a minute, huh?
Get out of here.
Get out!
Now, now, Mary.
Nobody's going to hurt you.
I don't want him
around here.
Why didn't you tell me
he was with you?
Get him out.
Now, he just wants to
ask you a few questions.
I'm not answering
any questions.
You leave me alone.
Do you hear?
I don't want to answer
any questions.
Now get out.
I want to talk to you
about Eleanor Morgan.
Eleanor Morgan?
I have a lot of
information, Mary,
from Boston.
You know about
Eleanor Morgan?
Yes.
Nobody knows
about Eleanor Morgan.
I do, Mary.
[sobs]
Peter know you were
his mother, Mary?
Mary: No.
But i watched over him
best i could.
Sure, you did.
Who do you think
killed him?
How should i know?
He had a fight with somebody
out at the auto camp,
gave him a couple
of black eyes.
Who was that?
Bill Burns
out at the plant.
What was
the fight about?
I ain"t gonna tell you nothing.
Now get out of here.
I'm trying to
help you, Mary.
Nobody's trying to help me.
They're all against me.
I know what they're after,
and they're not going to get it.
I'll get it first
because i know somebody
that'll get it for me.
If anybody else
comes nosing around,
they're going to get
something they don't like!
Now get out!
Now, now.
Alright, Mary.
Alright, we're going.
We're going.
Holy smoke.
Peter Berton's mother?
Mm-hmm.
Where does
the Eleanor Morgan come in?
That's the name she used
at the hospital in Boston
where he was born.
And later, when
she turned him over
to the children's home,
she used Berton.
Oh.
[vehicle approaching]
Hiya, Mac.
What delayed you?
For a guy who's
on his vacation,
you certainly
buzz around a lot.
I was looking
for you, Bruce.
I wanted you to come
out here with me.
Nick tried,
but he couldn't get anything.
Oh, yeah? Well, I'll get
something out of her.
He got something
out of her.
There. Okay?
Whoa.
[chuckles]
Hello.
- Hi.
- How are you?
Hi, cutie.
Hiya, babe.
Hello, sister.
Gentlemen...
Man: Say, ain't you with
that new burlesque show
down at The Grand?
There's my uncle.
I've got to go now.
Good-bye, cutie.
Good-bye.
Man: Yes, sir?
Oh, let's see now.
Where was i going?
Oh, yes. What time's
the next train to New York?
10:14.
Thank you.
That man who
was just here...
he was asking about
a train, wasn't he?
Yes, ma'am.
The 10:14 to New York.
Oh.
Give me a cup of coffee
and two aspirins.
Hello,
Mr. MacGregor.
I'm so glad
you're here.
Always glad to see a member
of the Charles family.
There's a man here.
I want you to arrest him.
What for?
Does it have to be
for something?
Oh, no. No.
You just pick out
anybody at all,
and i put them
in jail for life.
But this man's
going to leave town.
Look, Mrs. Charles,
I had a little business
with your husband
a while ago,
and i got a big
headache out of it.
I can't arrest
anybody for you
unless they do something
to get arrested.
Get that?
They got to do something.
I think you're being very
technical, Mr. MacGregor.
Make that four aspirin.
[wolf whistles]
Jeez, lady,
what's the idea?
Looking for somebody,
sister?
[men whistling]
Say, what have you
got against me?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Sorry, lady,
but we don't allow
no unescorted
females in here.
Isn't that an old-fashioned
point of view?
I mean, after all,
times have changed.
She's with me,
bartender.
Two beers,
and hurry it up.
I hope you don't mind
my barging in like this.
Oh, that's
quite alright.
Pool rooms
are so informal.
Well, I wanted
to talk to you.
You see, as a matter
of fact,
I've been
following you.
You've been
following me?
Ever since you
left the house.
It's silly. I know.
But my wife has got her
heart set on a picture,
one you bought
at the Crump Art Shop,
and i'd like to buy
that painting from you.
Painting?
Oh, the windmill.
Yes. Personally,
I don't like it,
but my wife
is keen about it,
so i'm prepared
to pay you a good price.
A good price?
Say, $500.
$500? Well, I only
paid $60 for it.
You can't make any money
paying $500 for a $60 painting.
Well, money doesn't
matter when it comes
to making the little
woman happy.
That's a fine quality
in a husband, mister...
Draque.
Edgar Draque.
Then it's a deal?
Well...
Fine. Can i get
the painting now?
Not now. I'll get it
for you later.
I'll bring it to you.
Well, I'd like to get it
as soon as possible.
I'm stopping at
the Sycamore Springs Hotel.
If you'd care to...
The Sycamore Springs Hotel...
That's where they're
holding the Charity Bazaar.
That's right.
I have to leave town tonight,
and i'd like to get
the painting before i go.
You beast!
This man insulted me!
Break it up!
Hold it, you guys!
Break it up there!
My, my.
[commotion]
Uh, get me the police
department, please.
There's no use
denying it.
You did have a fight
with Peter Berton.
Yeah.
Hmm. Looks to me
as if you got more
than your share.
All i'm asking is,
what was
the fight about?
Well, Mr. Charles,
it seems to me
that's nobody's business
but Berton's and mine.
Now that he's dead,
it's only mine.
Why didn't you like him?
Well, I like people
that are straightforward
and honest.
I want to be able
to peg them.
If i can't peg them,
I don't like them.
I see.
Well, if that's all
you're going to ask me,
I think i'll be
going along.
The fact
that the boy's dead
doesn't seem to have made
very much impression on you.
Why should it?
Death hasn't
endowed him
with any new
virtues, has it?
Well, that's a little brutal,
but, uh, honest.
Do you, uh...
do you know of anyone
who might have had
cause to Kill him?
The way he was cutting throats
at the plant,
there might have been
a number of people.
What about you?
Mr. Charles, when you've
got anything on me,
you can serve
your papers,
but until that time,
I figure my time
is my own.
What did he want?
He just wanted to
ask me a few questions.
Questions about what?
Come on, Asta.
[vehicle approaching]
Nicky, come on.
Come on.
- Huh?
- Don't stand there stargazing.
- We've got to hurry.
- Hurry? Where to?
We're going to a dance.
He offered me $500 for it.
$500 for a dance?
And it was right there
under your nose
all the time, too.
- Under my nose?
- Nicky, we've got to hurry.
I had him thrown in jail,
but he might get out,
and then he'd get
the painting.
Jail? Painting?
Sycamore Springs Hotel.
I figured as long
as i had one man arrested,
I might as well have
him locked up, too.
Did you do all this
on cider?
[ballroom music]
I thought you'd be
proud of me,
killing two birds
with one stone.
Two birds?
Yes. They're both in jail.
- Who's the other?
- Brogan.
- Brogan's in jail?
- Yes.
[indistinct chatter]
Nick: I'll split my business
up among you...
a gift to the boys.
Good evening,
Mr. Charles.
Hello.
I bet you think
i'm a silly little girl
for behaving the way
i did at the house.
You were perfectly right
to be angry with me.
I'm not angry with you.
Oh, aren't you really?
No. Here. I'll
prove it to you.
I'll take
all your tickets.
You can prove it
even better
by dancing with me.
Alright, put me
down for a dance.
Oh, do you jitterbug?
No. Put me down
for a slow polka.
Was that necessary?
Do you have to shine up
to him like that?
Oh, Tom,
you're impossible.
Nicky, it's gone.
Huh? What's gone?
The painting i gave you.
The painting you gave me?
I mean, the painting
i didn't give you.
The paint... come again?
For your birthday.
The painting that you gave me
but you didn't give me...
[ululating]
I beg your pardon.
I didn't understand.
Gracious me! What are you
doing in here?
Don't you remember me?
I'm looking for the
painting of the windmill.
The windmill?
Everybody's looking
for the painting
of the windmill.
Now, you get
out of here.
Goodness gracious!
All a painter has
to do nowadays
is to get killed
and suddenly
becomes a genius.
Did you say
the painter was killed?
Yes. Peter Berton,
all higgledy-piggledy.
Was that painting
by Peter Berton?
Gracious me, yes.
Everybody's been
after that painting.
First the blonde,
then Sam Ronson, and now you.
- Sam Ronson?
- Yes.
Well, where is it?
I sold it to the blonde.
Mr. Crump, what was
the blonde's name?
Mrs. Edgar Draque.
Crump: She lives here
in the hotel.
Draque. That's
the name of the man
who offered me
the $500.
- Uh... wait here.
- Where are you going?
I want to do a little business
with the blonde.
You think she'll
give it to you?
I can try, darling.
Anything for art.
I'll be right back.
No. I think i'll go
along and chaperone.
Well, uh...
Oh, hello, sailor.
Why aren't you
dancing?
I haven't got
any dance tickets.
No dance tickets?
Well, of course you have.
[chuckles]
There you are,
and here's your partner.
Gee, thanks.
Nicky!
[instrumental music]
Uh, what's the number
of Mr. Draque's room?
One-twenty-four.
One-twenty-four. Thanks.
- Good evening, Mr. Charles.
- Good evening, Willoughby.
Hello.
I see you've decided
to stay in town.
I never had any
intention of leaving.
- By the way, Tatum...
- Yeah?
When the hospital's built,
you must come in
and have my father
treat your nose.
There's nothing wrong
with my nose.
There will be.
[knocks]
Oh, pardon me.
Come in.
Come in, dear.
It's Mrs. Draque.
How do you do,
Mrs. Draque?
Well, you certainly
got right down to business.
I found her on the floor.
She was out cold.
Somebody had conked her
before i got here.
What about
the painting?
It's gone.
We're going after it.
I'm glad to have met you,
Mrs. Draque.
- Clerk.
- Yes, sir?
You better have someone
go up to 124.
What's wrong?
Mrs. Draque
is... indisposed.
Alright.
Now, let me think.
Ah, let's see.
Peter Berton painted it.
Everybody wanted it.
Draque offered 500.
Mrs. Draque got it.
She got conked.
Hmm... let's see, now.
Who else wanted it?
Crazy Mary said
she knew somebody
who would get it for her.
That might be it.
There's Ronson.
Ronson. Ronson said
he wanted it, too.
Yes.
There's the doc.
Bruce. Excuse me.
Are you busy?
Well, we're going
to have a dance.
Say, how would you
like to take me
for another little ride?
Well, I'd like to, but...
Oh, that's fine.
Come on, let's go.
Where are we going?
Crazy Mary's.
That's where we belong.
Come on, Asta.
Nora: Dr. Clayworth
is going to miss all the dances.
Don't worry about me.
I'm not much
of a dancer anyway.
Nick was the one
the girls always
wanted to dance with.
I hear he also
played the banjo.
She's dead.
Nicky. Nicky, look.
Shot with her own gun.
Hey, that's one way
of destroying
fingerprints, huh?
It certainly is, yes.
We'd better call MacGregor.
[Asta barking]
Asta.
Nora: Asta, what is it?
[barking continues]
Nora: That's it!
Your birthday present.
Asta, you'll get
an extra bone for this.
[growling playfully]
Nicky.
Hey, what are you
doing up this hour?
I came down
to ask you that.
Well, I was still concentrating
on this little gem.
Funny thing to concentrate on
at this hour of the night.
Why don't you tackle it in
the morning when you're fresher?
Say, you're pretty
fresh right now.
You know, this has
to be solved by morning.
We're in
the home stretch.
How's it look
for the finish?
Well, I'm not passing out
any tips just yet.
A secret.
Mm-hmm.
Worried?
Say, you are
worried, aren't you?
Oh, I've handled
trickier shows than this.
But your old man wasn't
in the audience watching you.
That's it, isn't it?
Or a part of it, anyway.
Hmm.
Ah. You'll get it.
You may not be any great
shakes as a detective,
but you're lucky.
You'll solve it.
And your father will
be proud of you.
Mm-hmm.
He'd better be,
unless he wants to hear
that Stinky Davis
story again.
Oh, no, no, no.
Not that, dear. Not that.
I'll be waiting
for you, darling.
Good luck.
I'll need it, sister.
And don't call me sister.
Mother: Sit down.
Make yourself comfortable.
I demand to know
why we were brought here.
Nick Charles' orders.
I demand to see Nick Charles.
Where is he?
Search me.
I demand to know
what those people
are doing in
my laboratory.
I don't know.
- Where's Nick Charles?
- I don't know.
You don't know
much, do you?
No, but
don't have to.
Mrs. Green's
little boy
has just swallowed
50 cents.
[doorbell buzzes]
I'll get it, Hilda.
Hello, sister.
Nick Charles here?
- Who wants him?
- Yeah, who wants him?
Is your name sister?
Where's Nick Charles?
He's a friend of ours.
What do you want?
Pull in your ears, pop.
Now, listen, you.
You behave yourself.
You leave him alone.
Look, bub,
he sent for us.
What's your names?
My name's
Slugs Lonnegan.
His is Finnigan.
Mickey to you.
Yeah.
Why didn't you say so?
Go on in there
and sit down.
And keep quiet.
Is it always
like this, Nora?
Always.
You have
my deepest sympathy.
Mrs. Charles,
where is your husband?
I don't know.
Why don't you sit down
and take it easy, Mr. Ronson?
I'll just make some cocoa
to quiet their nerves.
Cocoa? What a break.
Ronson: I'd like to know
why it's necessary
to herd us all
into a room like this.
For a very simple
reason, Mr. Ronson.
This is the way
he always works,
and this time, he has
a very special reason.
Whatever he does, no matter
how idiotic it may seem,
nobody ever
outguesses him for long.
Just wait. You're going to be
mighty proud of him.
I've seen him work
on situations like this
that look
completely hopeless,
when suddenly the guilty
party cracks up
and starts trying
to shoot his way out.
But he's not going
to turn this place
into a shooting gallery?
That's the way these
things usually wind up.
It's called the payoff.
I usually duck under
the sofa when it starts.
It's outrageous,
treating people in this
high-handed fashion.
Where is he?
Oh, he's probably
arranging
a few surprises for us.
Right now, it may be part
of a strategy of nerves
to keep us all on edge,
but when the stage
is set,
he'll make
a dramatic entrance.
I'm usually nervous, too,
but this time i'm not.
You see,
I know who it is.
You do?
Well, who is it?
Wouldn't you like to know?
Ah.
There he is.
And mighty beautiful
timing, I'd say.
Hiya, Slugs, Mickey.
Got them, huh?
All here.
Good. Suppose you
unwrap them, huh?
Sure.
Sorry i had to keep
you all waiting.
I just want to ask you
a very few simple questions...
nothing really difficult
or involved,
just some little things,
and i'm sure you will all
want to help.
Mr. Draque,
you like it?
A genuine Berton,
Mrs. Draque.
By the way,
how's your head?
That mean anything
to you, Willoughby?
To me, no.
It will.
Mr. Ronson, does it
mean anything to you?
No.
- Sure?
- Of course i am.
Alright.
I'm just asking.
Uh-oh.
Ronson's cooked.
Mr. Crump, does that
mean anything to you?
Gracious me, yes.
Squidgey, isn't it?
Mmm, worse than that.
Precisely,
yes, yes, yes.
Now i'm about to demonstrate
something to you,
and in order to do it,
the room will have to be dark.
I hope you don't mind my taking
a few ordinary precautions,
but sometimes
people have a habit
of carrying firearms.
So, Mac, will you take over?
Everybody's
going to be searched.
Frisk them.
He can't do that.
There won't be any payoff.
Now, look here.
This is going too far.
Nick, stop being absurd.
These people
aren't criminals.
They're respectable
citizens.
They don't walk
around with guns.
MacGregor: Here's one.
As superintendent
at the plant,
I handle the payrolls,
and i need it
for protection.
This is a .45 army colt.
That's the same kind of a gun
killed Peter Berton.
Let me out of here!
I've got to get out of here!
Wait a minute.
Take it easy.
You can't hold me.
You've got nothing against me.
I've got a very important
appointment.
Well, your appointment
will have to wait.
It can't wait.
Really, it can't.
With whom was
your appointment?
I can't tell you.
Well, I'm afraid
you'll have to stay, then.
I wonder
if she's acting.
Hmm?
Where'd you get this?
That? I bought that
at an auction.
It's just an antique.
You can't fire it.
[gunshot]
Just an antique, huh?
Here's another one.
Well, quite an arsenal
for a peaceful community.
MacGregor: Well,
what's your story?
Tatum: Why... I need it,
working around the bank.
Well, we're not around
the bank now, Mr. Tatum.
So i'm sure you can
spare it
for a few minutes.
Charles, if you can't
vindicate these actions,
I'll see that you
go to jail.
I'll keep that
in mind, Mr. Ronson.
Now, dad, I'm going to use
your fluoroscope for a moment.
Alright.
Slugs, will you close
those curtains, please?
And, Mickey,
you might keep an eye
on the Draque family.
Now, if you'll all gather around
the fluoroscope here,
I'll proceed
to the demonstration.
Mr. Ronson, just move
in here close, will you?
Yes, and you, too, Willoughby.
And Bill Burns.
Alright, now if someone
will just close those curtains.
Nick: All set?
- Anybody know what that is?
- Golly!
Nora: I got a bargain...
two pictures.
Nick: And i don't mean
the windmill
or this little dog
down here in the corner.
Look closely.
Willoughby, don't you
recognize that?
Good heavens.
Holy smokes.
Alright,
open the curtains.
Well, Willoughby...
Why, it's part of the plans
for the propeller.
That's right.
A foreign power
would pay a lot
of money for that.
They couldn't be stolen.
Why not? This was.
We've protected
ourselves against it.
The plans are divided
into five different parts.
Nobody is allowed
to see or to work
on more than one part.
Is that so?
Oh, slugs, let's have
those other four paintings.
Here they are, Nick.
And, uh, tell them
where you got them.
Why, where
you told me...
in Anthony Croner's
art gallery in New York.
Anthony Croner, known
to his intimates as Tony.
Make a note
of that, Mr. Draque.
Oh, Mr. Crump,
you recognize these?
Oh, gracious me.
Yes. Well, those
are the pictures
I sold to her.
Thank you.
Under these four
innocent-looking paintings
are the designs
for the other parts
of your propeller.
Surprised?
Yes, I am.
Bill, will you
tell me now
why you fought
with Peter Berton?
Well, he tried to
push me out of my job,
always making trouble.
What kind of trouble?
Angling for
somebody else's job.
He was always
doing that.
He should have
been fired.
Why wasn't he?
That's what
i'd like to know.
He must have had
a drag somewhere.
Willoughby
would just switch him
from one
department to another.
Nick: Hmm...
See what i mean?
The finger's on him now.
But my money's
on Brogan.
[door opens]
Thank you.
Oh, I'm sorry
to be late, Nick.
I was up
at Mrs. Stanton's.
You know, that
baby's about due.
Oh. Well, I'm glad
you came, Bruce.
I'm going to need you.
Shall we search him
for weapons, too?
Sure. Everybody's
doing it.
Well, I surrender.
- Uh-oh.
- Here's something.
Is that loaded?
Just with blanks.
Bruce, we're trying
to get all the facts
about Peter Berton...
how he lived
and how he died.
By the way,
when i phoned you
right after
Berton was shot,
where were you
in your house?
Well, let's see.
Oh, sure, I remember.
I was working
on my stamp collection
all that evening
in my study.
Hmm. No one disturbed you
during the evening?
No. Well, I had
one patient.
Ah. But you didn't
hear the shot?
- No, I didn't.
- No.
Alright, Willoughby,
maybe you'd like
to explain to us now
about Berton.
Well, the boy just didn't seem
to get along with people.
You could have discharged him,
couldn't you?
Yes. But he seemed
such a nice, honest chap.
Ah.
Well, he was
a very good workman.
Why don't you tell
the truth, Willoughby?
You were told
to take care of him.
You had orders.
Orders from whom?
From someone higher up,
someone on the board
of directors...
Mr. Ronson.
I gave no orders.
The boy was
recommended to me,
and i asked Willoughby
to look after him. That's all.
Come on, Willoughby.
You better speak up.
I refuse to be held
responsible for this.
I wanted to let him go.
Mr. Ronson wouldn't let me.
That's a lie!
Oh, is it,
Mr. Ronson?
I think we both know
better than that.
Bruce, what time was it
when we got out
to Crazy Mary's last night?
- You mean, the last time?
- Yes.
About midnight.
And about how long would
you say she'd been dead?
About half an hour.
Certainly not more
than an hour.
Ah. How does that
check with you, Mr. Ronson?
With me?
What do i know about it?
You ought to know. You were
in her shack last night.
I...in her shack?
Certainly, after you
bopped Mrs. Draque on the head.
Sit down,
goldilocks.
You bopped her on the head,
grabbed this painting,
and took it
out to Crazy Mary's.
I never heard
anything so absurd.
Look here, Nick.
You're making some rather
serious accusations.
Sam Ronson wouldn't do
a thing like that.
Dad, I know this is going
to sound a little fantastic,
but i'm going to tell you
a little fairy tale.
Once upon a time
in this town,
oh, about 20-odd
years ago,
a local playboy
ran off to Boston
with a young housemaid
to get married.
Unfortunately,
the housemaid
wasn't quite right
in the head.
Well, in Boston,
the playboy
got into a barroom brawl
and was Killed,
leaving the housemaid
in a very tough spot.
Seems a baby
was on the way.
Now, the dead playboy
had a big brother,
but brother wanted
no part of it.
So, the housemaid
had to go
to a county hospital in Boston
to have her baby,
and the records
show that later,
she placed him in
a children's home there
under the name
of Peter Berton.
Shall i go on,
Mr. Ronson?
No. No, you win, Nick.
Perhaps you'd rather
tell us about it yourself.
I tried to help her,
but she was so...
so irrational.
The boy grew up
in the orphanage.
When he was of age,
I sent for him
and got him a job
here in the plant.
He didn't seem quite
well-balanced to me,
but Crazy Mary
kept hounding me.
I didn't want any scandal,
for my daughter's sake.
Well, everything
went on alright
until Crazy Mary
discovered that her boy
was mixed up in a racket
to copy some
propeller designs.
She wanted to stop him,
but she was helpless
without revealing to him
that she was his mother.
However, when the boy
up and got himself killed,
there was something
she could do.
She could protect
his good name.
So, she blackmailed
Mr. Ronson
into removing the evidence
against her boy...
this painting.
He took it to her
last night
after he removed it
from Mrs. Draque's room.
Is that true, Mr. Ronson?
Yes, but i didn't
kill Crazy Mary.
No, but you slugged me!
Why, you
small-town thug!
Ah!
Now, now, Mrs. Draque.
Just keep on doing
what you've been doing.
I'll have the cocoa
in a few minutes.
Well, now we know
the technique
that was used to deliver
these paintings.
Berton copied the plans,
painted over them,
and placed the paintings
for sale with Willy Crump.
Mrs. Draque bought them,
and through her husband,
they were delivered
at Tony Croner's in New York...
a nice, safe
arrangement,
very little danger
and lots of money
in it for everybody,
thousands.
What?
Does that surprise
you, Mrs. Draque?
Tell him
nothing, honey.
You mean you haven't
told your honey
just how many thousands
Croner gave you
every time you delivered
one of these paintings
to his gallery?
That's a lie.
Well, I just
don't think
you should have been
cheated, Mrs. Draque.
After all,
you took a big risk,
and now you're
involved in a murder.
Oh, no. I didn't have anything
to do with that.
I only bought the paintings
and turned them over to Edgar...
Shut up. You're blabbing
just like he wants you to.
I don't care! i'm not getting
mixed up in any murder!
You didn't
tell me it was...
Someone's always hitting
that poor Mrs. Draque.
Draque, you arranged
the scheme to steal these plans
through someone here
in Sycamore Springs,
someone who lives here
and is well regarded
in the community.
When we find who that
individual was...
Nick, look out!
Hilda: [screaming]
Gracious me!
[barking]
Here you are, Nick.
It was exactly
where you said.
There's one
cartridge missing.
Ah, yeah.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is a rifle
called an Ambu.
It's used by Japanese snipers
in the Southwest Pacific.
It has long range
and great accuracy.
And this one's equipped
with a silencer.
Many of them
were brought back
by our boys
as souvenirs.
My brother Tom
brought that gun back.
Yes, that's right.
You're not trying
to imply that he...
I'm not implying anything.
I just agree that
it was his gun.
I think that's as good
as implying it.
Bertram: I agree
with Bruce, Nick.
These people
are my friends.
A little while ago,
you had us believing
Sam Ronson was guilty.
Ronson's just
a red herring.
I don't care if
he is a red herring.
I'll never believe
Sam Ronson killed anybody.
He didn't kill
Crazy Mary, dad.
When he arrived at her shack,
she was already dead.
How do you know that?
Well, he took
the painting to her.
That was the evidence
she wanted.
Had she been alive,
she would have
destroyed it immediately.
Apparently, she never
got her hands on it.
Man: Let go of me.
You got no right
to bring me here!
I haven't done anything!
Tom, I tried to get away.
They wouldn't let me.
What's the big idea?
Come in, Tom,
and join the party.
We're trying to
catch a murderer.
Bruce, according to
your autopsy report,
Peter Berton was shot
with a .45 revolver,
the bullet entering
the large left rhomboid,
puncturing the posterior lobe
of the left lung
and the lower lobe
of the right lung,
lacerating the parenchyma,
grazing the aorta,
and lodging against
the 12th right costal rib.
That's your boy.
Nick: In other words,
it entered about here,
passed all the way
through his body,
and ended up down there.
- Is that right?
- That's right.
Well, that's
very strange,
because
for a .45 revolver
to get that amount
of penetration,
it would have to be fired
almost point-blank.
And for a bullet
to have traveled
downward at such an angle,
the revolver would have
to have been fired
from some little gremlin
hanging from our porch roof.
Well, there was
no little gremlin.
So he couldn't have been
shot with a revolver.
No. The bullet
that killed Peter Berton
was fired from a rifle
from a distance
and at an elevation,
a rifle equipped
with a silencer,
a rifle like yours, Tom,
which, by the way,
has one bullet missing.
What are you
driving at, Nick?
Simply this...
Bruce, you switched
bullets on us
at the autopsy.
It was a Japanese
rifle bullet
you removed
from Berton's body,
but it was a .45
revolver bullet
that you handed
MacGregor.
What's the answer?
Well, I did that
to protect Tom,
because everybody knew
how jealous he was of Berton
on account of Laurabel.
You thought Tom might
have killed Berton?
No, but what
was i to think?
He had been raving
around the house that night.
Oh, indeed?
[door opens]
Oh, uh, Mrs. Hobbi,
on the night of the murder,
when i phoned
Dr. Clayworth to come over,
where was he?
He was upstairs, sir.
You're quite sure
of that?
Yes, sir.
I remember distinctly
of going to the stairs
to call him.
Uh-huh. And how long
before that
had Mr. Berton
left the house?
Well, just
a few minutes, sir.
That's all.
Thank you.
So, I was right,
Bruce.
Berton was
at your house.
Well, I told you
i had a patient, Nick.
Yes, but you
withheld the fact
that the patient
was Peter Berton.
It seems you
were not downstairs
in your study all evening,
as you said.
I might have,
for a minute...
Are you trying to
blame this on me?
Bruce, when we
went out to visit
Crazy Mary the first time,
you stood outside
and called to her.
Remember?
What's the matter
with that?
That's the only way
you can get in to see her.
Exactly,
but last night,
you didn't
bother to call.
You just barged right in.
Why was that?
I didn't just
barge in. I...
Well, I was excited,
I guess.
I don't know
why I didn't.
I'll tell you why.
Because it would have
been silly
to call to a dead woman,
and you knew she was dead
because you'd killed her.
I think you're crazy.
What was your business
with Draque?
I've never had
any business with Draque.
You called on him
frequently at his hotel.
I checked on that.
Oh, well,
that is professional.
He was a patient
of mine.
A patient?
Is that right, Draque?
That's right.
It's true?
He's never been sick
a day since i've known him.
Thank you.
Uh-uh.
The truth is that
Draque gave you a chance
to pick up
some important money,
and you talked that
bumble-brained Berton kid
into carrying out
the scheme.
When the news got out
that i was here
on a mysterious
investigation,
Berton got into
a panic and decided
to come to me and make
a clean breast of it.
That would have
cooked your goose.
So, when Berton left your house
and came over here,
you rushed up to
your brother's room,
grabbed his rifle,
and just as Berton reached
our door, you shot him.
You're a liar.
No, you're
the liar, Bruce.
You lied about
your association with Draque.
You lied about being downstairs
when Berton was shot.
You knew Crazy Mary was dead
when we went there.
You switched bullets
at Berton's autopsy.
I told you i did that
to protect Tom!
Miss Ronson, where was Tom
the night that Peter
was murdered?
He was in Boston.
I phoned him that night.
Nick: So, you weren't
protecting Tom.
You were protecting yourself.
Any other answers, Bruce?
Yeah. I...
I've got one more.
Oh, you were always
the smart boy, Nick.
You knew
all the answers.
You caught
the big fish.
You beat me
at everything.
Now it's going to be
different this time.
It's going to be a tie.
You've got me,
but i've got you.
You haven't the nerve
to pull the trigger.
Oh, haven't i,
though?
No!
[click]
- Drop it, Bruce.
- Leave me alone!
Take your hands
off me!
I forgot
to tell you.
Brogan removed the firing pin
from that gun.
MacGregor: Get him out, men.
- He can't beat me again!
Let me at him!
You can't beat me again!
Mr. Charles, I've been
wanting to do this
ever since you got here.
May i have
your autograph?
It's for my mother
in Walla Walla.
Gee... Thanks.
That was
wonderful, Nick.
Great work, my boy.
[chuckles]
Well.
Nora: Why, Nicky, I do believe
you popped a button.
[instrumental music]