Have a look.
If you'll just… I'll be right back.
Hey, did you get lost?
Okay. It's on the second floor
near the southwest entrance.
Great. See you in a minute.
A little worried she's gonna hate me.
Just whatever you do,
don't call her an artist.
Right. Not an artist. Craftsman?
- Just Hannah is fine.
- Okay.
Heading over now.
…bus route connecting
downtown Houston
to bush intercontinental airport.
If you were to make airport commutes,
Harris county officials are
keeping a close eye on the…
If you're heading northbound
on Sam Houston parkway
also known as beltway 8, it's…
…is at currently 83
degrees downtown Houston
with sunny skies, a light breeze
coming your way out of the southeast.
Looking for a high of...
Happy birthday to you
come on!
Are you kidding me?
This isn't a cake. It's a bonfire.
- Can you guys explain… here we go.
- Okay. I'll help.
All right!
Yeah, the only one looking out for me.
Hey, I'm the one who got
the vegan steak tartare.
We are all aware.
There we go. Nice.
Maybe I just like the
idea of being far away.
Someplace, just me and you.
How about you?
How about me?
Where do you think
we'll be in five years?
Don't tell me you're still mad
that I cheated at codenames.
Hey.
Everything okay?
Yeah. I'm just…
Thinking about the advantages
of land-based homes.
Okay.
Such as?
Porches that aren't
stained with bird poop.
No low-tide smell.
Weirdly kind of miss that.
Me too.
Okay, come on.
Well, you're not off the hook yet.
What, for cheating at codenames? Please.
Charlie is the worst operative ever.
If you can't abide by your own rules…
Well, I didn't make up the rules.
They're… the rule book.
- Be honest.
- Yes.
How did… how did I do?
Well… the hand-embroidered
cocktail napkins are a bit much,
but other than that, I mean…
If you think it's hard
paying attention to him,
try ignoring him.
You are a great son
and a crack party planner.
You should try adding that
to your online dating profile.
Yeah, I haven't really been
that focused on my dating profile.
I get it.
Look what I found in the office.
- It's your mom.
- Yeah!
High school graduation.
With her friend Quinn.
That reminds me. I put
aside some pictures of Kate.
- Excuse me. I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Let me see. I wanna see.
I'll never get over it.
She looks so much like you. It is crazy.
Is that frank camp a no?
We are leaving.
Now. Come on.
Excuse me.
Hannah? Hannah.
Hannah, would you hold on?
Hannah, would you stop, please?
How could you not tell us he'd be here?
I didn't know. He surprised me.
He's one of my oldest friends.
How could you still be
friends with that man?
The deal I made with frank
keeps the both of you safe.
- You know that.
- Everything okay?
Look, I am grateful for
everything you've done for Bailey.
And for me. I get it.
But if there's ever even the smallest
chance of putting us anywhere near
the man who wants to kill her father,
I'd appreciate it if you'd let me know first.
Fair enough.
Great party, Charlie.
- Happy birthday, grandpa.
- Thank you, sweetheart.
Bye.
A little gift.
Thanks.
Love you.
Love you too.
Thank you, sir.
You good, bails?
Yeah.
Look.
Grandpa seemed good, didn't he?
Yeah, really good, especially
compared to Christmas.
Is it weird that I've started
calling him grandpa?
He is your grandfather.
And he… he loves it.
Yeah, I know. I just…
sometimes feels a bit weird.
Yeah, well, how could it not?
I was just thinking, though,
it's so nice to have someplace
to go for birthdays, holidays.
Our odd little family.
Look at this.
Reading on the potty.
- My god. No.
- Adorable!
I'm gonna have to censor this one.
No, no, no. I'm holding
this for blackmail. I…
This will make you think twice
the next time you consider
cheating at codenames.
Okay.
Is this your mom? And
who's… Quinn. Yeah.
Charlie said that she was
one of my mom's best friends.
She works out of la.
I was… I was thinking of
getting in touch with her.
Wait, she's a camp a no.
- She's frank's daughter. But...
- wait, she's frank's daughter?
But she's not, like, one of them.
Charlie said she has
nothing to do with them.
She doesn't even go
by the name camp a no.
She goes by Quinn favreau now.
Bailey, they are still her family.
Well, Charlie and Kate and
Quinn and her brother Teddy,
they all grew up together,
and they were close.
And apparently, Quinn was
devastated by Kate's death.
- Bailey, I understand the curiosity.
- Do you?
I get how complicated this is for you.
But that's all the more
reason to be careful.
Okay. Don't you think
you're just being a little…
Paranoid?
I was gonna say circumspect.
Maybe. Maybe you're right.
But seeing frank camp a no
was just another reminder
that they are still out there.
I hear you, and it's…
You know, it's probably
good that you're still…
- Circumspect.
- Yeah.
But it's been five years.
And don't take this the wrong
way, but I think it's hard to move on
when you're looking over your shoulder.
This better be good. I had
to bail on Marco's game,
- and Sam was already on my case...
- I got it.
Are you saying what
I think you're saying?
That's fucking Teddy camp a no.
And that's the bingo can.
That container's full
of syndicate product?
I'm sure of it.
And I got the name of
the shipping company.
I get the proof rafina's
owned by the campanos,
you get the link between the
campanos and the syndicate.
Take the whole shitty family down.
You'll be a free man.
You're gonna see
your wife and kid again.
Yeah. If they'll have me.
The fuck is that? Is
that what I think it is?
You're not planning
on seeing them again?
Jesus, Owen. This could
jeopardize the whole operation.
They are the whole operation.
Keeping them safe is
the priority. They are…
I'll call you. After I get the files, okay?
Okay?
Okay.
Come on, come on. Harder. More.
Come on. Good. Body hook right.
Right hook, right.
Double jab right. Harder. Come on.
Hey.
I got you a little gift.
You said you wanted
a little extra protection.
Whoa.
Thanks.
System disarmed.
I heard an old friend lived here.
Married?
How about that? Never
thought I'd grow up, did you?
I wouldn't say "never," but…
Where is she? Do I get to meet her?
She's at the Malibu
house, and absolutely not.
Why? You're worried
she'll be threatened?
No.
Well, maybe a little.
We're actually just on a quick layover.
We're flying out tomorrow to Hawaii.
Wow. I'm happy for you, Jake.
You would've known about it two
months ago if you'd ever returned my call.
You know I work a lot.
Well, you didn't return my text either
so should I be taking this personally?
I've just been swamped. I…
I'm behind on commissions, I have
a show at the pacific design center.
I'm just living at the shop.
Come on, seriously, what's up?
It's… it is nothing really. It's nothing.
It's just the last few months. And I…
I don't even know
how to explain this but…
I've been feeling uneasy.
Bailey thinks I'm being paranoid.
Something happen?
No. Nothing happened.
Any sign of the campanos?
People following you tailgating cars?
Yeah. All of the above,
but when I actually stick around
to see who might be following me,
it ends up being nothing.
It's five years ago this April, right?
Yeah.
Owen disappearing, all the
stuff that happened in Austin…
It's a lot.
It's the kind of thing that leaves a Mark.
Do you talk to anybody?
Talking to you.
What about Jules?
Jules deserted me.
She's in China, three months
into a six-month assignment.
I miss her.
Excuse me.
Wow, she's really got
you on a short leash.
I promised her breakfast at Malibu farm.
Well, what are you doing?
You gotta get outta here.
I'll check in when I get back.
- Hopefully I'm still married.
- You're an open book.
I'm sure she knew what
she was getting into.
Thanks?
I'm not sure if that's a compliment.
Hannah, you shouldn't have to
live with one eye on your rearview.
I am working on it. I promise.
All right.
Thanks for coming.
- Nice to see ya.
- Yeah.
Okay, have fun.
Hey, is everything okay?
I was just calling to check on you.
Isn't your read-through on Thursday?
Yeah. Don't remind me.
It's gonna be great.
I don't know. The mom
character isn't working.
Can we talk about this later?
Sure. Is shep coming
to my show tonight?
Yeah. Didn't you wanna meet him?
Yeah, of course. Hey, is everything okay?
Yes. Yes, it's fine. I just… I…
I'm in the middle of
something. I'll call you later.
He said no. Well, that's a curious choice.
Tell him he can have two,
and I'll give him great recs,
or he can have three
and I'll ruin his career.
Miss favreau, 3:00 P.M. coffee?
Like clockwork. You want one today?
No, ma'am, but thank you.
Miss favreau?
I'm… I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm Bailey, but you
would know me as Kristin.
Kristin.
My mother was Kate Smith.
Everything okay, miss favreau?
Yes, thank you, Paul. Yes.
Yeah.
You have her chin.
Is now a bad time?
No. No, not at all.
Come with me.
She was ambitious. We both were.
Nicholas said that she was just like him.
Following in his footsteps,
becoming a lawyer.
It's not quite that simple.
We both came from families where…
We wanted to carve our own paths.
Is that what you're
curious about? Her career?
Maybe. I… I don't know.
I just wanna know what she
was like when she was my age.
Well, she would have been
about to start law school.
She loved to take pictures.
- She did?
- Yeah.
She carried around a polaroid camera.
I think I still have some
of the photos that she took.
They were these weird arty things.
Really?
She once told me that she
wondered if she made a mistake
not going to art school.
But I assured her she didn't.
Because she… she
wasn't good enough?
Because I was super judgy.
Guess I haven't changed much.
I need to go.
Look, I know this is
probably really hard for you,
but people aren't defined by their family.
At least not the one they're born into.
- We'll do this again.
- I'd like that.
Dad and I are down by the
creek and we're getting skunked.
Not a single bite. Nothing all day.
And I didn't care what
we caught, but your father…
- You're damn right I care.
- Language.
Jonny'd caught five perch the
day before and I was pissed.
- Language.
- Give me a sec, gang.
Hey, what's up?
I found something on
Tuesday's cams, Mr. Campano.
What is it?
Looks like a maintenance
guy taking pics of the Alpha cat.
Could be nothing.
What the fuck, craz? I thought
we had security in place.
We do. I don't know how he got near.
Funny, I thought that
was your job, to know.
Did you get a shot of his face?
Not yet, but I'll keep looking.
Yeah, you do that.
- Something you need to tell me about?
- No. Don't worry about it. I got it.
You gonna finish your potatoes?
So, I'm like a month into the job
and I turn to this middle-aged
woman who works next to me.
This lady who I've been working with
for four weeks and haven't said a word to
because I'm pretty sure she hated me.
And I'm like, "would you
mind putting me in this box
and mailing me to a better job?"
It was great meeting you
too. Thanks again for dinner.
You're welcome.
- Good night. Bye.
- Bye.
- Good night.
- Night.
Okay, so… so do you hate him?
No, not at all. No.
I mean, he's exactly as advertised.
Style lands' end, substance Noah kahan.
Okay.
There was actually something...
I really wanna tell you...
I'm sorry. You go.
Okay.
Well, when you called earlier…
You know, I've been having
trouble with the play and I…
Yeah. Well…
I actually went to see Quinn.
Quinn camp a no?
Yeah. Yeah, she was so great.
She actually… she told me all
these details about my mom.
- Are you angry?
- No, I'm not. I just…
I don't understand why
you'd want to socialize
with a member of the family
who wants your father dead.
She was best friends with my mom.
I have nothing but these
vague memories of her.
I know that seeing frank
spooked you, but I just…
I feel like maybe we're a little bit stuck.
There are so many
unanswered questions.
Yeah.
So, am I gonna take an Uber?
No. Come on, get in the car.
You were gonna say something
earlier after we left shep.
I finalized the sale on the houseboat.
You told me already.
- At dinner.
- Right.
Design show brain.
Don't worry. I'm fine.
This is our home now.
- Good night.
Your reading tomorrow?
Where is it again?
Pacific resident theater, 10:00 to 12:00.
I have a bunch of wine and
cheese left over from the show.
Do you want me to
bring it by for you guys?
Is that a serious question?
And hey, look at this.
I'm gonna pull off without even
watching you walk into the apartment.
Okay.
- Good night.
System disarmed.
What the…
Come on.
Fuck.
What happened?
System armed. One minute.
Hi. I'm here to check a gas leak.
Hi. Wait, I didn't call for a...
Relax.
Don't try to talk. Or struggle.
Just follow my instructions, okay?
Turn it off.
System disarmed.
Now, when I let you go,
you're not gonna scream or struggle.
Now, the next thing that happens
is we put you in a Van out front
and we take you to
them. Do you understand?
Say yes.
She's gone.
- What do we do?
- We follow her.
Okay.
That's what it's like to be young.
I had dreams when I was your age.
I used to have this polaroid camera,
and I still have some of the photos.
These weird, little arty things.
I wanted to go to art
school. Did you know that?
Bailey, you need to call me. Call me now.
There she is.
Shit.
Don't you see? You're
the one who's risen above.
You're the one who can fly.
Do you want notes, Bailey?
I mean... Bailey. Bailey!
I'm sorry, I have to go.
- The car's parked in back. Let's go.
- Okay.
Mom. Mom!
Just start the car, I'll be right there.
We got a report of a gas
leak. Someone named Hannah.
Go! Go, go, go!
Come on.
I parked crazy.
It doesn't matter. They'll
tow it after 48 hours anyway.
- Is there anything you didn't think of?
- Well, there better not be.
Here. Go.
One more stop.
Did you call Charlie and Nicholas?
Yeah, no. There wasn't time.
We'll try them from the car.
My god, this is like a…
a year's college tuition.
No plastic for a while.
Atm, credit card… it can all be tracked.
Okay.
Let's get out of here.
Call Charlie.
Hey, this is Charlie. Sorry I'm
not available. Please leave a…
Still no.
Well, I think we're in the clear.
Come on. You can do this.
You can remember the plan.
Talk me through it.
We're gonna stay at
hotels and rest stops.
Just cash only.
Places we usually wouldn't
stay at 'cause they're too shitty.
Well, because no one
would expect to find us there.
But yeah, probably.
Okay, so we stay at random
places for… for how long?
The plan was a few nights.
Just to… just to get our bearings.
And figure out what to do.
What happened? I mean,
four, five years and nothing.
I really don't know but…
I saw your dad.
He came to the show.
It's why I was so checked
out at the restaurant last night.
- I wanted to tell you right after dinner.
- What did he say?
Hardly anything, but he
slipped this into my dress pocket.
I didn't even see it till I
was home. I am so sorry.
- I should have just told you right away...
- no, no. You shouldn't have.
I would have just been freaking out.
You're not upset with me?
No. No. Why would I be? I…
This isn't your fault.
Thank you.
What the fuck is this?
I don't know.
I think I might have an idea.
Look up the Cape Cod inn.
This is it?
It might have changed a
little since we stayed here but…
Wait, why are we doing this?
Why are we following his plan?
Why aren't we following your plan?
If he wants us to come
here, I wanna know why.
And, look, my plan was to stay
at places like this for a few days
until we can figure out what's going on.
It doesn't really change things.
Except that he chose this place and…
Forgive me, but I don't think
my father has the best judgment.
Maybe, but I'm guessing he
has more information than we do.
I'm hoping coming here
will give us some answers.
And if it doesn't?
Then we'll leave.
Okay.
Hi.
Table for… Hannah.
Anywhere you want, Princess.
Smooth.
Nicholas isn't picking up.
- What about Charlie?
- No.
- Just a diet coke for me, please.
- Me too.
- Thank you.
- All righty.
Maybe my dad's sending a boat for us.
Or a helicopter. Or maybe there's a
telephone booth that can transport us
through space and time
like the tardis in doctor who.
Do you remember your
dad and I taking a road trip?
I'd just moved in.
We were driving to la. You
must have been, like, 15.
Vaguely.
We stopped at this little town off the pch.
They had a farmers market,
a stand where they sold
all different kinds of garlic.
Like 17 different varieties.
Thank you.
- Dad's heaven.
- He couldn't help himself.
So, he starts taking bites
of all these raw garlic cloves,
and I said, "Owen, you are
gonna make yourself sick."
And he was like, "no, no. I'll be fine."
Standard dad.
Anyway, we get back in the car
and ten minutes later, sure enough,
he's like, "Hannah, I
think you better drive."
I thought he was gonna
puke all over the car.
So we look for the nearest place to stop,
and that's how we
found the Cape Cod inn.
The next morning, we canceled the rest
of the trip, and we went straight home.
And later he admitted to me
that he'd been okay enough
to continue with the trip,
he just wanted to go home.
Why?
It was maybe only the second
time that he'd left you alone
since your mom died.
He didn't want to be away from you.
- Hello?
- Hannah?
- Hannah? Is that you?
- Charlie.
I didn't… I didn't recognize the number.
- I need to tell you something.
- What?
It's about my father.
- He had another heart attack.
- My god. Is he okay?
No. He…
He didn't make it.
Tell Bailey I'm sorry.
Everything has changed.