A little pause... and we are back.
Good evening, Ralf.
What are you doing so late?
Boy, boy,
the kippen don't help either, do they?
A new backpack, Ralf?
Ralf?
Is everything okay?
Good evening, Ralf.
It is today.
Nurfest and Jennifer.
I would have liked to have told you.
You said It.
Not to me.
You let a vacuum cleaner run.
You may never see me true.
So only you can tell
that this is who I am.
This is who I am.
No, no, no.
I am.
It is expected that Manfred Fest, the
current top candidate for the office
of the German Chancellor, will visit
his son in the hospital this morning.
Last night, Elias Fest was
victim of a attempted murder.
As a possible background,
the migration... Please turn this off.
Of course.
The first call was pretty positive.
But then this morning
the surgeon called and
said they need to
operate again on the leg.
What's the point of crying?
No, I'm asking you a question.
They are nowhere there
now before they prep him.
How can Elias help
you when you fall apart?
For heaven's sake,
pull yourself together.
Your mother is
crying like a little child.
She was never in control.
Should I send flowers from the office?
Right now?
Write something loving.
No, not loving.
We don't want any
misunderstandings to arise.
Write something...
something positive.
Something positive.
Preventive arrival in three minutes.
Understood.
I'm sorry, again from the office.
Do you want to give a statement
to the last Oledak Charles story?
I can say no.
For the British media.
For the British?
Well...
This man, Oledak Charles,
real name Suleiman,
which he prefers not to use,
understandably,
is an attention-seeking fraud.
Every time he has a
new piece of software to
sell him,
he promises It will save the world.
But all he wants to do is destroy It.
Oledak Charles is a traitor
to the West and its values.
These assholes.
Don't they have any manners?
What nonsense is this?
Please stay in the vehicle, Mr. Fest.
You too, please.
Thank you.
Mr. Fest!
We're going to be quick.
If the candidate leaves the car,
I want him to go through
this door in 10 seconds.
Understood?
PSC 1.
Check the 30-story building
southwest of our position.
The guard is probably
on the 17th or 16th floor.
You're a shark and I'm swimming
My heart still thumps as I bleed
And all your friends come sniffing
Triangles are my favorite shade
Three points, but two lines meet
Toe to toe, back to back, let's go
My love's waiting
Till morning comes
Let's desolate Let's desolate
Let's desolate
Let's desolate My
flow Give my all
Give I zone my all
Three guns A little pause.
.. and we are back.
It's just come in.
I knew you'D want to see It.
Russian 2000 MG.
Isn't that something
you see every day?
Hmm. The serial number's filed off.
Well,
terrorists aren't entirely stupid.
Sounds like a genuine article.
Yeah, looks like the real thing.
Although the
Brazilian and Egyptian
knockoffs are almost
as good these days.
Very nice gun.
Right, let's see if this is
one of our Belgian dealers.
There's got to be another
one in there somewhere.
They're not always entirely stupid.
They're not that smart either.
Bingo.
Have you seen this?
Where is It?
Where is that?
Germany.
That is an absolutely beautiful thing.
You know, I could have shipped
them to you and saved you the journey.
Well, I miss seeing all this.
No, thank you, Christ.
The puzzle board's something special.
Yes, It is. Sadly, not for sale.
However,
I do have a beautiful Kalani set
that I might be
persuaded to part with.
Go on, then.
This way.
Christ.
Herr Krasner,
with the greatest respect, I need
to get out of here
before I bankrupt myself.
Tech entrepreneur Ulla Dag Charles,
or UDC as he prefers to be known,
made his fortune in developing new
technologies to deliver financial...
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm good. How are you doing?
UDC has recently sent
shockwaves through the markets...
Do you want a glass?
No.
Oh, I'm good. Thank you.
...called River. Ulla Dag Charles,
what
is this mysterious new software,
River?
River is a revolutionary
technology... Uh, how's the paper?
Yeah, I finally came up
with a new title for It, actually.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What is It?
It's called Problematic
Violences and
Self-Traps of the
Messianic and the Tragic.
Thank you.
Of course they're detractors.
They don't want you to
know what they're doing.
What does It actually mean, though?
Come on, you were in firearms.
You know what It means.
Where's Jasmine? Homework?
Homework, exactly.
...a man who is a founder
member of the billionaire
club turning against
his fellow billionaires...
Can we find something
on a fest killing, please?
Come on, this is UDC.
You should be all over this.
He's got, like, 240 million followers.
Some people think he's God.
Yeah, including him. Look at him.
You never know with this guy, though.
I mean, if this software does
what It's supposed to, It's gonna
show us where all the big money
is coming from and where It goes.
Like, if he pulls this off,
this could get really interesting.
Yeah, but It's not interesting about
how someone's been assassinated.
Well, It is to me.
Please, can you just... No. Listen,
you can't just come here.
Give me.
Come home. I repeat,
I'm not... Fine, fine, fine. Take It.
Wow.
No respect for your husband, though.
Thank you.
According to police sources,
Fest was struck by a
single bullet fired by a
sniper from long range.
It's not yet confirmed if authorities
have been able to locate a suspect...
Evening, Mum.
Hi.
How you doing?
Fine. How was school?
Good.
Do you remember what's
happening tomorrow night?
Yes.
Parent-teacher's evening?
I'm going to come.
Good.
All right.
Okay.
I offered.
She wants you.
Yes, you can come.
Now, It is a nice day.
erez evening.
Very good night, Max.
It got to say good morning,
Al. Yes.
night.
Aren't you the only one who
hasn't finished your eye of night?
Sir, I have Vin Nieman
under this living suit of mine.
Oh, that's great.
Yes, exactly.
Go ahead, and fetch me your
passport. You mean this one?
Yes. Please, minute.
Sir, oh please.
You like that very much.
Okay. Yes.
If I can't job,
you might as well ask someone else.
Is this your car?
No, It's a rental.
Open the boot.
Open It, please.
What's happening here?
Nothing to worry about.
What's in the box?
So this...
is why I was in your room, though.
This...
is a... Jake set.
The ivory... is all pre-burned.
It's incredibly rare...
that I collect these things.
Wait here.
It's not mine.
Not a slave... if
I'm already free.
Not a captive... if
It's where I wanna be.
Let the crowd call.
Who's gonna catch
me... when I fall down?
Strolling down these
halls... in waterfalls... I...
can't help but smile.
What's the latest
on the first shooting?
Uh, the reports actually just come in.
Should be on your screen now.
Single shot to the head.
A lot of splatter.
Bloody good shot.
No, that can't be right.
What?
3,850 meters.
But that's not possible.
Well,
It's what the Germans are saying.
You know how precise the Germans are.
What's... what's going on?
They've called a meeting about It.
Oh, see.
I should be at the first meeting.
You'll get a full briefing afterwards.
No, no, no.
I don't want a full briefing.
Snipers is my patch.
I didn't drop the names, Bianca.
Wait, wait, wait. Who did?
Was It Isabel? I assume so.
Look.
Jordan's in there. Jordan.
What does Jordan know about snipers?
I have to be in there.
Who is that, anyway?
Werner Lechner, German intelligence.
And there's been rioting in
different parts of the country.
It's obviously very alarming, Werner.
And as you know, the Foreign Secretary
was a personal friend
of the Vest family.
He's very shocked.
As are we all.
What do you need from us?
We are not making any assumptions
about the nationality of the sniper.
So we are reaching out to him,
and we are reaching out to all our
international partners for assistance.
There's been a lot of
speculation about the shot.
Do you have a confirmed distance?
Yes, indeed.
From the apartment block
where the shot was taken
to the hospital door where
Vest was hit is 3,850 meters.
Are you sure about that?
Because the world
record for a confirmed
kill with a sniper
rifle is 3,540 meters.
Ukraine.
2023.
Did you retrieve the weapon?
No.
Right, so the sniper took It with him.
This is the suspect leaving
the apartment building
2 minutes and 52 seconds
after the shot was fired.
Sorry, where's the rifle?
He broke It down
and put It in the bag.
Obviously.
Can we get dimensions, please?
The bag is less than
60 centimeters tall.
So?
The Tac-50 barrel
is 737 millimeters and
It's the shortest
around in this category.
4 meters long.
The rifle's not in the bag.
If It was in the bag,
we'D see the barrel poking out.
He left It behind.
No. Forensics found no
trace of a weapon at the scene.
When a sniper finds a rifle,
one that
allows him to make a
shot at that distance,
that rifle is a keeper.
He's never going to leave It behind.
Which means he took It with him.
And if he took It with him,
then It has to be in that bag.
I'm not following Bianca.
You said the bag isn't big enough.
Which means the
rifle is bespoke.
The barrel came in two parts.
A barrel in two parts is
the gunmaker's holy grail.
If the rifling were
out the tiniest fraction,
It would compromise the shot.
It's impossible.
There's a gunmaker who's
been trying to do this for years.
His name is Norman Stoke.
Is Mr.
Stoke British?
Northern Irish.
Well,
I suppose they count
as British for now.
Do we know where Mr. Stoke is?
Can we get a special
branch to scoop him up?
He's been on the run since the
Stockholm assassination in 2018.
How unfortunate.
But I have an asset.
I know I can find him.
What good would that do us?
Oh, well, gunmaker makes gun,
gunmaker sells gun to assassin.
Highly speculative.
It is elite, however.
And to be frank,
we don't have many of those.
Let's go.
I'm going to the Northern Guard.
Bianca,
a moment, please.
It's always flattering when the
Germans come asking for our expertise.
Although It would be
a little embarrassing
if the gunmaker
turns out to be British.
Who exactly is this Norman Stoke?
Stoke started making machine guns
for loyalist paramilitaries
back in the 80s in East Belfast.
Norman and his
brother Larry killed more
than a dozen innocent
Catholic civilians.
Larry was eventually
caught and went to prison
but was released under
the peace agreement.
He's now an enforcer
for a gang of drug dealers.
Norman, meanwhile,
perfected his craft and made
the gun used in the
Stockholm assassination.
How would you go about
finding Norman Stoke?
I have an asset in Belfast.
Code name Sparrow.
I've heard good things about you,
Bianca.
Don't let me down.
Yeah.
Hey.
You look like you're at an airport.
Yeah, sorry.
What about parents' evening?
So I'm assuming you're not coming.
It's a last minute thing.
You know, she's really
worked her socks off this term.
I know. I know.
I feel awful about It.
There was nothing I could do.
Well,
you could try telling her yourself.
I can't. I can't.
I've just got to Belfast and
I'm already late for a meeting.
Can you do It, please?
Look, I will try my best
to get on the last flight.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
All right. Bye.
Bye.
When I saw your number,
I almost had a stroke.
I thought I'D seen the last of you.
It has been a long time.
How have you been?
What do you want, Nadine?
House the family.
Leave my family out of It.
If Larry knew who I was talking to,
he'D kill me.
But you're being careful.
You remember the protocols?
Yes. Good.
And there's nothing
for you to worry about.
When was the last time Larry
spoke to his brother, Norman?
Not since he disappeared.
Are you telling me the truth, Alison?
I know the brothers are close
and I need to find Norman now.
Not my problem.
It's very much your problem because
if you don't help me find Norman,
you'll go back to prison.
I'm sorry.
Are you married?
No. Children?
No. Career woman?
It's written all over you.
If you had a husband,
you'D know men
have their little secrets.
Well,
this is a little secret I want in on.
I need you to find
out where Norman is.
Today.
I can't just ask
Larry out of the blue.
He'D be suspicious.
I'D have to work up to It.
You've got my number.
I expect to hear from you tonight.
Can I go alone?
It's a free country.
Alison, It's Nadine.
I haven't heard from you and
I'm very disappointed. Call me.
Nadine?
Oh.
It's in-joke.
Look, baby, I'm so sorry.
You know about parents' evening.
I really am.
Don't turn around.
Did you come alone?
Yes, I followed your
instructions to the letter.
Who's the target?
Ulay Dag Charles.
UDC.
Can you get to him?
It'll cost.
I mentioned a guide
price of ten million dollars.
Multiply that by ten and then
perhaps we can have a conversation.
That's a very expensive conversation.
Half on commission,
half on completion,
all reasonable expenses paid.
Well, I'D have to consult
my colleagues about that.
Hello?
Alison, It's Nadine.
You were supposed
to call me last night.
I need to hear from you.
Uh, get me everything we have
on Alison's daughter, Emma.
Copy.
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah, on It.
The B and D believe.
The B and D believe our
sniper thought he'D find Manfred
at the Fest und Fest Unternehmer
offices the night before.
But Manfred wasn't there,
so he shot his son, Elias.
Manfred was
always the real target.
Elias was used as bait to
lure Manfred to the hospital.
That would take a lot of pre-planning.
Well, all planning is pre...
How did Belfast go?
My asset isn't cooperating.
I think we have to get
creative on this one.
She has a daughter, Emma.
A student in London
involved in a
radical leftist group.
I think I can see where
you're going with this.
We have to be very careful about
sanctioning this kind of operation.
Yep, that's her in the pink scarf.
Do I have to wait for her to act up?
No, just go get her.
Fine, but there's an
obstruction in a public highway.
If you do not get up and move
right now, you're liable for arrest.
Why don't you go and
do something useful,
like arrest the fucker?
I'm not threatening you, miss.
Well, OK,
you should try being where I am.
That's a threat.
It's a threat to me.
I'm being reasonable.
I'm not raising my voice
in the way that you are.
I don't care.
Right, that's enough.
Have a month. Thank you.
You're in very serious trouble, Emma.
You're in very serious trouble.
We have four witnesses who saw you
throw the bottle at the police officer.
We have four witnesses
who saw you throw the
bottle at the police officer.
What bottle?
What are you talking about?
Nobody was throwing anything.
You didn't even ask about the officer.
She was badly hurt.
I didn't throw any bottle.
The officer's going
to lose her right eye.
She's going to lose her right eye?
Since you didn't ask?
Just a young
woman doing her job.
How does that make you feel, Emma?
You're making this up.
So fuck right off.
And I want a solicitor.
I have a right to a solicitor.
You can call your mother.
Oh my god!
I wasn't expecting
you until next week.
Well, It was Kalita's birthday,
not her name.
What an art she has. What an art.
She was like this when I found her.
She's still alive.
I've called the paramedics.
Bianca, we've got a serious
problem with your students.
She collapsed.
They think It's a cardiac issue.
They've stabilised her.
They think she's going to make It.
I'm the accompanying officer.
Emma, hang on, OK?
You're going to be all right.
What's happening?
She's arrested.
I'm going to shock her.
Let me help.
If a friend or a foe Only
someone that you know
Disappears from the soil of this field
Then only then will you
know That a version of yourself
Will fade away and never reappear
Whatever It is, whatever you say
When It hurt to reach
out here To make amends
Running out of time Out
of time for a thought set
I swore my love to the very end
Out of time for a thought set