(MOUSE SQUEAKS)
(PENGUINS CHIRP)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCREECHES)
(QUACKS)
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
Sync and corrections by kaysukri
Yeah! (CHUCKLES)
Whoo-hoo!
(LAUGHS)
Yes. This is a hoot.
(CHEERING)
And the winner of the
three-legged race is...
not us!
(CHUCKLES)
But we ran a fair race, Kim Kil Whan.
Yes, quite.
Heh, heh.
Of course, we could have murdered them,
but I was holding back.
I'm glad you didn't show off, Dad.
Thanks.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Thanks to my team of awesomely
talented sales associates
and also my father, Jake, who's
visiting us this year...
this has been the most successful
animal sports/picnic
socializing event ever.
Uh, whoo-hoo.
ALL: Whoo-hoo!
Wow. Really nice deviled egg
presentation this year, Steve.
Mmm.
Dad, I'm glad you stuck around.
I confess I had an ulterior
motive for inviting you.
I really need your advice on something.
My advice?
Parenting advice.
I don't know how to deal
with my daughter, Bronwyn.
I have a granddaughter?
Psych, I knew that.
What's the problem, mijo.
Bronwyn is not doing well at school.
She seems to be busy enough
with homework when she's here,
but her grades are slipping.
And her teacher says she keeps
falling asleep at her desk.
Why is she so unengaged?
And how can I manage her
towards financial success
if she's that unengaged?
I thought you might have some insight
because of your teenage
kind of lifestyle.
What say we rifle through her
biz next time she's out?
Well, I'm no snoop,
but I found these unusual
graphics in her recycling bin.
What do you make of these?
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Ahh.
What are you thinking?
Not sure yet. I'll have to sleep on it.
I'll let you know tomorrow
if I think of anything.
Weird.
(BAT SQUEAKING)
- Whoo-hoo!
- (LAUGHTER)
- Yeah!
- Oh, man!
(CHEERING)
(CHANTING) Bronwyn! Bronwyn! Bronwyn!
Nice one, Bronwyn!
(WHISTLING)
Classic Bronwyn.
Hey, Bronwyn, isn't that your dad?
Nope. That's my granddad.
What? You here to bust me?
Nah, I'm just here to skate.
Yeah, okay.
Show me some moves.
Noice!
- Yeah.
- Pretty good moves.
You're actually kinda
cool, for a gwampa.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you. I value your opinion.
(LAUGHS) That's a spot-on KKW.
(LAUGHS) Yeah.
Um, that reminds me.
We're supposed to talk about
getting your grades up
- in school or something.
- What?
We're worried about your, um,
financial success!
I knew it.
You're not cool!
- You're just like Dad!
- What?
I mean, hey, I love your dad,
but we're nothing alike.
It looks like this round
gramps is a real square.
(LAUGHTER)
I'm not a square.
But now I am.
Whoa! Radical!
(LAUGHTER)
- How'd you do that?
- Do another one!
I'm an old tree.
(LAUGHTER)
An equestrian statue.
Jake, are you going to
stay here all night?
What? They like me.
They like my ageless
style and everything.
Hmm.
But hark! What's that I hear?
(FARTS)
Bronwyn beefed it.
(LAUGHTER)
Y-you're the fart.
What? No.
Old fart.
I'm cool!
Son, it's worse than we thought.
Oh, Koo. Is it black magic?
A cursed ring? An investment scam?
Worse!
I tried real-talking
with Bronwyn last night,
and now she thinks I'm a square!
I feel like you're losing
sight of the point here, Dad.
Pretty much everyone
thinks I'm great, right?
Maybe stay away from my daughter.
Don't worry, Son.
I won't rest until Bronwyn
realizes how cool I am!
But what about...
(GRUMBLES) Dad.
- I got this! I got this!
- Whoo-hoo!
Oh, Glob! I don't!
(LAUGHTER)
JAKE: Fellow dudes!
Old cheeseballs is back.
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow-ow-ow.
Check it out, kids!
I brought my roommate! He's 16!
That's so old.
Do something cool.
- No, I'm sleep...
- Here, play your flute.
Kids love flute.
Wha... (FOOMP!)
(FLUTE MELODY PLAYS)
Ugh. Is that solo flute?
Yo, that stinks nasty.
(BOOING) Uh-oh, kids hate flute.
But, they love mash-ups!
(BEATBOXES)
Whoa, Gwampa is turning it up!
(CHEERING)
(CHANTING) Jake! Jake! Jake!
Math! (SNORING)
This dude don't give a dump.
Dang, you're, like, like a cool gwampa.
Yes!
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(SQUEAKS)
Hey, guys.
Have you ever heard music like this?
(GULP!)
(COUGHING)
Way to choke, Bron.
Yo, how about a duet?
(BEATBOXING)
(COUGHING CONTINUES)
(LAUGHTER)
Even Gwamps can't save you, Bron!
B, why'd you stop?
They're laughing at me.
Hey, come on guys,
don't bust on Bronwyn.
Bronwyn's cool. I can vouch for her.
Now let's all watch me skate!
Whoo!
(LAUGHTER)
BRONWYN: Weak!
(COUGHS)
I can skate way better
better than you, Jake.
TOGETHER: Ooooooh.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
I challenge you to a thrash off.
(COUGHS)
- Ohh!
- Buh?
The winner is declared undeniably cool.
The loser is banned from the skate park.
I can live with that.
Whatever.
Dude, you're really gonna
ban your own granddaughter
from her own skate park?
Man, I hope so.
Hmm.
Yeah, real cool.
FOX: Hey, it's time!
Nice!
(CHANTING) Gwampa! Gwampa! Gwampa!
Bronwyn, did you see my cool new hair?
Ugh.
Hey!
Welcome to Thrashland.
Are you two ready to thrash?
From here, you must skate the
entire length of the park.
First, grind down the ramp,
through the bar maze,
past the big-armed worm,
through the junkyard,
over the log swamp,
and finally cross the finish
at the bottomless pit of love.
(ALL GASP)
Hey, Jake, no weird magic biz.
Heh-heh, same to you.
Remember, you're an instant
fart if you eat it.
Take it away, flute man.
This is a terrible idea.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
Whoa... oof!
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
Huh?
Oh, dang! I love you, Bronwyn!
Whoa, cool! Time to ice this cake!
Whoo! Jake, no!
It took me months to make that jump!
You're gonna biff it!
I won't biff it!
I'm the coolest guy aliiiiii...
(THUD!)
(FARTS)
Grandpa!
You're cool! You're cool!
Just please be okay, Grandpa!
Interference!
That means I win, right?
- Dad!
- Dad?
- Are you okay?
- I'm great.
She admitted it.
(GROANS)
Whoo.
Jake!
Bronwyn...
look, I can see that skating
is important to you.
And you seem very talented at it,
but you're still going to have
to pull it together in school.
Okay, I did get carried away.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I should have just come to you myself,
instead of sending
your cool grandfather.
I just thought you wouldn't
listen to a square like me.
Nah, I mean you're not cool,
but you're not uncool.
Kim Kil Whan! Bronwyn! Look at me!
(GRUNTS)
Time to go home.
Not the swan, that's where
the pups came from.