- Previously on Cross...
Voilà.
None of it matters
without the book.
This is not a scrapbook,
this is his bible.
No one
is gonna forget you now.
Drop it.
I wanted it to be you, Alex.
Someone from my past is out to get me.
In my professional opinion,
she cannot be fixed.
- What's this?
That name you gave us,
Peter Lenox.
Go live your life, okay?
Mine's already over.
This guy, he's full of guilt.
He blames himself
for what happened to Deirdre.
Years of focus, years of planning.
A guy like that is never gonna give up.
- Oh, come on. Whoa!
Alex, what are you still doing in bed?
Don't you want to go play with Sampson?
He's outside waiting.
I don't feel like it, Nana Mama.
I get it.
You know, back when I was growing up,
I was terrified of thunderstorms.
Scared the living daylights out of me.
I would hide in my bed just like you
until the storm passed.
But it hasn't been raining out today.
No, but you've been through
some real bad storms lately.
Losing your mama? And now your daddy?
It's too much for a child.
But the thing about storms is,
they don't last forever.
And God already gave you
your share, honey.
So from now on,
it's only gonna be sunny skies ahead.
Guaranteed.
And when the sun is shining?
Oh, that means
it's time to go outside again.
But what if something bad
happens to you, too?
I'm not going anywhere, Alex.
Promise?
Promise.
Got you, Nana.
It's gonna be okay, Nana.
It's gonna be okay.
I got you.
I'm gonna get him.
I'm gonna find who did this.
Don't worry, Nana, I'm gonna get him.
Run a FAST. Get her into Bay Three now.
Nana, I'm right here, right here.
Whoa. Only staff past these doors.
Daddy!
Hey. Hey.
Where's Nana Mama? Is she okay?
Doctors say she's stable for now,
but still critical,
so they got to keep an eye on her
to make sure she's okay.
Can we see her?
Not yet, baby girl.
They need to run some tests.
- I want to see Nana Mama.
Hey, kids.
See that vending machine over there?
How about we go find ourselves
some treats?
And see if they have anything
Nana would like.
Elle, I-I appreciate you coming. When I...
She's gonna be okay.
Peter did this.
The man who's been stalking me.
Now, I got backup coming,
but Damon and Jannie,
they can't go back to the house.
I got to get them somewhere safe.
I need to be out looking for him.
They can come home with me.
I-I appreciate that, Elle,
but I don't know where's safe.
This man knows everything about me.
Listen, I-I don't mean to intrude, but...
my family has a cabin out on Goose Creek.
And, uh, if you all need
somewhere safe to stay,
I could take you up there.
It's nothing fancy,
but it is out of the way.
And, uh, it's the last place that anyone
would think of looking for y'all.
Miss Nancy, I hate to suck you into this,
but that would be a lifesaver.
O-Okay, well, it's not you asking,
it's me offering, so...
I'll go.
I could use the time away.
Besides, those kids need as many
friendly faces around them as possible.
We got Nana Mama's favorite.
Red Vines.
Last pack, too. That's good luck, right?
It's got to be.
It'll do you kids good
to get out of the city.
Get a little fresh air, see some nature.
How far away is it?
- Hey.
Goose Creek is out there.
Way out.
I'll bet if you get up early, you could
see families of deer in the forest.
Cool. What's the homework policy
while we're out there?
homework policy is do it, Miss Thing.
Yeah.
I'll have your teachers
email your assignments.
Oh, actually, um,
I don't have Wi-Fi,
and cell service is pretty spotty.
I keep it old-school.
No Internet?
No Internet, but you can call somebody.
Here's the number for the landline.
Thank you. I know
none of this is what you signed up for...
Oh, stop. No, with, with
my own kids grown and gone,
you guys and Regina,
you've become quite the blessing,
so I'm, I'm just happy to help.
That's very kind of you, Miss Nancy.
Before you go, there's something
I want to show you.
Is that him?
The man who's been doing all this to us?
If you see this man,
I want you to run, okay?
- And get help.
I thought he'd have a scar
on his face or an eyepatch or something.
Hey. Hey.
Everything's gonna be okay.
All right? I promise.
I promise.
Detective Cross.
I'm Kat, Peter Lenox's case manager.
Thank you for seeing me
on such short notice.
What do you have?
Do you have anything for me?
I haven't had valid contact info for him
in nine years, so...
Yeah, that-that figures.
Uh, what about family?
I-I'll take anything. This is urgent.
Uh, based on his records,
all his known relatives
are either dead or incarcerated.
What is this about? Is Peter in trouble?
He's terrorizing a family.
My family.
I'm sorry.
Okay, this wouldn't be in his file
and it-it's probably not helpful,
but, uh...
I remember Peter had a "street mom."
Lady who'd come in with him sometimes,
help him with the paperwork.
Not a relative?
Peter called her his "fairy godmother."
Sweet lady.
And, uh, there was someone else, too.
White girl with dark hair.
What was her name?
It was like Dee Dee?
Something like that?
- Deirdre.
- Deirdre, yeah.
She's in jail, though.
- Street mom.
- Mm-hmm.
- How can I find her?
- I couldn't tell you that.
She never applied for benefits herself,
so she's not in the system.
Not even a name. I'm so sorry.
Yeah, well, just thank you,
thank you for your time.
Look, if you think of anything else at
all, just anything, you-you let me know.
Yeah.
It's so beautiful out here.
So calm, so quiet.
Yeah.
It was my little girl's favorite place.
Been in my family for years.
No matter how bad things got,
this place was always a refuge.
I sleep like a baby out here.
Mm-mm. I'm used to the city.
I mean,
the country quiet, I can't sleep a wink.
Oh, girl, my son, too.
Look in the medicine cabinet,
you will find what you need.
- And then you can sleep like a baby, too.
Do you have a dog?
Oh, my kids did.
Yeah.
Passed away a while back.
Kept the leash, though.
I guess some things
are just hard to let go of.
What's this for?
- Baby, do not touch that.
Mosquitoes.
You can take out a whole swarm
with just one pull of that trigger,
which is why it is not safe for children.
We might need it to protect ourselves.
Damon, you don't got
to worry about that.
Nobody bad gonna find us out here.
Why does that man hate us?
- I don't know, baby.
- I guess...
...sometimes some people hurt
so bad inside,
they just want everybody else
to hurt, too.
Aw. Okay, enough of that.
Who wants hot chocolate?
- Yes! Yes, yes, yes.
- I think that's exactly...
Hey.
- Heard y'all helping Cross
track down Peter Lenox.
- Yeah, everybody is.
- Any luck?
Not yet. It's just a matter of time.
Oh, that's good.
What about the kids?
- They all right?
- Yeah.
He sent 'em off to stay with a family
friend until we get Peter locked up.
We're all just hoping Nana Mama
pulls through.
Yeah. Yeah, me, too.
I just got back from the hospital, so...
It's not good, but she's a fighter, so...
Look, if y'all need any help,
just let me know.
Should we tell Cross to call you?
No. If he wants to, he will.
- Oh. Thanks, Tana.
- You're welcome.
Hey, Alex, what's up
with you and Two John?
What do you mean? Did he say something?
He was in here earlier,
I asked where you were, he didn't know.
And that's the first time he's ever
not known, as far as when I ask.
I thought of the worst thing
I could say to John,
and I said it.
And then you apologized?
Yeah, I don't think sorry's
gonna change anything.
You might be right. I just...
If it was me, I would find out.
Hello?
Miss Nancy. It's Alex.
I was just checking to make sure
you guys are all settled in all right.
Oh, yeah. Snug as bugs in a rug.
Um, but I'm really glad you called,
because Elle and the kids were
starting to get a bit worried.
Um, were you able to track down that man?
No, not yet.
Hey, can I speak to Elle for a sec?
Sure. Elle.
Thank you.
You just interrupted
a very competitive game of Life.
These kids of yours,
they gonna run the world one day.
Yeah, that sounds like
my Damon and Jannie.
Hey, um, any updates on Nana Mama?
Yeah, she's, uh, she's stable,
but there's some internal bleeding.
And they can't fix her until
they get that under control.
She's gonna make it, Alex.
I know it.
If that's Daddy, I need to speak
to him right this minute, please.
Hold on.
Daddy, the cabin is so cool.
There's a fireplace and bunk beds,
and it's okay if me and Damon
both want the top bunk
- because Elle said we could take turns.
- Yeah?
And Auntie Nancy gave us chores
and said she'll pay us.
Oh, it's "Auntie" now, huh?
Yeah. It was Damon's idea,
but Miss Nancy said
she would like it if we called her that.
She says what makes you family
isn't blood.
It's how much you love each other.
So people like her
and Uncle John are family, too, right?
That's right, kiddo.
You don't have to be blood to be family.
Blood doesn't make you family.
Daddy? You still there?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I'm here. Uh...
Hey, you kiss Damon for me, okay?
I am not kissing Damon,
but I'll tell him you said hi.
Love you.
Love you, too, baby.
Alex. Cross.
Hey, I don't have time
for anything right now.
You don't know what this is about.
Ramsey sent me his book.
- What are you gonna do with it?
- I don't know.
I mean, I-I have a million things
in my mind.
Tania, I don't have time
to help you right now. I don't.
Shit.
Something's really going on. What is it?
If you want to hold onto that
for a couple days, we can talk about it.
Otherwise, please don't make him a star.
You lost your mother.
How did it feel to lose a family member?
Blood doesn't
make you family.
What makes you family
is how much people love you.
You'll never find me.
One Mississippi, two Mississippi,
three Mississippi, four Mississippi,
five Mississippi, six Mississippi,
seven Mississippi...
The woman who helped Peter
with his housing application,
would you remember her face
if you saw it again?
Yeah, I think so.
I'm sending you a link.
Did you get it?
- Internet comes and goes around here.
Got it.
Is that the woman you saw?
Ah. Y-Yeah, that's her.
Uh, she's aged a little bit,
but that is definitely
Peter Lenox's street mom.
This is crazy.
How did you figure that out?
What you doing?
Miss Nancy. We were playing.
Hide and seek.
I thought this
would be a good space to hide.
Not good enough to stop me
from finding you.
All right, come on up, wash your hands.
It's almost time for dinner.
Damon, baby, you okay?
You kids are under a lot of stress.
I hope this ends soon.
Oh. Knowing Alex, I'm sure it will.
And in the meantime...
...there's nothing to worry about.
We're all alone out here.
- Excuse me.
- Mm-hmm.
Hello?
Hey, Miss Nancy,
um, I'm sorry to bother you again,
but, uh, can I talk to Elle for a sec?
Um, Elle is just bundling up the kids,
because we're gonna go out back
to make s'mores.
Let me give her a message.
No, uh, you know what,
it'll only take a minute,
but I-I really need to talk to Elle.
It's kind of important.
Oh, is something wrong?
No, uh...
No, no, it's, um, Jannie, she-she has
a little condition, and I just realized
I forgot to send up the medicine, so...
But now-now there's a way to manage it
without the medicine, and-and I need
to walk Elle through the regimen.
All that time that I spent at the house,
I never saw Jannie take any medicine.
And Regina certainly didn't
mention anything.
I'm surprised that it never came up,
but it is a thing, so...
can I please talk to Elle?
Is it a thing, Alex?
Or do you know?
I'm sorry?
Do you know who I am?
Do you know what this is?
Do not hurt my children. Do you hear me?
Aw.
I love that "I'm in charge" tone you got.
But I don't think
that's your reality right now, is it?
Look, if you touch one hair
on their heads,
- I swear...
- Jannie? Jannie.
Honey. Come here for a minute.
Hey.
You know what? Um, I just remembered
there's a special place
that I wanted to show you.
It was my little girl's favorite.
I think you're really gonna like it, too.
What is it?
- No, it's a surprise.
Oh, my God.
She's his mother?
What are we gonna do?
Well, how about
we take a walk in the forest,
just you and me?
- No.
That sounds like fun.
Mm-hmm.
Can we do it after the s'mores?
Absolutely, we can do it
after the s'mores.
Okay, go back. Finish your dinner.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Can you just go get more butter, please?
Yes. Thank you. Thank you, baby.
O... kay.
- Should we tell her?
- No.
No. And I can't have you acting
any different, Damon.
I need you to do something for me.
Can you get Miss Nancy's keys?
Good.
I will handle everything else.
Please.
Please, please,
please don't hurt my children.
Now, that's a much more
appropriate tone, Alex.
I know that everybody thinks
that you're the world's best detective,
but to me you're just
another little fuckboy.
Why-why-why are you doing this?
You're such an expert,
you tell me.
- What do you want?
Thank you, sweetheart.
I want you to come here.
You will be unarmed,
you will bring no one,
you will tell no one.
And if you violate
any of these conditions,
I swear to you, you will never
see your children alive again.
I'm gonna put a clock on you.
Let's say, uh, four hours.
Give you a little bit of extra time
in case you hit traffic.
And I hope that your shiny new Mustang
can get you here in time.
Drive safe now.
Okay. Where were we?
You were missing this.
How is it?
Delicious.
Look here, motherfucker.
You...
...you were right.
You were right the whole time.
I've-I've been out of line lately.
No, not just lately.
Ever since Maria died.
And I was pissed at you
for pointing it out.
I was even more mad
when you tried to help me.
I took our friendship,
our-our brotherhood for granted.
Said some shit I can't come back from.
And now, now, John,
I-I'm not even here for the right reasons.
I should have come here
and looked you in your eye
like a man and said I'm sorry
and I love you, brother.
But I-I-I couldn't swallow my pride.
And now my family...
our... our family is in danger...
Sugar, stop.
You had me at motherfucker.
No. No, Elle. No, I'm serious.
I-I do not date.
I-I have acquaintances.
You know, I get acquainted.
- And then I get on up out of there.
Date.
So you never saw yourself settling down?
No.
I didn't see it for you, though.
Oh, Regina told me Alex pulled
some dumb shit, and you weren't having it,
but let me tell you something.
I have seen the way he looks at you,
and I've heard the way he talks about you.
It's real. It's worth fighting for.
Maybe one day you'll add some babies
of your own to the Cross family, huh?
Oh, we're there now?
- Then, Miss Nancy,
I'm gonna have to ask you
for something stronger than this tea.
Girl, I was wondering when you were
gonna join the party.
'Cause this whiskey here,
this is hitting the spot.
It's what we do at the cabin.
We drink, we eat, we try to keep warm.
Here you go.
Thank you.
To you and Alex working it out.
Cheers.
I can't believe it was her the whole time.
Man, that woman's crazy.
You realize how long
she must have been planning this?
Just to get in the house
she had to volunteer for Early Mozart,
go to school, single Damon out,
convince Damon to...
Damn, man. And think about
all the times she was sitting
right next to you.
I mean, why not just do it then?
I don't know, John.
I'm afraid to find out.
Jannie? Jannie, baby. Jannie.
Hi. Come here, come here.
- What's happening?
- It's time to go, baby, come on.
Come on. Watch your head.
Here we go. Let's go, let's go, let's go.
I don't sleep.
This isn't about you.
They're not your kids.
Get out of my way.
Run!
Just go!
- Get in the back.
In the back, in the back.
Watch your head. Watch it.
Damon, keys.
No, no, no.
No, no. Run.
- Run! Run!
We're about a mile out.
How long do you need?
Once you get there,
just give me ten minutes... and duck.
See you on the other side.
- Show me.
- I'm not armed.
Where are they?
You want to see your kids or not?
Alex.
They're fine...
for now.
Put 'em on.
Sit down.
Nuh-uh.
Chair by the window.
I tried to get them out.
I'm sorry I got you into this.
You asking
the wrong questions, Alex.
This is about you, not those kids.
Then why are they here?
Damon and Jannie didn't do anything...
Deirdre didn't do anything.
But you said she was crazy.
You said she couldn't be fixed.
By the time I met her, she was broken.
But I should never have said
that she couldn't be fixed. I'm sorry.
- I am, Miss Nancy.
Wouldn't that be nice
if "sorry" was all I wanted?
Was there something else? Huh?
Hmm? Just go ahead,
t-tell-tell me what it is.
Why you keep looking at your watch?
You got somewhere to be?
He brought backup.
Just like you said he would.
Your buddy's dead, Cross.
Bleeding out on the forest floor
like a stag.
- No.
Maybe go back later...
...collect the antlers.
No.
Alex!
I've wanted to do this
for so fucking long.
Peter, stop.
That's not the plan anymore.
Give me that.
Take this.
And get him back in the chair.
So, Alex,
you've lost your wife,
lost your best friend.
Grandma's barely alive.
Mm-mm. You still don't hurt like I do.
You still don't know
what it's like to lose a child.
What?
Oh, my God. Please, Miss Nancy, please...
Shut the fuck up.
Bring the kids.
Good news is...
...we only gonna take one.
And you get to choose.
So, which one will it be, Jannie...
No, no.
...or Damon?
No, please.
No, N-Nancy, I can't answer that.
You-you want revenge, kill me. Kill me!
I'm not dead.
I'm in agony.
Every minute of every hour of every day.
I need you to feel that.
So pick one,
I'll have Peter shoot that one.
- No, please.
- What?
It'll be over in an instant.
But you see, if you don't choose,
I will take them outside
and you get to watch them both die
a slow, painful death.
The kids haven't done anything.
He has to choose.
Why?
Eye for an eye,
she'd just kill one of them.
That's not justice for her.
She needs more.
It's the choice.
The choice.
Making me choose one of my own.
But why is that important?
Unless...
Right now
Peter's just a person of interest,
but we would like to speak with him.
If you do see him, let me know.
I sure will. Thank you.
- Hey, what'd they say?
- They're looking for Peter.
My God, they're going
to put him in prison.
He did it, right? So...
I know, I know. Oh, God.
With his record,
they gonna bury that boy.
Maybe even death sentence.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
But maybe there's a way
that we can help him.
That you can help him.
How?
What if there was a different suspect?
What if... what if someone else confessed?
A young white girl,
no criminal record,
who, uh, made a mistake and,
and, uh, and got scared,
and things got out of control.
Jury would never go hard
on someone like that.
She might even be out in a year.
Maybe even less.
Okay.
Yeah, I'll do it.
He's my brother, I-I have to.
Oh, God. Thank you.
What makes you family is
how much people love you.
Peter, she never told you.
Your mother's the reason
Deirdre went to prison.
- It's a lie. It's a lie.
- What's he talking about?
I read the letters
between you and Deirdre.
I saw you racked with guilt,
knowing she went to prison...
- Don't listen to him.
- ...for something you'd done.
- Begging her to change her confession,
thinking it was your fault she died,
but it wasn't
Deirdre's idea to confess, was it?
Shut the fuck up!
Mom.
Did you?
I-I didn't have a choice.
They were gonna put you away forever.
It wasn't your decision to make.
I had to protect you.
That is what mothers do.
Deirdre wouldn't want this.
She wouldn't want these kids here.
Come here.
N-No! Don't...
Don't let him get in your head.
Nothing's changed.
No. No, no, no!
It should be me.
It should've been me in prison.
It should be me in the ground.
No. Nobody should be in the ground.
My plan would have worked,
but he said, he said that she was broken.
He broke her.
She was broken by the time I met her.
Going to prison snapped her.
You did that.
Why, Mommy?
I'd rather be in jail than know
she died because of me.
Don't let him break you like he broke her.
No, no, no, son. Look at me.
I'm your mother.
I'm the one who loves you.
I'm the one who saved you.
I need you to help me finish this.
But Deirdre wouldn't want us
to hurt these kids.
No, Deirdre isn't here
to tell us what she wants.
Do you want to know why?
Because he destroyed her.
She was hanging in that prison cell.
He might as well have put that noose
around her neck himself.
He destroyed our family,
and now we are gonna destroy his.
Get the kids.
Out this way.
You good, John?
Never better.
Don't hurt my baby. It's not his fault.
Oh, he got to pay.
And so do you.
I can't go now.
My babies need me.
You don't have a choice.
Those were Maria's last words, Alex.
Or, at least, that's what I was told.
You're gonna pay for this.
I'll pay in hell.
No! Mama!
Sugar, let's go! Come on!
Sugar, let's go!
- You all right?
Locked and loaded.
Come here.
- Put this on the table for me, Damon.
- Who wants donuts?
- Mmm.
Breakfast is ready.
I'm about to use
all this whipped cream on these waffles.
Boy, if you don't
give me some of that...
Actually...
Oh, you gonna go ahead and...
Oh, yeah, I am, actually.
Thank you.
Go ahead, put some of that
- on your eggs.
No.
There he is.
What took you so long?
Can I get you anything?
We're fresh out of Pappy Van Winkle,
but DC tap water goes down pretty smooth.
That's very kind of you, Alex,
but, no, thanks, I'm good.
Guys, come on.
You deserve better than this.
Is that your way of telling me
you're not afraid of me?
Would you like to pick
a place to start, or should I?
You requested me. Why?
I can't think of a better way to
put a button on the Fanboy legacy...
I guess I did end up
embracing that name after all...
than to confess
to the legendary Alex Cross.
What legacy?
That's funny.
One thing you can't do,
Alex, is rewrite history.
Eleven kills puts me in the pantheon.
Now, do you want to pick a place to start,
or should I?
Eleven? No.
You're being charged with one murder.
Emir Goodspeed.
And one kidnapping. Shannon Witmer.
I'm confessing to all of it.
All 11,
with all the dirty details.
Oh, oh. Hold on.
Hold on, I... I see what's going on here.
You know you're going away
for a long time, maybe forever,
and you figure,
"Hey, it won't hurt to
get famous on the way." Right?
And you can't take it, can you?
You're so used to winning.
You can't bear to be my secretary
and take my dictation
while I write myself
into the history books.
What... history book...
Are-are you confessing to
the Emir Goodspeed murder?
I don't know what game
you're trying to play, Alex,
but not taking my confession
will not stop the truth from coming out.
Or have you forgotten about my book?
What book?
You mean Bobby Trey's book?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You know that book is mine.
Never saw you with it.
I only saw Bobby with it,
and in about an hour,
I'm going to walk into a press conference
and announce that Bobby Trey Abellard
is the Fanboy.
Bullshit!
I'm confessing to all 11 kills,
all of which I have documented
in painstaking detail,
every transformation, in my book.
Can you describe the book to me?
Fuck you.
Hey, you're a fan of live streams, right?
That's your thing?
Check this out.
Hey, John.
Hey.
Can we get a look at that bookity-book?
What is this?
Got it right here.
Does it look like this?
Two John.
Yeah.
Do it.
All right, then.
Ooh, that's hot.
Now, where should I start? Let me see...
- Oh, this one's definitely got to go.
- No.
No!
No, no, no!
No! You can't do that!
You have to keep that, that's evidence!
No! It's evidence!
Those kills are mine!
Paul David Harris, mine!
Patricia Bennett, mine!
Charles Anderson, mine!
Donald Clark, mine!
That motherfucker is turnt all the way up.
It's like he actually
believes what he's saying.
But we all know he's just crazy.
I will be remembered!
I will be... I will be remembered!
I will be remembered.
You on surveillance detail?
I'm looking for mermaids
with my granddaughter.
I cured her of Santa Claus,
but she truly believes Ariel's
gonna pop her head up any minute.
How's the family? Regina?
She's recovering.
We all are.
I wanted to give you
a heads-up about your hearing.
You'll be cleared.
- How?
- Victim took a settlement.
Dropped all charges.
So you can put that video behind you
and move on.
Well, if that is your "good news" face,
Alex, it needs some work.
Getting cleared doesn't erase what I did.
Nobody wants to see you lose your badge.
You're the cop who took down
DC's most prolific serial killer.
One day you'll thank me.
Consider it my last good deed as chief.
So you are running for mayor.
And me not facing
a disciplinary panel probably helps.
Well, sure, it helps me,
and you get a do-over.
But you earned it.
That's not the world I want to live in.
But you do. That's the reality,
whether you're on the job or not.
And if you're not, how are you
ever going to change things?
You're a hero, Alex.
But only you get to decide
what that means.
Look, I don't know if they told you,
but this is a spit-free zone.
As a matter of fact, I got a whole
circumference around me
that needs to stay
saliva-free at all times.
I got a call to come get
Emir's personal effects.
Evidence is downstairs.
I know.
I, um...
...I came to say thank you.
Hold up.
Are we having
a civil conversation, Malika?
You still ain't shit.
Better watch yourself, girl.
Thank you for coming.
I'm not here for you.
Why'd you do it?
Why me?
My wife was murdered
near Union Market.
You were the only employee
with a violent crime on his record.
You had called sick that day,
and the killer,
they'd used your security badge
to escape through the delivery tunnels.
I reported that badge stolen.
I know that now,
but at the time
I figured either you-you...
you killed her or you knew who did.
- He didn't know shit.
Please let him get it out.
And when you started running, I...
Damn right, I took off, man.
You think I don't know what it means
when a cop shows up out of the blue?
Don't even need a record.
Don't need shit.
Just the color of my skin.
The color of our skin.
You been on the job so long,
you forgot what you look like?
No, I haven't.
Then you need to act like it, man.
You're absolutely right,
and I am so, so sorry.
You should resubmit your complaint.
Publicly, so the department
can't sweep it under the rug.
I don't need your badge.
Just want cops to live by
the same rules as the rest of us.
But the next time
you see a brother running,
I hope you put yourself between him
and whatever the fuck is about to happen.
I will.
I promise you.
Let's go, Damon!
You got this,
you got this.
You got this.
I'll be right back.
So, you're here.
What should we talk about?
Maria.
So,
Crossy-Cross really thinking
he can pin me as the Fanboy?
Maybe not forever.
He is planning on
using that book to make you
America's most wanted.
But he did build you an escape hatch.
He knows you killed Tavio Lemmons
and Vanessa Norris.
Knowing... ain't proving.
It's Cross.
You want to roll the dice?
I want to hear the offer.
That's fair.
Well, a lot of Ramsey's victims
have family members
that are still looking for answers,
and that's where you come in.
You would have to
provide us with information
that would lead directly to
the recovery and positive ID
of at least six Fanboy victims.
Think you can do that?
In return for?
Full immunity,
with 24 months served.
You have any idea how long
24 months is in dog years?
Come on, I hate math.
I am guessing it's less than life.
I get that immunity in writing,
and you can tell Crossy-Cross
we got a deal.
I'll turn myself in tomorrow at 10:00.
Today.
When you're done eating.
That puts a different spin
on these here wings,
- but okay.
- Okay.
One more thing.
It'd be nice
to have some money waiting for you
- when you got out, wouldn't it?
Now, you see, you see.
I knew you had your own angle. What it be?
Ramsey had a lot of dirt
on people worth having dirt on.
Yes, yes, yes. Yes, he did.
And if I knew where it was,
why wouldn't I keep
all that dirt for myself?
If you want to work all those
Capitol Hill assholes retail, sure.
But I suspect you'd much rather
get paid wholesale and just walk away.
Is this you or... our Uncle Sam talking?
Money won't know where it came from.
I guess data is the new oil.