We want Nicky!
Previously on Drag Race
France...
Hello, hello!
It's time for Snatch Game.
[cheering]
Hello.
Château Lax.
Sorry. I needed a breath of
fresh air.
What do you think of your
impersonator?
The person at the wax museum
did a pretty good job.
But. apparently, it was a
trainee.
[laughs]
-Punani!
-Oh!
That's what I want to see on
Drag Race.
Congratulations.
You are this week's winner.
Ginger Bitch.
There were too many repetitions
in your Victoria character.
-Piche.
-Wrong choice
with Geneviève de Fontenay.
I expected more.
♪ Say yes and light up my life ♪
I've made my decision.
Ginger. Shantay, you stay.
You can join the others.
Piche. Sashay away.
Thank you.
[cheering]
[melancholic music]
Oh, my God, it's horrible.
It's awful.
It's horrible to see Piche go,
because I know what she's worth.
She's an incredible performer.
She's got a great sense of
humor.
She got lost in the maxi
challenge
against Ginger.
She was too shy.
It just wasn't her day.
"So happy to be the rebel queen
of this season."
[laughs]
"Go all out!
Sorry for the mistakes.
Signed, Fat Piche."
[murmurs of desolation]
What should I say?
-Bravo, Piche!
-Well done!
[cheering]
Piche, you have been
a formidable competitor.
Too bad it wasn't enough.
Ginger, the tornado, came,
and you flew away.
Bye, honey. I love you.
How are you?
Me? I don't know.
Actually, it's weird.
I'm happy to stay.
-Uh-huh.
-But I know
I have eliminated someone. So...
-That's the game, baby.
-Yeah. I'm pissed.
But I'm glad I made it.
-It gives me a bit of
confidence.
-She's a great competitor.
Beware of the sleeping Ginger.
[laughs]
She's awake now, and it stings.
Bravo, Punani!
-Well done, Punani!
-Thanks a lot.
You see how being the aquatic
version
of Marge Simpson can...
[laughs]
I'm sad to have won with this
outfit.
[laughs]
No. I'm glad I won...
-Snatch Game.
-Yeah.
It's iconic.
-Congratulations!
-Thank you.
Now that I've won this
challenge,
I feel more relaxed
in the competition.
But I won't be resting on my
laurels,
because there are still
many talented queens.
So, it's not the time to falter.
I'll have to keep on fighting
to reach the top.
Keiona, how does it feel
to be at the top all the time
and never win?
[laughs]
-[inaudible]
-Frankly...
Try to join me, honey.
[screams]
-There you go.
-Then, ask me again.
-Yeah.
-And you'll know what it's like
to be at the top and never win.
Fourth week, still on top.
I'm not giving up on you.
I'm staying on top.
[theme music]
On the jury this week:
Daphné Bürki, Kiddy Smile,
flamboyant singer Juliette
Armanet,
and the great DJ Barbara Butch.
Y'Paris is proud to offer
the big winner a crown
and a crystal scepter worth
40,000 euros.
[theme music]
Misterb&b, the LGBTQ+ travel
community,
offers an exceptional trip
for two to New York City,
including a Broadway show
and a five-star hotel.
[upbeat music]
Mac Cosmetics is pleased
to offer a year of products
to create your makeup looks
and reveal your inner artist.
DRAG RACE 2 FRANCE
ONLY ONE WILL BE QUEEN
One drag, two drags, three
drags.
Four drags. Five drags.
-Ah!
-Six drags. Seven drags.
[upbeat music]
Got you!
[laughs]
Got you. Under the fabric.
Got you, under the wedding
dress.
[screams]
Got you, under the green dress.
You all suck.
-Come on, girls.
-Let's do this.
This week, I'm all pumped up.
I really thought I was leaving
last week.
I don't want to go through that
again.
No way. I'm going to give it my
all,
and I'm fired up!
[shouts of joy]
[crowing]
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
Oh!
My queens, do you ever want to
escape?
-[All] Yes.
-Not from here.
-In life.
-Oh!
I watch fairytales, musicals.
Everything looks so perfect.
When someone wants to kill you,
he does it while singing.
[sings] You're going to die.
It sounds great.
Magic, right?
So, my queens, will you make us
dream,
or will this chapter be the
last?
-[All] Yeah!
-This.
[screams]
I can't. I have too much botox.
[laughs]
[all] We want Nicky. We want
Nicky.
Hello, hello.
Nicky is wearing blue and red
rhinestones.
She's very "patrio-chic."
-My queens.
-[all] Oh!
How can you really tell it's
summer?
The sun shines until evening.
Tight shorts all over the
sidewalk.
And, of course, Fort Boyard.
[shouts of joy]
I'd love to be in Fort Boyard.
But only if I can do it in drag.
The longest wig, the longest
nails.
The most impractical heels.
That would be something.
For this week's mini-challenge,
we'll play together
in our version of the famous
show
Fort Boyard.
[cheering]
[laughter]
-Yes.
-Oh!
To win, you'll have to face
your greatest fears.
[screams]
[Nicky laughs]
Can't we do something quiet?
Can't we visit a dollhouse
or do a quick dance?
I'm going to show you something
scary.
[all] No.
[suspense music]
A sleeveless down jacket.
[screams of panic]
Oh, the horror!
What a fashion faux pas!
Horrible. It's like capri pants.
This is heresy.
If the fashion police catch you
wearing a sleeveless down
jacket,
they'll put you behind bars for
life,
because it is a crime
of the utmost importance.
This is a crime. A criminal
crime!
Really, you should be locked up.
You have five minutes to get
into drag.
Let's go!
[hubbub]
In five minutes, you can't do
much
apart from getting ugly.
And that's what I'm doing.
I'll get right on it.
You can [inaudible]. Oh!
I'm running. I'm flying.
My look is Diam's meets Sheryfa
Luna.
Everything's fine. I'm at my
best.
[upbeat music]
My look is insane.
It's a race.
A wig, some lipstick, a bikini,
and here we go!
[laughs]
MINI CHALLENGE FORT BOYARD
-My queens.
-[all] Yes.
You're about to plunge into the
unknown.
-[all] Oh!
-Literally.
[hubbub]
Each jar holds a key
that you'll have to retrieve
from a mystery content.
[panicking]
But one key only can unlock the
secret.
Oh, Pit Crew!
-Oh!
-Ah!
And what a secret!
-Who wants to play?
-[all] Me.
Cookie, it's your turn.
[panicked scream]
[panicking]
Time to get down to business.
And to get my hands dirty.
-Here we go.
-Is it alive?
[panicking]
Go, go, go.
[panicked scream]
-Is it poop?
-It's gross.
-So gross.
-My nails!
-You can't do this to me, Nicky.
-Ah!
The texture, the little noise,
this [inaudible].
It's... [disgusted]
Cookie's hand has disappeared.
[cries of disgust]
How awful!
-These are leftovers from
yesterday.
-Come on.
Come on, look for something
hard.
[laughs]
[panics]
Ah, what is that?
[cries of disgust]
I think this is the key.
I have the key to my love for
you.
Cookie's hands are black
and all, I'm...
[disgusted]
It's crazy. It really grosses me
out.
Punani.
[cries of disgust]
What's inside? Can anyone help
me?
Can anyone tell me?
[cry of disgust]
Let's go!
Come on, Punani!
Go on. Keep going!
Come on. Come on!
Put your hands in the big tuft!
There you go. Shake it!
Like this.
[all] We can see it.
[screams]
[hubbub]
[cheering]
Yes!
[applause]
That's what you find
when you unclog the sink.
No.
[disgusted]
Sara, it's your turn.
Come on!
[panicked screaming]
Sara is so funny.
[screams]
Oh! She can't take it anymore.
She's trying, and I'm thinking,
"Is she going to find her key?"
[screams]
This way!
I can't believe it!
There's no end to it.
[screams]
She's dancing.
[fart noise]
The noise is like this.
It's awful.
It reminds me of De Funès.
[disgusted]
The Cabbage Soup.
[laughs]
Go ahead, baby, mix it up!
I didn't sign up for this.
-Come on, Sara.
-You can do it.
Ah ah ah ah!
Well then?
[screams]
Is it okay?
[cheering]
Bravo!
-Moon, it's your turn.
-Go ahead, baby.
Give it your all.
[panicked screams]
Oh, no. That's horrible.
Stop it. Stop it! I'm not okay.
I'm not feeling well.
This is the worst.
[screams]
[laughs]
Come on!
[screams]
It's okay. They're just eels.
-It's disgusting.
-Put your hand inside.
-I'm fucking inside!
-No, you're around it.
"To the left! No, the other
left.
In the middle!"
What an idiot!
[screams]
[laughs]
[cries of joy]
Ginger.
[cries of disgust]
-The perfect basket.
-Ah!
The texture must be awful.
Water-filled sponges, that's my
phobia.
Come on, Ginger!
-Come on!
-Come on, Ginger!
-Oh!
-Come on!
-It stinks.
-It's down there.
Ah, it's cold. I...
It's the leftovers
from the canteen, it's okay.
-Mix it up!
-It stinks!
-I'm going to puke.
-Come on, Ginger!
You've got it! There it is!
[all] Yes!
[shouts of joy]
[inaudible]
[cheering]
Keiona.
Oh!
[cries of disgust]
I'm not scared.
Okay. You're going in there with
no fear.
Yeah.
[upbeat music]
-Mix it up!
-No!
-No, go back.
-More energy!
I've got it.
[cheering]
Wow! What an expert!
I love winning!
[laughs]
Are you always this fast?
Sometimes, I make the pleasure
last,
but sometimes, I have things to
do.
[laughs]
And, finally, Mami Watta.
[screams]
My Lord!
I put my hand inside,
and I feel like caterpillars
or worms climbing on me and
going
inside my body.
Red alert: Mami is grossed out.
It sticks, and it's wet!
[screams]
[hubbub]
-It fell!
-It's falling!
[laughs]
[cheering]
It's disgusting.
It's Mami drama. It's Mami
Watta.
The water spirit, the comedy
spirit.
It's the stage. Always the
stage.
-Are you ready to test your
keys?
-[all] Yes.
-Cookie.
-Oh, goodbye.
-Come and release the secret.
-The little bird will come out.
Wait until you see it
before saying it's little.
Excuse me. Hello.
If you don't mind. How kind.
Wait. How do I get in there?
Is this the right key? Please,
let this be the right key,
for once in my life.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Oh!
Oh, no! The lock is too tight.
-Oh, no.
-It's not a match.
-I'm off. The bird didn't come
out.
-Bye, Cookie.
See you.
Punani.
[screams]
Ah! Ah!
[cry of desolation]
It's not a match.
[inaudible]. I'm sorry.
[sighs]
It's not me.
But, well, I won Snatch Game.
-The others can have the key.
-Keiona.
[suspenseful music]
Oh!
[cheering]
[laughs]
I have...
revealed the secret.
I'm so angry. I didn't even
get to try my key
and see if I could open it.
I couldn't get near the Pit
Crew.
Congratulations.
You win this mini-challenge.
[cheering]
[applause]
[laughs]
And you won...
[suspenseful music]
...a sleeveless down jacket.
[screams]
Keiona!
All respect left Drag Race's
Werk Room
when this orange sleeveless
down jacket made its entrance.
[instrumental music]
Goodbye, respect.
[upbeat music]
My queens, for this week's maxi
challenge,
you'll take part in the first
edition
of a cult challenge.
[cries of amazement]
We'll make a Rusical!
[shouts of joy]
In other words, a "musidrag"!
[cheering]
You will pay tribute
to the greatest French musicals,
in a new show called
The Hunchback of Notre Drag.
[cheering]
It's great!
[sings] A musical!
[coughs]
Keiona, as you won the
mini-challenge,
you will assign the parts.
[all] Yes!
-Sister!
-I love you. You are beautiful.
So beautiful. Your skin is so
moisturized.
Your teeth are sublime.
She is beautiful.
Tonight, the audience will
consist of us,
your dear jury,
and two guests who love
musicals.
Our favorite DJ who spreads love
on the dance floor,
Barbara Butch.
[cheering]
-Barbara.
-She's flamboyant.
She's beautiful.
She's a lesbian, and she's here.
And the disco ball of French
music,
Juliette Armanet.
[cheering]
I'm going to meet stars
and not you, too bad.
-You should have done Drag Race.
-#Drag Race France.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
[all] No.
-Bye.
-[all] Bye, Nicky.
-Bye, Nicky.
-Oh!
-Okay, let's go.
-Let's listen!
Come on.
[calm music]
[gasps]
-It's great.
-It's high level.
The musical is great.
It's funny. There is singing
and acting-- this musical is
insane.
-It's awesome.
-It's going to be great.
-So great.
-Yeah.
The characters, in order of
appearance.
Uh-huh.
The narrator tells the story.
And even if she sings out of
tune,
she wants her solo.
She's with a sexy young man.
[all] Oh, Pit Crew!
I got the Casting Director part.
[screams]
My head.
So, who wants to be the
Narrator?
-Ah!
-They're afraid of big, thick
text.
-Oh! Not me.
-Quasimollo.
His father locked him up in his
room,
because he's ashamed
of his appearance and manners.
He has one dream only--
To live to the fullest.
-Great.
-That's it.
-It's the story of...
-Everyone here.
It's our story.
[all] The Baker.
-Yes.
-She knows about Quasimollo,
and she is fond of him.
Esmeraldwa... in your face!
She's a young girl...
[laughs]
A cheerful street girl.
She spends her time dancing
barefoot.
She's very happy. Kind of a
hussy. Mallo.
He's Quasimollo's father
and embodies the patriarchy.
He locked up his son,
his heart, and a little secret.
-A little secret.
-And now...
the last part is the Dragoyles.
-Oh, yeah.
-The gargoyles.
-It's insane.
-I love it.
A revisited version of the
gargoyles.
It's a funny, groovy, and
inseparable duo.
Keiona chooses simplicity.
She decides to make a table,
to make statistics,
to enter the first, the second,
and the third choices of each
person.
And fit it into the boxes.
-Mami Watta...
-First choice is Quasimollo.
Uh-huh.
-Mallo in second.
-Yeah.
-Narrator in third.
-Oh!
-And the baker.
-Very good.
I love Mallo. He's great.
Playing a dad is kind of cool.
-Yeah.
-I like Mallo's part.
He embodies the unbearable
patriarchy.
If the trans person does it,
it could be great.
-I put Mallo in one.
-I'd like to do Mallo
and her, Esmeraldwa.
I don't want to play Esmeraldwa.
-Oh, you don't?
-Nope.
I've said it at least three
times.
-Punani.
-I'd say Dragoye.
Uh-huh.
I like many of the parts,
but there's one I'm eyeing,
and it's Dragoye.
-Sara forever.
-Dragoye or Dragoya.
Okay.
[instrumental music]
Punani as Dragoye. Sara as
Dragoya.
[instrumental music]
-Okay?
-Yeah, great.
-Okay.
-It's so predictable.
They're friends in life.
You want to manage.
So, choosing them is
predictable.
-Actually, it's...
-We would make...
-A great duo.
-But the point is also
to compete with one another
and not work with a friend.
We've never worked together.
The first time, I wanted to,
but I couldn't do it.
Exactly.
I can see you doing this
together.
Cookie interferes in things
that don't concern her.
If you wanted to assign the
parts,
all you had to do was win the
challenge.
As you didn't...
Esmeraldwa: Ginger.
I get the part that nobody
wants.
Cookie will be the Narrator,
and Moon will be Mallo.
-Right on!
-I will be Quasimollo.
-Great.
-And Mami will be the Baker.
-You'll have to sing a lot.
-Nice.
You have a lot of lip-sync.
I'm counting on you. I trust
you.
After the song.
[laughs]
And Keiona will be Quasimollo.
The casting is done!
[cheering]
-Come on.
-[all] Back to work!
[cheering]
[instrumental music]
ELIMINATION DAY
-I'm pumped!
-The musical!
[dancing]
Today, it's elimination day
in the Werk Room.
-The dreaded day.
-Girls, how are you feeling?
I'm really happy,
because that's what we like to
do.
And we're taking a great deal of
pleasure
in this challenge. We are
together
and defending something
that we know is beautiful and
exciting.
So, this energy is cool.
The Rusical created a real
sisterhood
and pushes us to the top.
The atmosphere is amazing.
We all love this challenge.
I identify with Quasimollo,
because I share
the same story with my father.
Actually,
we're out of touch,
because from a young age,
I realized he isn't open-minded.
He judges a lot,
and he doesn't try to
understand.
I cut ties with my father
when I reached adulthood.
I realized
I didn't want to be friends with
him.
He never understood
and never tried to understand
who I was, and the reasons for
my choices.
He has always wanted his older
son
to become a soldier or a doctor.
I've thwarted his plans,
clearly.
I'm the total opposite
of what he was hoping for.
Your father won't watch the
show?
I think he will.
My brother will try to show him.
How do you hope he'll react?
Well, I hope he regrets it,
because he'll miss the
opportunity
to be with a star.
[laughs]
It's great that his pain
and what he went through are
driving him
to do things onstage.
It's a kind of catharsis,
and it'll help.
It adds a special flavor to her
part.
When I told my parents, they
said,
"You just dress like a girl."
As if that was it.
And, here, we'll sing, I mean,
we'll lip-sync and act,
and you realize that's not just
it.
It's not only about taking on
another gender's attributes
or...
I mean, taking another form.
It's much more than that.
The art of drag is the art
of self-transformation,
it's creating an alter-ego
and bringing it to life,
it's being your own muse,
your own inspiration.
It's not, "I'll put on fake
eyelashes
and get free drinks."
It's much more than that.
The problem with drag
is that it's hypersexualized,
and people mistake
drag with prostitution or
cross-dressing.
Everybody is confused,
and they need to realize
they wouldn't do the same
to a singer or a movie star.
So, they shouldn't do that to
us.
When it comes to drag,
there's often a lot of
misunderstanding
or ignorance, mostly,
and that's the problem.
People think it's a shady job,
and that it's linked to sex
work.
There's nothing wrong
with sex work, but there's no
link.
For us, it's about acting.
We play characters like an actor
onstage,
as an artist in their own right,
and that's what people
often don't understand.
So, there are often questions
or just ignorance about the
matter.
Most of the time,
my drag is based on characters,
on alter egos I create.
It's great to play a man,
and I've fought for this part.
-Yeah.
-So, I embrace it.
Yeah.
But I think I overestimated my
courage
to go back to being a man,
especially since it's the
disguise
I've used for 30 years,
and that, since I came out
as a transgender person,
I haven't put back on.
And to put it back on, on TV,
now that I'm doing my makeup,
I realize it's complicated.
It's hard to reappropriate male
codes.
It took me so many years
to let it go and understand
that it didn't belong to me.
So, going back to them
after my transition is super
hard.
But I can't wait to do it with
you.
You'll be fine. You're very
brave, Moon.
Because, beyond the risk-taking
onstage
and in the theater,
it's really taking a personal
risk.
I don't think we realize
what it implies and means,
because I have drag daughters
whom I accompanied
during their transition.
So, I know exactly
what you're going through,
and I understand it.
And I just want to say thank
you.
Thank you for existing.
Thank you.
Come on, girl.
It's so important, you know.
There's so much involved.
Honestly, take it and enjoy.
I know you're going to kick ass.
If Moon can pull off this part
of the stereotypical dad,
of the father trapped
in toxic masculinity,
it could be the highlight of the
musical.
I'm going to put my dysphoria
aside today.
And enter euphoria for the
musical.
That's it.
And it will be a smash.
It will be a smash!
-Yes.
[exciting music]
[applause]
Good evening, and welcome
to the big Drag Race France
stage.
[applause]
Oh!
With us tonight, Daphné Bürki.
Good evening, Nicky.
Daphné, what's your favorite
musical?
Cabouré.
I love it.
Shall we watch it tonight?
With us too, Kiddy Smile.
Hello!
What's your favorite musical,
Kiddy?
My life.
That works.
[laughs]
Our first guest is a DJ, an
activist,
a singer, and a Jean-Paul
Gaultier muse.
And, yes, we can all be that
at the same time.
Barbara Butch.
Good evening, Barbara.
Good evening.
Barbara, you mix all over the
world.
Can you speak several languages?
Do you speak English?
Hablas español?
Muy bien.
Muy lesbian.
[laughs]
I'll keep it.
She's burning up the dance floor
with her fiery disco hits.
Juliette Armanet is with us.
[applause]
Juliette, drag queens love
performing to your songs.
By the way, last year,
Elips did her talent show
to "Burning Fire." Have you seen
it?
Many times. I wish I could take
off
my clothes like her.
Oh! She'd be happy.
Okay, folks, let's go.
This week, we asked our seven
queens
to perform the very first
Drag Race France Rusical:
The Hunchback of Notre Drag.
[laughs]
So, my queens, get ready,
and may the best drag queen win!
Good evening, children,
young and old,
I'll tell you the story
of the Hunchback of Notre Drag.
Go ahead and applaud, don't be
shy.
[applause]
Once upon a time, a different
person
whom no one cared about,
Quasimollo,
was locked in the attic
by his father to hide him away.
The poor kid wasn't blessed
with good looks.
He was ugly, slouched, with a
hump
on his back, and a slanted face.
But what bothered his father
was that he was... effeminate.
Anyway, one day, the kid decides
to escape
and discover the world
at the village market.
And then comes the moment
you've all been waiting for,
so park your little buttocks in
your seats.
-The time has come...
-For cathedrals?
No! My solo, the only one,
as far as I'm concerned.
But I haven't said my last word.
♪ That day, his whole life
changed ♪
♪ When Quasimollo went to the
market ♪
We got it.
Enjoy the show!
[vocalizes]
♪ All these smells
Suddenly intoxicate me ♪
♪ So many colors
My heart is knocked over ♪
♪ And these bananas, how sweet
they are! ♪
♪ I'll take one
No, I'll take twelve of them! ♪
♪ Look at these thousands of
loaves ♪
♪ Big, hard, long and thin ones!
♪
♪ And, finally
All the others choose yours ♪
♪ A good baguette feels good ♪
♪ My only project is to live ♪
♪ So, I run, and I don't look
back ♪
♪ That's it
I feel that nothing is
impossible ♪
♪ I know that, one day
I'll be able to be myself ♪
♪ Look, I knew him as a child ♪
Who is it?
♪ Quasimollo
The son of a very good friend ♪
A friend?
♪ My child, I know
it's not easy every day ♪
You can't even imagine.
♪ So, tell me, what brings you
here ♪
♪ I'm all ears ♪
I'm fed up, madam.
I'm tired of being locked up in
a tower.
Away from the world.
I want to be blown...
away ! I dream of grasping
all the big... opportunities
that fate has in store for me.
And, finally, to swallow...
the nectar of life.
Come closer!
-The time has come...
-For cathedrals?
No, not cathedrals! But to
welcome
the divine, the legendary...
The hairy, too...
Esmeraldwa!
[upbeat music]
Oh, she's so pretty.
She's such a good dancer.
She's so graceful.
She looks like an angel.
An angel?
[upbeat music]
Go for it!
Quasimollo!
Go home!
Right away!
Right away.
Come back and dance with me
tonight.
♪ Back home, Mallo ♪
♪ Ma, ma, ma, ma, llo, llo, llo
♪
-Go away.
-Okay.
As for you, you put me to shame.
Shame!
Go to the attic, immediately!
♪ It was better when real men
ruled ♪
♪ But it's all falling apart! ♪
♪ My son dances like Beyoncé ♪
♪ It's really not normal ♪
♪ I would have preferred ♪
♪ For him to be a man ♪
♪ A real one ♪
♪ I don't know what I'm doing
wrong ♪
♪ I just wanted to dance ♪
♪ And be free like Esmeraldwa ♪
♪ If only heaven could hear my
voice ♪
[coughs]
Damn, that feels good.
I was starting to get stuck in
this wall.
You're always complaining.
I'm the one with the sun in my
face.
And always on the same side.
Regarding pigeon shit,
it's a tie.
-[coughs]
-Ah, yes, sorry.
I'm Dragoye.
And I'm Dragoya.
Are you gargoyles?
Dragoyles, man.
It's the same thing but in drag.
We're much more fashionable.
Thanks.
We've come to help you.
Really?
You're always complaining
right in front of us.
It's a bit boring, actually.
"Boo hoo, I'm unhappy."
What Dragoye is trying to tell
you,
is that we have...
"Boo hoo, I'd like to be someone
else."
There's a solution for you.
-Drag.
-What?
Drag.
♪ When people are lying down ♪
♪ In their well-ordered lives ♪
♪ It's time to eat ♪
♪ Not to put make-up on ♪
♪ We put on our fishnet
stockings ♪
♪ And we make magic ♪
♪ We dress with style ♪
♪ Our well-lacquered wigs ♪
♪ We're ready to eat ♪
♪ The whole world ♪
♪ When we arrive as queens ♪
Yeah!
[cheering]
♪ As queens ♪
♪ In this unchanging world ♪
♪ We're kind of a bit bored ♪
♪ So, become someone else ♪
♪ To show who you are ♪
♪ Don't explode ♪
♪ You can free yourself ♪
♪ With some blush ♪
♪ Heels, false eyelashes ♪
♪ And, finally ♪
♪ Become your own heroine ♪
♪ When we arrive as queens ♪
♪ You, all over the world ♪
♪ Looking for people like us ♪
♪ We're just free and back in
drag ♪
♪ The world is crazy ♪
♪ For wanting to control
everything ♪
♪ You are free to be who you are
♪
♪ As a queen ♪
♪ When we arrive as queens ♪
Oh, yes, I want to!
Are you sure you're ready?
Oh, yes, please!
Where should I start?
-Who tells him about the...
-Ah, yes, the...
-The willy.
-The willy?
The willy.
♪ The willy ♪
♪ You need to hide the willy ♪
♪ In a place ♪
♪ Unlike others ♪
♪ You hold it with some tape ♪
Take a deep breath.
And then, on the count of three,
you twist it.
Okay, let's put him in drag!
[cheering]
-Wow, I say yes.
-I diverge.
That's magic, thank you,
from the bottom of my heart.
I've never felt so beautiful and
strong.
See you later.
♪ When we arrive as queens ♪
[upbeat music]
♪ With the power of the throne ♪
♪ Quasimollo went back ♪
♪ To the village ♪
Sorry, madam.
Who the hell is that?
She's so hot!
She looks like Esmeraldwa's
sister.
Wow!
How beautiful!
Oh, yeah, that's because you're
cheating!
No, she's hot!
I wish I could be like her.
Who is this beauty?
I feel like I've seen her
before.
I know these features.
No, it's Quasimollo!
Quasimollo! Quasimollo!
She's beautiful. She dances
well.
-Quasimollo!
-He's fucking annoying.
-I'm going to kill him.
-I think that's against the law.
Shit, I don't want a son...
[imitates an effeminate boy]
What? Different?
But we all are, Mallo.
Since you're an idiot,
I'll explain it in a song.
Careful, it's going to be sick!
♪ It's so hard here ♪
♪ And we only have one life ♪
♪ He has a hunchback ♪
♪ I have a fat ass ♪
♪ But I love myself ♪
♪ I am ♪
♪ We all have differences ♪
♪ This is surely a chance ♪
♪ You have big feet
You are nodding off ♪
♪ And you don't even speak
French well ♪
♪ But we are ourselves
That's the way it is ♪
♪ Not all the same
The same desire ♪
♪ We want love and respect too ♪
♪ And to love ourselves ♪
♪ I'm suggesting now ♪
♪ To open your hearts wide open
♪
♪ I like boys ♪
♪ The hair at the same time ♪
♪ As for me, I don't like people
♪
Come on, Mallo!
The real courage in life
is to be yourself.
♪ I would have liked a bigger...
To feel good ♪
♪ In my underpants! ♪
Well, that explains it.
You're perfect the way you are.
♪ But we are ourselves
That's the way it is ♪
♪ Not all the same
The same desire ♪
♪ We want love ♪
♪ We want to live
And love ourselves ♪
♪ We want to love ourselves ♪
Love yourselves as you are,
and life will always be a party!
[upbeat music]
♪ We arrive as queens ♪
[cheering]
[applause]
Well done!
[laughs]
I just wanted to say
that I'm extremely proud of you.
It was crazy!
I know how hard you've been
working.
This competition isn't easy,
and you give it your all every
week.
But, tonight, I saw stars in
front of me.
-Well done!
-[applause]
We all are Quasimollos in the
end.
And that's what brings us
together.
When we all hold hands
and say that life is a party,
it's very beautiful.
It was dazzling, moving, funny,
and I think we were all moved
to see you tonight.
Thank you. It was great. Well
done.
I didn't think they would cry
and be moved like that.
Nobody thought that.
It will resonate in everyone's
heart,
and it's really important to say
to the people watching us
which aren't free yet,
to be who they are,
that, together, we're all one
family,
and that they are not alone
and never will be,
because they'll always find
people like you,
like us, to welcome them.
We were also in tears,
because we felt an emotion.
We were thinking about people
watching us who are like us.
We really felt the power of the
message.
I'm super proud
to be part of this musical.
A lot of people will recognize
themselves
in Quasimollo!
I hope they meet a family
that accompanies them,
like you're doing right now.
And I hope they find an art
or a safe place
where they can express
themselves,
where they feel safe,
where they can grow.
What you just did onstage,
I don't think you even realize
it.
You've just created a family, a
big bubble
in which we feel very happy.
And that's drag.
-So, well done.
-[applause]
I'm convinced we've done
something big.
[applause]
Shall we do it again?
[laughs]
[theme music]
For the runway, the category is:
Excess Couture.
First up, Cookie Kunty!
[upbeat music]
She looks like me when I go
shopping.
My look made of pink taffeta
and black velvet is so couture.
Dramatic!
My trail follows me like a
cloud.
Amazing!
Drag me wherever you want.
The hair is out of proportion,
the train is oversized,
and my ego too. A little.
Oh, it's so cute.
It's great. The outfit is
beautiful.
[upbeat music]
Sara Forever.
-Oh, my!
-[laughs]
She doesn't do things halfway.
No!
I'm wearing a huge tape measure
all around me.
It's beautiful and is
embellished
by stupid and extraordinary
accessories.
Honey, I shrunk the Drags.
[laughs]
It's so cute!
I chose this look
as a little tribute to Nicky.
She wore part of this look
on her season.
[upbeat music]
She will "decimeter" the
competition.
[laughs]
Keiona!
Oh, my!
Volume, volume!
I feel stuck in this sheath
dress.
I take tiny steps in very high
heels.
And my sleeves are huge!
She's got a good pair... of
sleeves.
[laughs]
That's all I can think of.
For Excess Couture,
I'm a modern-day Diana Ross.
I'm the next disco star.
[upbeat music]
Punani!
I'm wearing an oversized dress
with large, oversized shoulder
straps.
My headband is a hanger
that holds both my hair
and my shoulder straps.
-She's very self-centered.
-[laughs]
I wanted to play with my
childhood,
when I used to try on my
mother's dresses.
She really needs to come out
of the closet.
[Nicky] For sure.
[upbeat music]
Ginger Bitch!
I'm wrapped in a giant belt
to prove you can be big
and still find belts ten times
too big.
-She's crazy!
-[laughs]
I'm wearing an imitation
Jean-Paul Gaultier corset.
My thigh boots are vinyl
and my cap too, for the fetish
aspect
of belts.
I used to be a cop.
So, I'm wearing a real cop's
cap.
[upbeat music]
Oh!
For my look, I decided to sport
an oversized hat.
What a nice hat!
My dress and my heels are
oversized.
-Oh, the little detail!
-Thanks for the shoes!
And an oversized bag.
I'd love to wear a bag
to put the patriarchy in.
-Is it big enough?
-I'm hoping it's good enough.
My look represents partying
and wealth. It's festive and
fashionable.
-She's wearing Jack Foam!
-[laughs]
[upbeat music]
Mami Watta!
-[gasps]
-Wow!
-Okay!
-[laughs]
It's my most couture outfit so
far.
I was inspired by an outfit
created by Virgil Abloh.
He's one of my favorite
designers.
I'm excited to honor him
on the Drag Race France stage.
She doesn't joke about fashion.
I'll put this on to take the
subway.
[laughs]
Just kidding, I don't take the
subway.
Today, Naomi Campbell is my
mother.
Mami Campbell is here today.
That's me.
Wow! Holy cow!
It will be hard to decide.
♪ Sissy that walk! ♪
My queens, it was Fashion Week
on Drag Race France today.
-Well done!
-[applause]
[suspenseful sound]
We'll start with Cookie!
Obviously, by wearing my outfit
and my wig, you look
magnificent.
-[laughs]
-You're really sublime.
-I'm so glad it suits you.
-Gorgeous!
Thanks for the train.
-It's never too long.
-Never!
I'm dazzled.
You are beautiful and inspiring.
We don't know where you came
from.
You were an apparition.
You opened the Rusical
and really set the tone.
That lip-sync was quite long
and complicated,
it had different rhythms,
but your delivery was truly
extraordinary.
It was a mix of Rika Zaraï and
Régine,
who are my idols, so I loved it,
and I want to see more of that.
Compliments feel good, right?
Yes, really good.
I'm in heaven now, thank you
very much.
[suspenseful sound]
Sara Forever!
Your performance in the Rusical
complemented Punani's perfectly.
Yes, your duet was perfect.
We really wanted to be your
girlfriends,
despite the fact that you
dislike people.
I tolerate them.
Yeah, it's kind of mutual.
Your performance was great,
and I'm glad I discovered you.
Thanks.
For Excess Couture,
I really like this camp look.
It's very pop.
It's really funny, and at the
same time,
you totally fulfilled
the excessiveness of the theme.
It's funny, but I would have
liked to see you
in a haute couture outfit.
[suspenseful sound]
-Keiona!
-Hey!
I love this look,
because I understand all the
references.
Once again, you're paying
tribute
to our ballroom culture.
You're doing it with elegance,
and I'm delighted.
When I saw you as Quasimollo,
I immediately thought of Lucas.
This young boy who was bullied
at school
and committed suicide at home.
What you did tonight could save
the lives of many of these young
people.
It's not just a queen
who told the story of
Quasimollo.
It's a queen who told the story
of an entire community.
And that really touched me,
because I expected to laugh
and see something very camp.
But, actually, I saw myself on
the stage.
We've all seen each other
on this stage via your story.
I can still feel this emotion.
It was so powerful.
I could see the fear in your
eyes,
and I could actually feel it.
When you changed and suddenly
blossomed,
a solar energy emerged
and freed itself from all of
you.
My heart opened up all at once.
Thank you,
and congratulations on your
performance.
Thank you, Juliette.
It was very important for me to
do
what I did today,
because I was telling a Rusical,
but I was also telling my own
story.
They trusted me...
[sighs]
...to tell this story.
If I'm going to shine,
I can't do it without them.
There.
Thank you.
Once again, well done!
Let's get on with it.
Punani.
[laughs]
Can you make this outfit in a
larger size?
Because I really need
this outfit for myself.
No worries.
About your performance,
as Dragoye and Dragoya, you were
awesome.
It made me very happy.
"When We Arrive as Queens"
is a fucking hit song.
[laughs]
An amazing hit song.
That was great, bravo.
You looked great.
If I need to look at details,
one shone slightly brighter
than the other.
But thanks for your energy
and for bringing the elements
to make the story evolve.
Well done to both of you.
Thank you.
-Ginger Bitch.
-Good evening, little bitches.
Fasten your seat belts.
Ginger Bitch is fully strapped
in.
Indeed, it's extremely well
done.
The corset is, of course, a
tribute
to Jean-Paul Gaultier.
The braids are amazing.
Everything is...
-You set off fantasies.
-I love your look.
And it's true, it makes me kind
of wet.
I love the name Esmerldwa.
[laughs]
You didn't have many lines,
when you arrived onstage,
all eyes were on you,
and you really were into it.
Don't forget to change your
make-up too.
Esmeraldwa had the same evil
look,
and I struggled to connect with
your eyes,
and to see the energy
you were trying to convey.
Okay.
Moon!
Hi.
In the Rusical,
your character was the best
played.
You embodied it really well
with a lot of humor,
and I also enjoyed the quality
of the transformation of your
face.
It's incredibly brave.
It must have been quite painful
to play a toxic parent,
because, unfortunately,
it's very common in the
community
to face this kind of person,
and you embodied him
wonderfully.
Thank you for putting yourself
at risk. It paid off.
Thanks a lot.
Mami Watta!
I love this look.
It reminds me a lot of
the creations of Balmain,
the silhouettes of the Saharan
people.
Grace Jones in Alaïa has nothing
on you.
It's just as pretty
as what you did onstage.
I understand that musical comedy
was a dream of yours.
-Yeah.
-If you came here
thinking you were going
to be a fashion queen,
to me, you will remain a baker
forever,
because you sold it very well!
The Baker was just phenomenal.
She stole the scene every time
she opened her mouth.
You were the light.
You shone on everyone.
It was great to see and to feel.
If I had a baker like that...
[laughs]
...I'd go refine my brioche more
often.
[laughs]
-That's it.
-Thank you.
Thanks, girls, go unpack your
jewelry
while we deliberate.
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
[applause]
Let's go.
[upbeat music]
How are you, girls?
-I'm fine.
-It's ambivalent.
It's very complicated.
Everyone got positive reviews.
What will they decide?
No idea.
Who will be on the top and on
the bottom?
No part was below the others.
-Exactly.
-And that's great.
Everyone shone.
I don't feel that way at all.
Oh, shit!
This part was forced upon me.
I tried to get another part.
Nobody listened to me, apart
from Keiona.
I can't let them say
that life is beautiful
and that everyone played a role
and got the part they wanted.
It really pissed me off
that when I tried to plead my
case
and get another part,
you didn't hesitate to say,
"No, you're not right for this
part."
-Who?
-Cookie, for example.
"You're not right for the duet.
Punani is a better fit.
You should do that."
Excuse me?
I wanted a specific part
and was fighting to get it.
Nobody has a say in the matter.
In the end, I got the part
nobody wanted.
The part that didn't have many
lines.
As far as I'm concerned,
I've been robbed of my
challenge.
Drama!
I don't understand
why you're saying this now.
You feel that your performance
wasn't up to scratch,
so, now, you decide to say you
were robbed.
It's hypocritical.
It's going downhill!
[laughs]
You felt this way yesterday,
but you didn't say anything?
It's not hypocritical at all,
Cookie.
I said it yesterday.
You didn't listen,
because you were in your
thing...
It wasn't up to me to decide.
But those next to me
heard it wasn't the part I'd
chosen.
You're entitled to feel that
way.
-Of course.
-But I don't understand
how it's my fault.
She chose a part, she's a big
girl.
She can defend herself.
I didn't say it's your fault.
So, why are you mentioning me?
-Well...
-You're a big girl.
You can fight your battle on
your own.
Don't pin this on me.
It's even better
than The Young and the Restless.
"No! I can't let you say that,
Samantha."
You were great as Emeraldwa.
It was hilarious.
Nobody would have danced like
this.
And, uh... [laughs]
Keiona is trying her best
to calm things down. I say, "No!
Honey, let them fight!"
I say, "Fire, fire, fire, keep
going!"
Once again, maybe it's my fault.
I want what's best for the
group,
and I'm always trying to help.
It's okay, I won't do it again.
[sings] And so, on this note...
[all vocalizing]
[sings] Let's go back onstage.
Okay, ladies, it's time to chat.
What do you think of my queens?
Let's start with Cookie.
Cookie was great tonight.
Her look on the runway
is a truly glamorous Hollywood
look.
Who wouldn't want to wear this?
Sara Forever.
I loved it.
This kids sewing club aspect is
very '80s.
Since the start of the
competition,
she's surprised us every time.
Keiona! Quasimollo.
[applause]
-Oh, yeah.
-That was...
I can't stop clapping.
I couldn't stop crying, like
everyone.
Punani! Sara is still the
dominant twin.
Her performance was great.
She's very professional
and knows how to work in pairs.
Her look was very nice today.
But she was slightly below the
others.
Ginger Bitch.
-Oh, my.
-I have to say
that I really loved her look.
But in the Rusical,
she was below the others.
The challenge is greater
when you have a small part.
In Season 12, I had a small part
too.
In a musical, you need to act,
even if you don't have lines.
It's a shame she didn't take
the opportunity to shine,
even when the spotlight wasn't
on her.
Yeah.
Moon. It was crazy tonight.
Yeah, that makeup was...
She managed
to make us smile, despite her
cruel part.
But, on the runway,
I didn't like her outfit.
She's got us used to better than
that.
Mami Watta.
She's getting better every week.
And she still has many things to
give us.
If she wasn't here,
but on a real musical, I would
buy it.
Yes, at one point...
No, come on, everyone...
[indistinct chatter]
Quiet!
Bring back my queens!
My dear queens, we've made our
decision.
[suspenseful music]
You were all exceptional
tonight.
Which means we need
to examine each detail.
Keiona!
[instrumental music]
You seized all the big...
opportunities
the challenge offered.
You're a star.
[instrumental music]
Congratulations,
you are this week's winner.
[shouts of joy]
[applause]
-Thank you.
-Well done, honey.
[screams] I won!
After four weeks at the top.
Thanks, Nicky.
It was a very big challenge for
me,
because Quasimollo goes through
a lot.
I'm really proud to have been
able
to tell his story
and relive mine with a happy
ending.
So, I'm so happy. Thank you so
much.
Well done!
[applause]
Two makes two happy endings,
because you won this!
Nona Source, the circular
platform
for the resale of exceptional
fabrics,
offers you a tailor-made outfit
created by star designer Victor
Weinsanto.
Oh!
-[laughs]
-Thank you.
Thanks, you may leave the stage.
-Bravo, you did it.
-[applause]
-Well done, darling.
-Thanks, Nicky.
I knew you had good taste.
I always trusted you.
[upbeat music]
[suspenseful music]
Cookie Kunty.
Your character is a bad singer,
but your performance
and outfit were fantastic.
-Congratulations!
-Thank you.
-You're staying with us.
-Thanks.
-You may leave the stage.
-[applause]
I went from lip-sync to safe,
and now to the top of the
ranking.
Maybe I've finally arrived!
I'm going to cherish this
moment.
Moon!
[suspenseful music]
Tonight, you made us want to
love
and to love you more than ever.
-Thanks.
-Well done.
You stay with us. You can join
the others.
[cheering]
[applause]
It feels so good.
I've been at the top
of the ranking for two weeks.
I can be proud of myself.
[suspenseful sound]
Mami Watta.
[suspenseful music]
Sara Forever.
[suspense music]
You have amazed us this week,
thank you.
You're staying with us.
You can join the others.
[applause]
[suspenseful music]
It's a tragedy. I'm sad
to see Punani in this position.
It's the person I'm closest to.
Which means that Punani and
Ginger Bitch,
I'm sorry, but you might leave.
[suspenseful sound]
Last week I was in the top-- I
even won--
so, it's a little like...
Come on, girls, come on!
Ginger!
Lip-syncing isn't my thing at
all.
This is the second lip-sync of
my life.
I'll do everything
to captivate the jury
and continue the adventure,
because this is not the end of
Punani.
[suspenseful sound]
There are two queens left on the
stage.
[suspenseful sound]
My dear queens, it's now or
never.
This is your last chance to
impress us
with a legendary lip-sync.
[suspenseful sound]
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
Girl, strap on your heels. Here
we go!
♪ This is the end, the very last
morning ♪
♪ The very last jasmine ♪
♪ Don't let go of my hand ♪
♪ This is the end
The sun in the distance ♪
♪ Collapses alone in his corner
Don't let go, I've got you ♪
♪ The last day of disco
I want to run it over your skin
♪
♪ And make it blush like a poppy
♪ The last day of disco ♪
When I lip sync,
I feel like I'm leaving my body.
♪ And tell you
There's nothing more beautiful ♪
♪ This is the end
The bronze statues ♪
♪ Sink in their grief
Don't let go of my hand ♪
♪ This is the end ♪
I'm having fun.
I make my big braids twirl.
♪ Slump like satin
Don't let go, I've got you ♪
♪ The last day of disco
I want to run it over your skin
♪
♪ And make it blush like a poppy
♪ The last day of disco
I want to hear it in stereo ♪
I give it my all.
I can't fall apart now.
♪ Run it over your skin ♪
♪ The last day of disco ♪
♪ The last day of disco
I want to run it over your skin
♪
♪ And make it blush like a poppy
♪ The last day of disco
I want to hear it in stereo ♪
♪ And tell you
There's nothing more beautiful ♪
♪ This is the end ♪
[cheering]
[applause]
-Well done, girls!
-Thank you.
-It was magnificent.
-I was thinking...
I'm lucky, very lucky.
Thanks. I'm going to sing that
song
'til the end of my life,
and I'll have that vision,
that strength you gave me.
This is a very nice gift.
Thanks from the bottom of my
heart.
Thanks, Juliette.
[applause]
Girls, I've made my decision.
[suspenseful sound]
Punani. Shantay, you stay.
[applause]
I'm very happy to continue the
adventure.
And I'm proud of myself.
Juliette cried.
It was probably for me,
I don't know, but maybe.
Thank you. I have as few words
as when I win.
It's awful. I'll work on my
vocabulary.
Thank you, thank you for
believing in me.
I won't let you down again.
Thanks, Juliette, for this song,
thank you all.
-You can join the others.
-Thank you.
[applause]
Oh, no! How ungrateful!
[laughs]
Ginger.
-Hi, my little bitches.
-How are you?
I've never done so much exercise
in my life.
See, I've lost my belt.
I've lost so much weight.
You started to do drag at over
40.
You are here,
and you make us all very proud.
I hope you are very proud of
yourself too.
-Thank you.
-Because tonight
is not a failure at all.
It was a pleasure
to represent 40-plus queens.
And plus-size queens.
[laughs]
It's not easy to break into this
business
when you're plus-size and older.
I'm glad I did it on television.
You don't need to wear a size 6
and be 23 years old
to be a great queen.
Well done!
[applause].
I can't wait to see
what the future holds for you.
But, for now, sashay away.
[applause]
Well done!
I'm out of here. This place
sucks.
Love you all!
-And don't forget to be a bitch!
-[laughs]
That's it, the adventure is
over.
I feel I have grown, because I
know
that I belonged in the Werk Room
and on this adventure.
I belong in the drag business.
Go ahead and live your dreams.
Make them come true. I did it at
44.
I never thought I'd see this
day,
but I did.
Love you, girls. Fight.
[upbeat music]
You wanted love by the
shovelful,
you got XXL love.
Love you! See you soon!
-Congratulations to you all!
-[applause]
My queens, love yourselves as
you are,
and life will always be a party!
-Music!
-["I'm a Winner, Baby," RuPaul]
Next, on Drag Race France...
For this week's maxi challenge,
we will have a Ball!
[shouts of joy]
You'll have to create your
outfit
with at least three vintage
accessories.
I don't know how to sew.
It's going to be very hard.
Oh! What have I done?
Ready for the Time Ball?
It's going to be a long night!
[laughs]
[cheering]
It's very clever!
My queens, I have a question for
you.
We are all looking at each
other.
There's something wrong.
-I have something to say.
-Yes?
I'm afraid she's going
to say something stupid.