IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
PRODUCTION SUPPORTED BY:
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS AND TOURISM,
KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
EPISODE 1
Hold on. Let me start over.
The song that starts like that.
I heard it a few days ago on the radio,
and they said it helps with insomnia.
You said your sleep pattern
has been off lately.
Try listening to it
when you can't sleep. Okay?
This is Seoul.
Boston, please respond.
Hey, engineering student.
Chan.
Hey, Chan!
Is it a gift?
I could engrave it if you'd like.
The design contest winner is…
Song Haran!
Me? You're kidding, right?
Well, this is unexpected.
The second-year newbie won.
Congratulations, Haran.
- Congrats, newbie!
- Really?
- Congrats! You deserve it!
- Congratulations!
Thank you!
I can't believe it!
Chan! Chan! Chan!
The pen you sent me for my birthday…
I used it to draw a design,
and it won in our company contest!
- Let's go!
- It won?
Thank you so much!
You know,
you're my savior.
Hey, it smells like rain.
You know that particular smell
before it rains?
I love that smell.
But it disappears so quickly,
so I just stand there smelling it.
That's the smell
of organic matter diffusing.
It's called petrichor,
and it's when plant-derived
organic matter spreads--
- Hey, nerd. Stop.
- The pores in rock crevices…
Stop ruining my joy
with science talk, you nerd.
Anyway, smelling the rain
puts me in a good mood.
You should try it sometime.
I recommend it.
But the catch is that
you always end up with a nasty cold.
ACHOO!
Hey, it's a vapor trail.
I wish I could get on a plane
and go see Chan.
The boyfriend who's studying in Boston?
I heard Chan's too busy with research
to come during vacation.
Eunchan, you know Haran's boyfriend?
A bit.
He's my little brother.
- What?
- Really?
Let's enjoy our four days off
and work hard for our next season.
Yes, ma'am!
Four days?
Hey, Yujeong!
We're getting together later.
You free?
Why are you running?
I'm going to Boston to meet Chan.
I'll tell you everything later.
Tsk.
Chan, I saw a vapor trail earlier.
But that made me want
to get on a plane to go see you.
So…
Ta-da! I'm at the airport!
Isn't that crazy?
I'll have to come back
after only a few hours,
but I wanted
to tell you something in person.
I'll be there at about 1:00 p.m.
in Boston, so just hang in there.
Wait.
I changed my mind.
I'm going to say it now. Hang on.
Chan.
I love you.
I love you, Chan.
BIT, please.
5 MINUTES, 0.7 MILES
Just five minutes left.
Hey!
EUNCHAN
Hello?
Haran, what do I do?
Chan…
Chan is…
SEOUL, SEVEN YEARS LATER
Let's begin.
One, two, three.
Awesome.
- All right.
- Let's take a few more and call it.
Okay.
Excuse me. Coming through.
- Hi.
- Hey. The outfits…
I like how the texture shows here.
Nice.
- Nice! You look great.
- Perfect.
Dart. 0.5.
Ms. Kim is here.
Let's fix the darts by 0.5 inches
before resuming.
Start pinning right away!
Lights.
Dim the backlight by 10%
and adjust the fill lights.
Everyone, move.
- All right.
- Hurry!
Quickly, everyone!
All right.
Two, three.
Okay.
Okay. Great work, everyone.
Great work, everyone.
The Korean queen of fashion,
the head of Nana Atelier.
Give a round of applause
to our queen, Nana.
It's fine.
Clap for the person in charge, not me.
Ah, the person who oversaw it all,
from the outfits to the shoot.
Let's give a hand
to our lead designer, Song Haran!
Excuse me…
I'm sorry, but I don't think she's here.
Where did she go?
She's not here?
What's going on?
She was just here.
She even approved the final select shots.
Ghosting…
She disappeared again,
like always.
Ms. Song's routine never changes.
She's like my salary.
She disappears every time.
Right.
Mr. Yeon's coming to our hotel.
The car rental…
Where did he go?
Did he wander off again?
Do you guys remember what I just told you?
Yeah!
Okay, let's go.
What's one plus one?
- Two!
Ben, look.
Didn't it come out nice?
I bet
you're the only one in this world
who always makes friends
with everyone on the plane.
You think so?
Mm!
This taste brings back memories.
When was the last time you were in Korea?
It's been about seven years.
Isn't your family in Korea?
Why didn't you come--
Ben. Let's go to Hangang River
after the meeting.
No, wait. Maybe Namsan?
Oh!
I got a list, man.
Okay. Let's look through
my Seoul destinations list.
First…
No, I can't hear you! I'm going to sleep.
Then, I'll have fun by myself.
Great. Go do that.
I really did come back.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Nice to meet you. I'm Yeon Taeseok.
It's nice to meet you,
Mr. Yeon!
I really wanted to see you.
After communicating through just emails,
I knew I'd be happy,
but I can't believe how excited I am.
Well, I'm not that excited…
Just think of him
like a golden retriever
who loves people.
I see. A golden retriever.
But your Korean is really…
Ah. I'm Ben.
My wife's Korean,
and my in-laws live in Pangyo.
- Ah. Right. Ben.
- Yes.
Stand over here, Ben.
Let me formally introduce myself.
I'm the one who proposed this project
and a supervisor
with CAN Animation Studio, Seon…
Well, many people get confused,
so let me tell you in advance.
My name's Seonu Chan, not Seon Uchan.
- This too?
- Mmm-hmm.
Wait. Hang on. I can't carry this alone.
You can do it, baby.
- Great work, guys.
- Great job.
- Great work, everyone.
- Good job.
After checking if we have everything,
let's clean up and go.
We should go now
if we want to make it to the afterparty.
What's going on?
I guess Ms. Song didn't arrive first.
- I should text her to come to the party.
- Stop!
Sol, our rookie intern.
You're still clueless about her.
Honey, have you ever had lunch
with Ms. Song before?
- Yes or no?
- No, never.
She always leaves first during lunchtime,
so she must be busy meeting people.
- Not at all.
- Every day, all the time.
Do you think it makes sense
to always have plans?
Gosh. Are you saying
she's avoiding us on purpose?
That's right.
She loves to brood on her own.
She really isn't my vibe.
Where is she
always disappearing to?
PARK GENIUS
Two points.
Three points.
I got it!
It looks so good.
Mmm.
CHAN SENT PHOTOS
Oh, God.
What sort of Korean
enjoys Korea this much?
Sorry about that.
The ice machine
is acting up today.
Be quiet.
Quiet!
Good boy.
This is AI.
Oh, those.
If you're interested, check them out.
One of my regulars here
organized an exhibit,
and they're showing paintings
for each season.
You can take a bunch of those
and go with friends.
One is enough. Thank you.
Ah. Really?
Going by yourself will be nice, too.
RADIANT SEASONS
Proceed through
the four seasonal rooms in order.
Okay.
"SHIM"
Coffee House
SPRING ROOM, THE WONDER OF LIFE
WINTER ROOM, DEEP SILENCE
A lone woman
stands with her back turned
in a white, snowy landscape,
quietly conveying
a sense of sorrow and emptiness.
Rather than sharp tension,
the artist's brush captures
the gentle air
and subtle tremble of light.
No way…
Chan.
I love you, Chan.
I'm sorry.
You idiot.
What will you do if it really is her?
Huh?
Hey, watch out.
Watch out!
Song Haran!
Are you okay?
That was close.
Are you all right?
Gosh. That was close.
Are you okay?
Should we call emergency services?
Are you all right?
- Are you okay?
- Come quickly!
- Yes, I'm okay.
- Are you okay?
- Is anyone hurt?
Get down here!
- Are they okay?
- It's dangerous.
You should all come down.
- That was so close.
- Come on.
Hey, Too Much.
Why is a Korean so busy touring Seoul?
Right?
Maybe I overdid it.
I fled seven years ago
because I thought I'd see her
everywhere I went.
Seoul seems so big,
but it was actually really small.
Are you saying it's big or small?
Hey, Chan.
Did something happen?
Mmm…
Something did happen…
but I'm going to pretend it didn't.
I'll think about this today
and forget about it tomorrow,
so don't worry and go to bed.
Bye.
RADIANT SEASONS
Song Haran!
I'm sure they called my name.
Who was it?
Of the three, I'm in charge of designing
and planning the Korean character…
CHARACTERS
NIA, WON, FIN
Just think of me
as the guy in charge of Won.
To highlight the identities
of each character,
we planned collaborations
with designers from each country.
I made the collaboration offer
because I really wanted you
to design the Korean character's outfits.
What do you think, Ms. Kim?
Ms. Kim?
So why should I do this?
I was curious.
To be honest, I was excited.
I thought your roots
were similar to Won's.
Won isn't someone who shines like the sun.
Instead, she gives light
to those in the darkness,
like the moon.
"Douceur lunaire."
What's that?
"Soft moonlight."
The first collection you put out
when you were 22.
I saw it myself.
You reinterpreted Korean traditional silk
through moonlight.
You saw it yourself?
It was on display at the fashion school
you attended in France.
Thanks to you,
I got to see the Eiffel Tower, too.
So, what if you expressed Won
with roots like that?
Just imagining that made me so excited.
So?
What should we do first?
Yes!
Unbelievable.
Then, let's take a selfie first
to celebrate this day.
Sorry, but you really shouldn't…
Was I being rude, by any chance?
Very rude.
You know,
my left side is prettier.
Then, I'll take one from the left.
One, two, three.
Should we show you the story reel first?
- The video will be pretty helpful.
- Sure.
The USB is in my car,
so I'll go and get it.
CHARACTER "WON"
It's strange.
- She looks familiar.
- Pardon?
It's an original character
that Chan created.
No…
I'm sure I've seen that face before.
Hmm?
Huh.
Ms. Song.
Right.
This character looks like
our lead designer, Song Haran.
I'm sorry.
I dropped my pen by accident.
May I help you?
Are you here for the collaboration?
No…
Oh.
Yes, I am.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Song Haran, the lead designer.
"It's nice to meet you"?
- Excuse me?
- Right.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Seonu Chan.
My pen…
Ah… Here.
Thank you.
Do you have something to say?
No.
NANA ATELIER DESIGNERS
LEAD DESIGNER SONG HARAN
Hey, Chan.
- What happened to you?
- It's fine.
I'm sorry.
My prior engagement
ran longer than expected.
No need for excuses.
Say hello.
This is Lead Designer Song Haran,
who will be the main support
for this collaboration project.
She'll be working with you
for the entire three months.
Let's continue.
Then,
let's watch the story reel together.
Wait.
Mr. Seonu.
That character.
Was it based on someone?
No, it just came to mind.
My grandmother…
I mean, Ms. Kim said that
Won resembles my sister…
I mean, Lead Designer Song Haran.
- Ooh!
- Oops.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I…
I can't stand those messy clothes.
- Remy, get him a new shirt.
- Yes, ma'am.
We'll resume in 10 minutes.
Why don't you wait
in the fitting room?
I'll pick out a pretty shirt for you.
It's on the fourth floor.
- I'll do it.
- No, it's fine.
It's all right.
Just head to the fourth floor.
Can you deliver this to the animator?
I mean, seeing you
brooding like this by yourself again…
You look very, very…
free right now.
I'll leave your shirt here.
I'm sorry! You weren't answering.
Right.
Ah…
Here's your shirt.
Thank you.
What's with you today?
You've been acting weird…
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Ben.
I'm stepping out of this project.
What?
You stick to the schedule.
I'll head back to the US.
This isn't funny, Chan.
I'll call you as soon as I find
a replacement supervisor.
What on earth…
Are you serious right now?
You know the director's coming here
with the EA team soon, right?
Hundreds of people have been working
on this project for years
because they believed in you.
Not to mention the expenses.
Seonu Chan.
The Seonu Chan I know wouldn't do this.
No, he can't.
Tell me the reason.
Because I'm scared.
I shouldn't be here.
What do you mean?
Sorry, Ben. Not now.
Let's talk about it later, man.
You said
drawing made you so happy.
When you became a supervisor,
you asked me to smack you
because it felt like a dream.
Now I see
just how little it really means to you.
Fine. Go.
I don't need a supervisor
who gives up so easily on his work.
WON COSTUME COLLABORATION PROPOSAL
Memento mori…
He sure left quick.
Morning, Ben. How are you?
Wait, actually. It's probably
nighttime there, right?
Anyway, I was just wondering
how the first meeting went
for the fashion collaboration.
Uh, yeah, it went well, but…
Before we get into that,
there's been a bit of an issue with Chan.
- Um…
- Hey, am I late?
Sorry. I was taking a shower.
I thought I should get dressed
before hopping on.
Let's share it.
Okay.
Okay, um…
I've sent the materials to Ms. Kim,
and we're meeting in a couple of days
to discuss the concept.
All right. Sounds great.
- Right?
- Yeah. Yeah. That's right. Uh…
- Seonu Chan.
- Yeah?
- What was that?
- What?
Your clothes were gone.
Oh. I dropped them off at the cleaners.
They were all crumpled.
- Let's go get some soy-marinated crabs.
- Soy-marinated crabs?
It's midnight.
Don't you know shops are open
24 hours a day in Korea?
We need to eat well
in order to work hard, you know.
- Right, Producer Ben?
- Seonu Chan.
- You're buying.
- No, I'm not. Last one out is buying.
Three months…
Just three months.
I'm sure nothing will happen.
Grandma.
- Hey.
- I'm here.
How was your day?
Mmm. It was tough.
It's hard being a high school senior.
But…
Ta-da!
I got a perfect score
after all that studying.
Gosh, you did a great job.
These brains and these looks.
I got so many good genes
from you, Grandma.
But what did I say
was just as important as studying?
Managing my health.
Here.
I've been taking the tonics
that Mr. Yeon gave me to help me focus.
I'll go get some rest.
Good night, Grandma.
Good night.
How are you busier
than a high school senior?
Where on earth have you…
Forget it. Go upstairs.
Good night.
Why leave your perfectly fine room
and go into that cave?
Come to my study.
What?
Don't make me repeat myself.
Meet Photographer Yoon.
He's been interested in you
for a long time.
He's talented and has great character.
Someone like that is rare.
Give him a chance.
- No, I'm not interested in dating--
- I know.
Just change your mind.
I'll set a date, so meet with him.
I'm sorry.
FAREWELL TO MY FORMER LIFE
Good morning.
"Good morning"?
When did you get home last night?
Just a little after midnight.
I suddenly got a bunch of plans.
Why is everyone
in this household so extreme?
I wish I could mix the two of you.
What? Me and who?
My lonely eldest sister?
At a construction site in Seoul,
a large tower of scaffolding
begins to tilt toward the sidewalk.
The scaffolding was a second away
from falling on a woman passing by.
What's with all this fuss again?
What are you doing?
Well…
I'm trying to protect
my beautiful grandmother's skin
from all the electromagnetic waves.
It's a display of touching devotion
from your second granddaughter.
I'll go get ready for work now.
She still hasn't sobered up yet.
Haran!
What? Where is she?
Are you in there again?
Come out here right now!
What is it?
What?
This woman passing by who almost
got hurt at a construction site.
This is you, isn't it?
It is.
What?
Even I was startled by this.
What if Grandma had seen this?
Please, keep your head on straight
when you're outside. Okay?
I'll keep that in mind.
The woman stopped just in time
when someone urgently called her name.
Fortunately, that stopped
- what could've been a terrible…
- Hang on.
What?
This shirt…
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Wow. If it weren't for him,
you would've been a goner.
- Hmm? That shirt…
- You recognize it too, right?
Yeah. We remember every color
and texture that people wear.
Isn't that…
the animator's shirt?
- It is. He wore it at the meeting.
- What on earth?
Then, does that mean he was passing by
and shouted when he saw
that you were in danger?
He called out my name.
That's before we even met.
What? How did he call you by your name
when he doesn't know it?
Ah. I get it.
He must be someone in the industry
who knows you.
You're known for your looks.
Plus, plenty of people
wear the same clothes.
You think so?
That's the only way it makes sense.
So who could this savior be?
Right?
Who could it be?
Oh. Hello, Ms. Song.
Good morning.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Yes?
Ms. Song, the black dress sample is here.
The measurements are perfect.
Let's see it on a mannequin…
I'll wear it.
That will be easier to check.
- Okay. Thanks.
- No problem.
WORK ORDER
Oh?
Ms. Song.
What's with this men's shirt?
Just give that to me
and change into the dress.
Okay.
I'm sure it's the same shirt.
Plenty of people
wear the same clothes.
The art exhibit.
RADIANT SEASONS
I went to the exhibit
on the day of our lookbook shoot…
It was the 16th.
He was at the exhibit
on the same day as me.
Then…
he really was the one who called my name?
SEONU CHAN
Seonu Chan.
Seonu Chan…
It doesn't ring a bell.
How did he know my name?
SEONU CHAN
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Song Haran, the lead designer.
Chan. Chan.
I love you.
I love you, Chan.
Ms. Song.
- Something weird was delivered to you.
- What a nutjob.
What are you going to do?
I'm the one who received this delivery.
I'm going to be traumatized
after seeing something that sickening
with my pretty eyes.
Do you have any idea
who could've done this?
Not at all.
Did you have a bad breakup recently?
Those kind of exes turn into stalkers--
It's fine. This is a personal matter.
Please get back to work.
We don't know what these weirdos
might do if we leave them be.
He's right. A crazy stalker like this
could pop out of nowhere and do something…
Thanks for your concern,
but I'll deal with it myself.
- We're just worried…
- Ms. Song…
That darned glass.
She's always turning it…
My pretty hands…
What kind of crazy jerk would do this?
Hang on…
Haran. I mean, Ms. Song
since we're at work.
The stalker who sent those photos…
Maybe it's the same guy
who called your name in the street.
Right, ma'am?
He could've been following you,
and he could've yelled your name
by accident when you were in danger.
- If you're done, get back to work.
- Work isn't important right now.
All right, Ms. Song.
- What are you doing?
- There's a smudge on it.
Just a second.
I'll excuse myself.
If the stalker who sent the photos
is the same guy who called my name…
Seonu Chan?
WON CHARACTER CONCEPT
Ms. Kim said that
Won resembles my sister…
I mean, Lead Designer Song Haran.
If the character
is based on the type of girl he likes,
maybe he saw that I looked similar
when he came to Korea
and learned my name after stalking me.
Then, he followed me to the art exhibit
and witnessed the accident.
I bet he didn't know
we'd be working together.
Is that why he reacted like that?
Right.
It's…
It's nice to meet you.
It's because it wasn't
his first time seeing me.
Emergency ice water for you.
You seemed frustrated
about something.
The ice machine
stopped acting up.
One of my regulars who's really handy
dropped by and fixed it instantly.
Thank you.
There's an urgent meeting
with a client.
Come to Grand Lumiere Hotel
by 7:00 p.m. tonight.
WON CHARACTER CONCEPT
"SHIM"
Coffee House
- Hello.
- Hey!
My VVIP regular who fixed my ice machine.
Come on in.
Welcome.
Hi, Genius.
Here. Sit down.
I'll make you some coffee.
Okay. Thank you.
Genius, wait.
Did you go to the art exhibit?
You said you'd go right away
when I gave you the ticket.
Uh…
Yes. Thank you for the ticket.
But for someone
who always smiles so handsomely,
why do you look so gloomy today?
Uh…
Right?
I'm usually really handsome,
but I didn't get much sleep,
so I guess I look less handsome today.
Why didn't you get much sleep?
Did you have a nightmare?
Oh.
Do you play the harmonica?
Oh, that.
I found it while cleaning out my clutter.
I get out of breath easily now,
so my chest hurts.
I can't play it so well anymore.
- Here.
- Thank you.
I used to play that often
in my neighborhood when I was little.
Where's your hometown?
Chuncheon.
All I did was find one old object,
but it reminded me of my old hometown
and my childhood friends.
It came with a full package
of old memories.
Memories…
are kind of like sausage links.
What? Sausage links?
Yes.
Even if you think
you've forgotten everything,
recalling just one memory…
seems to bring everything else along.
Like sausage links.
Hey.
Wait just a moment.
- Okay.
- Hang on.
What kind of meeting is it?
I should at least know…
I told you I'd set you up
on a date with Photographer Yoon.
No.
If that's what this is, I'm not attending.
I'm sorry.
How long do I have to see you
act like this?
It's been seven years.
Everyone gets back up and lives
after going through immense pain.
You're the only one who refuses to.
Are you going to keep running away
from everything like a coward?
You can survive
with at least one person to rely on.
But with no one, you'll crumble.
Mr. Yoon can be someone like that for you.
He's a good man, so--
I don't need a good man!
How can you…
Of all people, how can you do this to me?
I'm the one who wants to live like this.
I feel comfortable this way.
I know, okay?
I know I shouldn't live like this.
I know I'm being stupid and weird.
But…
I'm too scared.
I don't want to end up
being anxious and worried every day
that something might happen
to someone I care about.
So just let me live like this.
If there's no one by my side,
at least nothing bad will happen.
Dad! Mom!
Dad! Dad!
Dad! Mom…
Mom, get up! Mom!
Oh, my God!
Help!
No, Mom…
Mom!
Haran.
I can't believe what happened. Hmm?
Grandma.
Mom, Dad,
and Chan…
Even Chan is gone.
Chan is dead, too.
Haran, let's go home. Okay?
Chan is dead too, Grandma.
Chan…
Chan is dead, too.
Grandma…
At least show Mr. Yoon
some basic courtesy.
Oh.
I'm sorry. I played without permission.
Bravo!
Will you have
some wine with me?
There's some sediment in this wine,
so let's drink this
after it settles in a bit.
Okay.
By the way, I guess you like Bach.
No.
I just happened to hear about the song.
Someone told me it's good for insomnia.
Seeing your expression,
I'm guessing today's the kind of day
when your memories come flooding back.
From the way they're coming back to me,
I guess I haven't forgotten about them.
They were just…
buried for a while.
Mmm.
The thing about memories
is that sometimes…
they're really rebellious.
The more you try to forget,
the more vivid they become.
And when you want to remember,
they run away from you.
So don't strain yourself.
Just try leaving them be.
Just like this wine,
memories get cloudy if you disturb them.
But if you leave them be,
they'll eventually become clearer.
All right.
I'll try to just leave them be.
- Let's drink.
- Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'll talk to Ms. Kim and make sure
this mistake doesn't happen again.
I came to say that you don't have
to waste your time on me.
Yes, I know.
I know you don't have any feelings for me,
but I really am sincere…
Are you kidding me?
Right. I understand
you don't want to hear it.
But I really am sincere--
I'm sincerely sorry,
but something urgent came up.
- I'll get going. I'm sorry.
- Excuse me?
Ms. Song!
What?
Why are you…
Could you say my name?
- What?
- You're the one who called my name
in front of the art museum
on the 16th, right?
I met you for the first time
a few days ago.
How long have you known me?
Tell me how you know me.
What are you hiding?
Someone I have to meet…
Someone who brought me back to life
and seems to hold…
the keys to my life.
The seasons of life
don't always come in order.
Sometimes, the moment
you feel like it's spring,
a harsh winter suddenly arrives.
Seven years ago,
in the midst of my coldest winter,
she came into my life
like a warm spring breeze.
And now, she's here again.
And that day, we had no idea
whether our future seasons
would be warm like spring
or harsh like winter.
Seonu Chan…
who are you?
I love you, Chan.
I love you,
Kang Hyeokchan.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Mr. Seonu.
Why are you stalking me?
It feels like
it's hard to get close to her.
She never talks about herself.
How did you know
I don't like eggplants?
There's another guy who speaks like him.
Why does this keep happening?
It's scaring me.
What are you doing here?
I'm going to live here.
They look good together.
Keep an eye on Ms. Song
and Seonu Chan.
Translated by Juyoung Park