Hurry, hurry, hurry. Come on.
Hurry! Come on!
♪ Things haven't been the same
Since you came into my life ♪
Hi. Hi.
-John! John!
-Hello.
John! John, right here. John!
♪ Happiness lies in your own hand ♪
♪ It took me much too long ♪
♪ To understand how it could be ♪
♪ Until you shared your secret with me ♪
-…you've got a great manicure.
-John.
-Hey.
-Who are you with?
Oh, I'm flying solo tonight.
Congrats on the line.
I've been dying to put
a coffee table into this world
since I was old enough
to put my chin on one.
And Donald Judd furniture
in the flagship store. You've got guts.
One, America will appreciate
a little Donald Judd injection
into their boring homes, and two...
Who told you
about the flagship store?
Well, that was my two. Who told you?
It's top secret.
I have my sources.
So do I, John. So do I.
I'm gonna get a drink.
I'm too nice. That's the problem.
-This wouldn't happen.
-No, you're absolutely not.
♪ Something's comin' over, mmm-mmm ♪
♪ Something's comin' over me ♪
♪ My baby's got a secret ♪
♪ Mmm-mmm, something's comin' over ♪
♪ Mmm-mmm, something's comin' over me ♪
♪ My baby's got a secret ♪
♪ Mmm-mmm, my baby's got a secret ♪
Kelly convinced me to have riding lessons.
-I fell off and broke my collarbone.
-Disaster.
He hasn't stopped talking about it.
I'm never going on a horse again!
Hey, guys, I'm gonna take off.
Got an early morning.
Oh, I don't believe you for a second.
Who are you chasing tonight?
I'm kinda off the market, Calvin.
-Good night.
-Good night, John.
I bet he's on his way down
for a nightcap in manhole.
You never know.
Anyway, I fell off.
I broke my collarbone and ended up
in the hospital for three weeks.
-Hi.
-Stop, stop.
The paparazzi, they're… right there.
Go.
Go! Ten paces ahead. 20!
Come on.
Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me.
-Did you forget your keys again?
-No, they gotta be here somewhere.
Oh. I guess it's just not
in the cards for tonight.
Don't you even… mmm.
-Oh, my God. Hi.
-Oh, thank God.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Good night.
Seriously,
I have to sleep at home tonight.
-I told you on the way over.
-No, stay. But you always say that.
Hmm.
-A wedding band.
-Hmm.
I knew there was something
you weren't telling me.
It's my dad's.
-What time is it?
-7:30.
And you don't have to be in till 9:00,
so, you know.
No, no. I have to get out of here before
your photo seagulls arrive downstairs.
-No, come back.
-Okay.
We can both leave later together.
-Oh, yeah?
-I mean, it's gonna happen eventually.
Mm-hmm.
I was lucky enough the first time
and missed the photos.
I'm just very, very happy
there's a second time.
Me too.
But I like it just right here.
Just us.
That's it.
Okay.
Can I borrow this?
I should at least look a little different
if I'm gonna go in in the same clothes.
-What?
-You're gonna do it.
You're gonna do it, aren't you?
You're gonna break my heart.
Is that your morning-after line?
So smooth.
Oh, it just makes me wanna…
-Call into work…
-Yeah?
-…quit…
-Mm-hmm?
-…and stay in bed all day.
-Yeah.
Who was the very first person
to break your heart?
If it ever happens,
you'll be the first to know.
Did you see this?
Look, they're stealing the Kate posters.
Give me that controversy.
I love it.
Mmm.
However, there's this.
Kate's irate.
Irate about what? Being an overnight
sensation with the world at her feet?
I think it's more
about the world in her face.
I actually kinda feel for her.
Oh, come on.
She knew what she was signing up for.
Did she?
She was just a girl from Croydon
who booked a job and then all this.
I don't think she expected
to be a sensation any more than we did.
Oh, I stopped feeling sorry
for famous people a long time ago.
Yes, boo-hoo,
fame takes some things away from you,
but it gives you more.
And if young Kate doesn't like it,
-she can always go back to Croydon.
-Mmm.
Over your dead body.
Hey, what is that that you're wearing?
It's really kind of terrific.
Oh, I just threw it on this morning.
What are you doing?
No, God. Please, no.
-I hate it when you do this.
-Don't run away from me.
Oh, God.
No.
You can run, but you cannot hide.
Just put it…
Come on. You're wonderful.
Just one.
Aphrodite. Second century BC.
I broke this once.
Glued it back together. She never noticed.
Of course she did.
Do we really have to sell all of this?
No, not everything. That's why we're here.
It's just the public auction of it all
feels so intrusive.
Well, a private auction isn't gonna
generate a fraction of the money we need
to pay off a $34 million inheritance tax.
They cataloged my high chair.
Do you wanna bid on it?
Oh, my God.
Wow. I'd ask what that is,
but like any true artist,
you stated it very clearly on the page.
This is an airplane.
I can't believe she kept this.
Is it flying
over fire or the ocean?
-The landscape is subjective.
-Mmm.
You should keep that.
Oh, her swimming ring.
She'd wear this when she'd swim,
so she wouldn't lose her engagement
and wedding ring.
I love that that is what
was disposable in her mind.
How are you holding up?
-Still feels surreal.
-Mmm.
I think of things
that would make her laugh,
and suddenly I'm reminded
that she's not here anymore.
I think this is the first time in my life
where I actually feel as old as I am.
Well, when you can't agonize
over your parents' mortality,
you have no choice
but to contemplate your own.
Hell of an appraisal.
It's funny,
now that I have kids of my own,
I really understand why
she needed to parent us differently.
You realize from the minute they're born,
you need to be
a different parent completely.
Clean slate.
How do you think
she parented us differently?
I think after Dad, we were
just ensconced in so much chaos.
You needed structure and stability,
and I didn't wanna be treated
like a little kid anymore.
I refused to be.
That I remember.
I do like to think she held on
until she knew you were ready.
Ready for what?
To make a life for yourself
as you see fit.
-I gotta go. Oh.
-Okay.
-I'll see you later.
Don't forget about dinner at ours.
-Saturday.
-And don't break anything.
I'll try.
Fuck. Narcy, this is so good.
Don't show this to Calvin.
Keep this for yourself.
By the time
I get the nerve to leave him,
this rag'll return to the earth.
-Aren't you gonna go get it?
-No, just let it ring.
-Okay.
-Hello.
Please leave a message after the tone.
-Hi, it's me, John.
-Oh.
Just, uh, seeing if you're around.
Mm-hmm.
-Okay, bye.
-Aw, keep going.
Oh, you are unreal. Screening him.
What, did you read that
in The Rules or something?
It's just feeling a little intense.
Yeah, as it should be.
Jesus. Enjoy it a little.
Have some fun.
You always know when to bail.
I think I might have
missed the moment this time.
It's all moving really fast.
I'm meeting his friends tomorrow.
For drinks. I don't know.
Oh. Sick of JFK Jr.
Life, so tough, huh? What do you want?
Can you just call him John?
You sound like a Post headline.
Okay.
I don't know what I want.
I know what I don't want.
If this keeps going,
the press is gonna find out.
Maybe in a month. Maybe tomorrow.
Before that happens,
I need to know that it's real.
I can't just have fun
and then forever be known as JFK Jr's ex.
Hey, Carolyn, please.
-His name is John. Mmm?
-Uh-huh.
Just go. Don't be weird.
Hello,
please leave a message after the tone.
Hey, it's me again.
Sorry to clog up your machine like this,
but, uh, I totally forgot
to tell you something.
Yeah, I'm kind of, like,
right outside your apartment right now.
Oh, my God. I have to come and see...
No, no, no. Stay here.
And I was thinking
about going to get a burger
down at this dive at Breezy Point.
They know who I am and they
don't give one shit and it's really nice.
-It's right on the water.
-Oh.
They've got boats you can
cruise around on, fresh air…
…and I was wondering if you'd wanna
come with me.
-If you don't go out there, I will.
-But you're not home.
-Stay. Stay.
-Hmm? Hmm? Hmm?
You're not answering my calls right now.
Come on.
I guess you are home.
You're wild.
♪ If you make sure you're connected ♪
♪ The writing's on the wall ♪
♪ But if your mind's neglected ♪
♪ Stumble, you might fall ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ I ain't gonna go blind ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ I see through you ♪
♪ I'm gonna get myself
I'm gonna get myself ♪
♪ I'm gonna get myself connected ♪
♪ I ain't gonna go blind… ♪
I know that there's a ton
of political magazines out there,
but this one's gonna be different.
It's gonna be full of ideas
from unexpected places.
-Uh, a public square...
-Your magazine needs to be sexy.
Sorry, I love your ideas about content,
but I talk about magazine ad buys all day.
And if you're gonna compete
with a whole news stand of sexy covers,
then your cover has got to be sexy
and let their brains be changed
by what's on the inside.
You sound like Berman.
Could this Berman fellow
actually be right about something?
He's right about a lot of things.
He may not have magazine experience,
but he's brilliant.
He's my partner,
and he's always had my back.
I trust him.
And trust for me is hard to come by.
Yeah, same.
You close with your dad?
You always wear that,
but he never seems to come up.
Really close with my stepdad,
but Dad Dad, he was great.
Shit, have I missed something?
Did you lose your dad too?
No, no, no, no. My real dad's still alive.
It was just your typical
suburban 1970s divorce,
but I was young, so it didn't register.
You know, bad things can register
even if you're too young
to understand them.
Maybe.
But hey, I cut you off.
Go on about the magazine.
Convenient how that steers you
away from talking about yourself.
I put this song on.
I think I put this one on.
Or I did too.
You like this song?
What animal doesn't like Sade?
♪ I gave you all the love I got ♪
Come here.
♪ I gave you love ♪
♪ I gave you all that I have inside
And you took my love ♪
♪ You took my love ♪
♪ This is no ordinary love ♪
♪ No ordinary love ♪
-The magazine cover should be sexy.
-Hey.
We can do sexy on the outside,
-wonky on the inside.
-Mmm.
Well, I think I've been trying to sell you
on that exact concept for months.
Yeah, well, maybe you were right.
You are right about some things sometimes.
Oh.
Maybe you can realize that
sooner in the future?
-Yeah, I'll try.
-Try hard.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
Santina.
So where's the latest victim?
Santina, be nice.
I heard a little about her
from Trey at Tunnel.
He says he sees her out a lot.
I think I know her a little bit better
than your random drug dealer.
Trey's a random drug friend, okay?
Just getting your back, checking around.
No big. Where is she?
Wow, someone's giving John
the John treatment.
Every minute she's late,
I'm loving her more.
-Mm-hmm.
-Do you think she's gonna show?
She's the first woman I've dated
who doesn't wanna be seen
with me in public, so…
Not counting Madonna.
Seriously, she's different, you guys.
Okay.
They're always different.
-Sounds like my ex-girlfriend.
-Yeah.
Aha.
-Hi, sorry I'm late. It was a work thing.
-Hi.
-It just went on and on. Hi.
-Carolyn.
Santina, Michael,
Anthony, Tommy and Colin.
Hi, Santina, Michael,
Anthony, Tommy, Colin.
-Nice.
-Wow.
Thank you. It's a pleasure.
Carolyn, uh, Berman and I
were just talking about the mag.
What was it you were asking me
about, um, that discount thing?
Oh, I just asked John if you guys
were doing frequency discounts.
A rate for buyers who place
a certain number of ads in a period.
Yeah, yeah, we're working on that. Yeah.
-Berman, you think we should hire her?
-Oh, you can't afford me.
I told John I… I love your idea
for the covers. It's just smart.
Thank you.
Is it smart like the kayak company?
Or is it smart
like the rent-a-dog company?
Hey, that was a good idea.
You and John are just too smart.
-What can I say?
-Yeah, okay.
Anything more involved than the ball
of yarn that Colin gets to play with
at Dad's investment firm
is a little bit too much for him to grasp.
I will die richer than all of you.
You know, we haven't seen
the waiter in a while.
I'm gonna go get a bottle from the bar.
-Yes, please.
-Sounds good.
Yeah.
So how's everything at Calvin Klein?
Calvin's great.
We're about to launch
our new unisex fragrance,
so if you guys play your cards right…
What does it smell like?
Oh. You know,
like you could go either way.
Oh.
So… fitting.
-That's good.
-Smart.
-She means…
-I got it.
Hey, that happens
literally everywhere the guy goes.
He won't take her number,
not in front of you.
He's just being polite.
To her or to me?
What you got?
White wine.
Hey. All right, who wants some?
Here we go.
Where's my glass?
Nice lighter. "Blue eyes."
-Gift from an ex.
-Oh!
Wow. Classic John.
What did she expect from Margot?
Ugh, still such a fricking DG girl.
You've got to give me that.
Hey, do you know Trey from Tunnel?
-Trey. Um…
-Mm-hmm.
Nope, why? Is he a friend of yours?
From what I've heard, I hope not.
Smells like victory.
-You guys, I gotta go.
-No, stay for dinner.
No. You said drinks.
So, I made dinner plans.
We got more questions. Cancel.
You do not know my mother.
You do not cancel on Ann Marie Messina.
Take me with you. These guys bore me.
You also don't know my mother.
Showing up with you spur of the moment
would not go over well
with Ann Marie Messina.
But you guys, this was so fun
after hearing so much about you.
No matter what John says,
I think you guys are great.
Bye.
The next one, when we have more time.
Damn,
always leave them wanting more.
This one knows how to play the game.
Yeah. Hold on a second.
She's not playing. You guys just
don't know a real one when you see one.
I've seen plenty of real ones.
Hey.
What are you doing tomorrow night?
My sister's throwing a party.
You should come.
Wouldn't that be a little soon?
Yeah, but I want you to meet her.
Okay, sure.
-Sure, why not?
-Great.
What can I bring?
A bottle of wine? Flowers?
No, no.
They've always got everything covered.
I'm just happy to bring you.
-Night.
-Bye.
Calvin has his moods,
but if you give him space,
you remind him of the bigger picture,
he comes around.
-I kinda wanna meet him, but I'm scared.
-Mmm.
Mom, stop cleaning. It's just gonna
get messy as soon as you leave.
I cannot eat my dinner looking at this.
All right?
Oh, I hope he knows
how lucky he is to have you,
because I could not endure
that kind of ego day in and day out.
Yeah, probably makes you wanna be
around, like, normal, hardworking people.
Like, low-maintenance.
-Low profile.
-Stop.
What? What does that mean?
-Nothing.
-Just tell her.
-There's nothing to tell. Stop.
-She's not gonna care.
Carolyn's, uh,
hanging out with John again.
-John?
-Sorry, Kennedy Jr.
I should've clarified.
What happened to the movie star
that he left you for?
-Nobody left anybody.
-Mm-hmm.
Both of us were just…
-It was bad timing.
-Mmm.
But it's good timing now?
It's different this time.
But it's also not serious.
We're just having fun.
Oh, yeah. Like going to his sister,
Caroline's house tomorrow night.
Lauren, can you just stop.
No, no. She seems like a ball.
So, it's not serious, it's new,
but you're meeting his sister?
It's just a party. It's not like
we're meeting up to meet each other.
It's really not a big deal, Mom. I swear.
Right, well, but you're giving him
a second chance,
so that leads me
to believe otherwise, right?
Listen, honey,
everything is going so well right now.
And that is because of who you are,
just you and the hard work that you do.
I just don't want you to lose yourself.
When has that ever happened?
Exactly.
I also didn't think
you were the kind of woman
who says, "It's different this time."
-You want some sweet and sour sauce?
-Stop, stop.
Hi.
One second.
C, you're gorgeous.
Come on.
This is friendly territory.
They're gonna love you.
Yeah.
-This is a dinner.
-Yeah, sort of, I guess.
-I thought this was a party-party.
-This is a party-party.
-Hello. Hi.
-Hi. How are you?
-Good.
Hi.
Carolyn, this is my sister Caroline.
-Hi.
-Lovely to meet you.
-Yes, likewise.
-Her husband, Ed.
Hi. Thank you so much for having me.
-Of course.
-Happy birthday, Caroline.
Thank you, Sonia.
-Hey.
-Hi.
I'm gonna go make a quick adjustment.
Uh, would you grab her a drink?
-Absolutely.
-Excuse me.
-She likes white wine.
-Coming right up.
I'll be right back.
Anthony.
I'm so sorry.
John failed to mention
I was crashing a sit-down dinner.
Oh, it's fine, please.
He does that kind of thing all the time.
I-I just mean that he's forgetful,
not that he's bringing women unannounced.
He also didn't mention it's your birthday.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Oh. There's Ed with your wine.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
-You wanna drop your coat?
-Wait, what?
-I forgot my line. I had to improvise.
It's Glengarry Glen Ross.
You can't make shit up.
St. Davids put on
Joseph's Technicolor Dreamcoat every year,
and John had one line,
and he always went up and then
his voice cracked every time.
I did the production at Gravestone.
I played Joseph.
He-He's 73 going on 100.
He-he… I mean, they gotta get
a better candidate.
A legislator, not a visionary.
So funny. To this day, when people ask,
"Where'd you go to college?"
He says, "In Cambridge."
Yes, Caroline always used to say,
"Just outside of Boston."
Like it's not public record.
-Carolyn, where'd you go?
-Uh, BU.
Oh, you know what, Serena,
I just realized you went to Princeton.
So, you're shit out of luck, aren't you?
Well, okay, I am a proud Tiger,
though we both know
that it's not the same thing.
Anyway, say what you
were saying earlier about the lamb.
It's my mothers recipe.
Oh, yeah? Really?
-Did you ever cook?
-Me?
-Yeah.
-No.
What are you looking for?
Candles.
Ed was gonna go to the deli,
but I know they're here somewhere.
Are you mad at me or something?
Why would I be mad at you, John?
All right, you already don't like her.
I don't know her.
You didn't bother to tell me you were
bringing her, so allow me to catch up.
All right, well, that's not her fault.
I mean she understands
she wasn't expected here tonight.
Why would you put her in that position?
I really didn't think you would mind.
You say you're feeling older?
Wonderful. Act like it.
I'm assuming if you've brought her
here tonight, she's important to you?
She is. She's very important to me.
I'm really starting to feel like
she's my person.
Then act like she's your person.
-I love you.
-Love you.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Caroline ♪
Hey, Kelly.
Have you seen these drafts for…
What?
Nothing.
Oh, shit. Who told you?
Don't worry. Come sit.
No. Do people know?
I don't want people to know.
Hilarious.
The one woman who doesn't want to be
known as his girlfriend is his girlfriend.
Yeah, I-I don't want to be known
as someone's other half.
Neither do I. Trust me.
No, Kelly. I didn't mean it's a bad thing
to be a famous person's other half.
You and Calvin, you're-you're married.
You have a business together.
You're a team. We're…
I don't even know what we are yet.
Well, it's a good thing
you didn't start a few years ago.
I mean, he has to settle down soon
and get on with it.
John single at 40 is not a good look.
You've got good timing.
No, I'm not timing anything.
Oh, I know. You're not like that.
That's the beauty of it.
And he's such a good guy,
and he just keeps getting better.
Don't worry it to death.
Hey, if it all works out,
you're here for a couple more years
and then you get to be a Kennedy.
Could be a lot worse.
I just wanted you to know
how happy I am for you.
-But even more happy for him.
-Thanks.
But can you please not tell anyone?
Oh.
Please don't tell Calvin.
Oh, please. Unless something
directly affects Calvin, it doesn't exist.
Oh, um, will you come to the meeting at
3:00 today with the flagship architects?
-Three o'clock today?
-Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Don't tell anyone.
Okay.
-Hey, fellas.
-Hey, John.
-When the little hand...
-Oh, don't give me that.
-How you doing?
-Yeah.
-Has she showed up yet?
-I haven't seen her.
She did great last night, by the way.
Not sure I did.
I didn't exactly tell Caroline
I was bringing someone.
Oh, dude.
And forgot to mention to Carolyn
that it was Caroline's birthday.
Or that it was a dinner.
Oh, my God.
W-Well,
I guess you were just being you.
I love you, buddy,
but that is kind of classic you shit.
I don't think it works for her.
I don't think it really works
for me either anymore.
Yeah, she's the first woman
I've dated in years
who's not actively trying to marry me.
Either that or she's playing
some Kasparov-level chess.
Well, from what you've been telling me,
I don't think she's playing chess.
I-I-I think you just finally met someone
who's kinda…
Great,
who isn't interested in the bullshit
that follows in your wake.
Not all of it, at least.
-I just don't want to blow it, you know.
-Yeah.
I don't know, so maybe don't?
Yeah, you're always
full of great advice, buddy.
Thank you.
-You okay?
-Yeah, yeah.
Now, say hut.
Ready. Say hut.
Hey, who knows what time it is?
Uh, it's like 3:45.
-Good catch.
-Yeah, thanks.
-See you. Good game.
-Good game.
Hello.
Aye aye aye, sorry about football.
Kelly had me stay late for a meeting.
How was the game? Did you win?
-Yeah.
-Yay.
What's a girl gotta do to get
a scoop of Chardonnay around here?
It's in the fridge.
What is it? What's wrong?
Nothing. Just…
Thinking about how we met.
I'm just trying to remember.
It was Calvin's idea
to introduce us, yeah?
Why are you asking me this?
John, what's wrong?
You have to tell me right now.
You know, it'd have been fine
if you asked him to introduce us.
I didn't ask anyone to introduce us.
Then Calvin did.
Then you asked for my number.
Then I didn't give it to you.
Then you tracked me down in the showroom.
Okay, I'm not gonna stand here
and wait for you
to tell me whatever the fuck this is.
I'm gonna get my shit and leave.
Somebody left a letter in my bag.
It's a lot of stuff about you.
Like men you've dated,
drugs,
shady friends that you've got.
Things like… like you were trying
to meet me,
that you were fixated on me.
That you were asking everybody about me,
that you were trying to land me.
Where is it?
-Hold on, Carolyn. Wait...
-Shut up.
I've been driving myself crazy
trying to figure out what's between us…
Where this is going, how strong it is,
and this-this is…
This is how strong it is for you.
Someone writes these terrible things
-about me…
-Hold on.
…and some friend of yours shoves it
in your bag.
Suddenly everything
between us just disappears.
-Carolyn, hold on.
-That's all it takes.
-Carol... Carolyn.
-No, this is it.
That's all that's between us.
-Carolyn, just wait a second.
-Goodbye, John.
Carolyn.
Please, Carolyn. Where are you?
I'm sorry.
Carolyn, please, please call me back.
♪ Looking out the door, I see the rain ♪
♪ Fall upon the funeral mourners ♪
♪ Parading in a wake of sad relations ♪
♪ As their shoes fill up with water ♪
♪ Maybe I'm too young ♪
♪ To keep good love from going wrong ♪
Hello?
♪ But tonight you're on my mind ♪
Carolyn?
♪ So you never know ♪
♪ Broken down and hungry for your love ♪
♪ With no way to feed it ♪
So,
someone you were playing with?
I mean, I assume so. Yeah.
-We were in the middle of Central Park.
-Jesus Christ.
Of all the impulses you've indulged,
whether it's ice climbing
or diving for sunken treasure,
this might be the most thoughtless.
I mean, for someone who's
dragged through the rumor mill
on a daily basis,
you'd think you'd exercise
a little more discernment
before running to the woman
you claim to care about
with an anonymous letter
assassinating her character.
Yeah, I don't know
what I was thinking, all right?
It just fucked with my head.
If someone who claimed to be my friend
cravenly stuffed an anonymous note
into my bag,
I'd take a really hard look
at the company I'm keeping.
People give me a hard time
about being closed off and guarded,
but this is why, John.
My whole life, I've watched people
ingratiate themselves with Mom.
Calls for play dates with girls at school
I never even knew, drove me crazy.
I know you like to give people
the benefit of the doubt
because it makes you believe
that your life is normal,
but it isn't.
It's never been normal.
It never will be normal.
And if you let everyone in because
you're afraid of looking like a bad guy…
Then who does that leave room for?
So what are you saying I do?
Change my whole world?
Fire all my friends?
No. I mean, maybe I could help
make suggestions at a later date.
You were raised by judicious women.
You know who you can trust.
Yeah, I trust her. She's the only one
who doesn't want something from me.
Well, that's obviously not true.
Because if she cares about you,
she's going to have wants and needs.
They just shouldn't have anything
to do with your access or your notoriety.
No, she doesn't even want to talk to me.
I don't blame her.
Then try harder.
And if it doesn't work out,
then learn from it
and be better next time.
Just please, no more actresses.
They're way too high maintenance.
-I love you.
-Love you.
-How'd you get in here?
-The super let me in.
-I'm gonna get him fired.
-Please don't.
John, don't.
There's no coming back from that.
I'm an idiot.
You're not an idiot. You're just weak.
Yes. Yes, absolutely, I'm weak.
I have a weakness, a big one.
Don't.
The world gets out of my way.
It just winks and waves me through.
It gives me what I want
when I want it, mostly.
I enjoy the way the world treats me.
Who wouldn't?
But I know that deep down…
The way I live my life isn't real.
So when someone wrote that,
wrote that you were not real,
that you were
exactly what I was afraid of,
it made me doubt
my whole experience with you,
because my experience
is generally not trustworthy, you know.
I'm always trying to understand what
parts are real and what parts aren't.
But us…
That felt so, so real.
The whole world makes you look unreal.
But when it was just… just us,
just you and me, no world, that was…
You somehow seemed so much better than
the world's version, and then you didn't.
This, I don't wear this
because I love my father.
I wear this to remind me
that what he seemed to be, he wasn't.
And anyone else who seems as wonderful
as he did, they're…
They're probably not either.
I wear it to remind me to be careful,
and I am. I'm…
I'm… I'm too careful.
And I'm not careful enough.
Everything for me right now,
it's all question marks except for you.
You, this, this is where I begin
if you let me. I…
I love you.
I love you so much, Carolyn.
I never thought I could love someone
like this.
I couldn't until now.
Until you.
That's real.
This is real.
And I want to start right now.
I love you too.
I don't want to keep it a secret.
We'll get to that later.
♪ If you, if you could return ♪
♪ Don't let it burn, don't let it fade ♪
♪ I'm sure I'm not being rude
But it's just your attitude ♪
♪ It's tearing me apart
It's ruinin' everything ♪
♪ And I swore, I swore I would be true ♪
♪ And, honey, so did you ♪
♪ So why were you holding her hand? ♪
♪ Is that the way we stand? ♪
♪ Were you lyin' all the time?
Was it just a game to you? ♪
♪ But I'm in so deep ♪
♪ You know I'm such a fool for you ♪
Jesus.
♪ You got me wrapped around your finger ♪
♪ Do you have to let it linger? ♪
♪ Do you have to, do you have to ♪
♪ Oh, I thought the world of you ♪
♪ I thought nothing could go wrong ♪
♪ But I was wrong, I was wrong ♪
♪ If you, if you could get by ♪
♪ Trying not to lie ♪
♪ Things wouldn't be so confused ♪
♪ And I wouldn't feel so used ♪
♪ But you always really knew
I just wanna be with you ♪
♪ But I'm in so deep ♪
♪ You know I'm such a fool for you ♪
♪ You got me wrapped around your finger ♪
♪ Do you have to let it linger? ♪
♪ Do you have to, do you have to ♪