Previously on Next Level Chef...
From 24 chefs, only 15 of you
will make it into
that incredible draft.
Let's go, Home Chefs!
- Oh, my goodness!
- I want one of you to want me.
I did not get this far
to get this far.
Five professional chefs,
social media stars,
and home cooks.
You have earned your way
into that incredible draft!
Talk about adrenaline!
- And tonight...
- We're going to draft our teams!
♪ C'mon, Chef Ramsay
♪ Pick your boy
Good luck, Gordon!
You'll need it!
- Gotta go! Gotta go!
- Oh my God!
Platform!
No! No! No!
Wanna write 'em down
in your little book?
Oh, my goodness me.
"Does not take criticism well."
Hello!
- Good morning, chefs!
- Alright!
Let's go!
The butterflies
I'm experiencing are insane -
sort of like Hunger Games
without the death part.
- Are you guys ready to go?
- Yes, chef!
I am glad because
we are going to draft our teams!
The fact is,
we all know it's Team Blais
- that was victorious last year.
- Oh, Lord.
Chef Austin put us up
on the top level,
and I plan on keeping our team
up there all season long.
Listen, you best believe...
you guys...
I've been taking notes...
okay...
- ..on all of you!
- Yes!
- You have a notebook?
- I sure do
because I'm
putting together a team
that is going to absolutely
dominate all season long.
Nyesha's coming out fighting!
I looked at her notebook
and it says "How to beat Blais.
"Page one."
It's been a minute
since Team Arrington
has had a winner
with Pyet in Season 1,
but we're gonna take back
that crown.
I love the fact that you two are
super confident. You know that?
But there's only one
two-time winning mentor
standing in front of these
talented chefs. Yes!
And I intend taking it
to a three-time hat trick.
Right. Team Arrington
gets the first pick.
Nyesha, you're on the clock.
Where are you going?
Chef Arrington is a legend.
I would love to be
on Chef Arrington's team.
Come on! It's a match
made in heaven.
This is a very important
decision.
I'm looking for
a well-rounded team
who brings the best energy.
I've taken a lot of notes
on who would fit
on Team Arrington.
My first choice
is an easy one...
..and it's gonna be...
Danielle.
- Wow!
- Woo!
Did she say Danielle?!
The very first?!
I have never been no. 1 pick
for anything in my whole life!
- I will make you proud.
- I believe it.
Number one, baby!
I'm not shocked, but I am happy
'cos that means I get
the chef that I wanted
from the minute
they stepped into that kitchen.
I'm not looking for
a frontrunner.
I'm looking for someone
that I can help mentor
and get stronger.
The first member
of Team Ramsay...
Come on, Chef Ramsay!
Pick your boy! Pick your boy!
..is Gabrielle.
Welcome.
Woo!
Let's go!
Are you kidding me?
Chef Ramsay's first pick.
Thank you, chef.
We won't let you down.
- Welcome to Team Ramsay.
- That is un-freaking-real!
Listen I'm very excited
about this moment
'cos I get two
championship picks in a row.
Uh, my first pick though:
an absolute slam dunk.
To be honest, this chef had me
at first bite.
Team Blais's first pick is...
- ..Christian.
- Wow!
Let's go, Christian.
Let's go.
First bite.
- Bring the flavors. You ready?
- Yes, chef.
It's a Blais!
Oh, can't wait to get you
your first pickleball set!
Okay, so you might not see
my next pick coming here,
but after studying
the performances
here in the auditions
and maybe doing
a little online research
as well,
the next member
of Team Blais is...
..Tim.
Let's go, Tim.
Come on! Let's go.
- I'm ready for this.
- Startin' strong!
I see huge potential
in my next pick.
Andy! Come on!
I saw her
in your little black book.
- You did, clearly!
- I did! I did!
I gave that one to you!
The next member
of Team Arrington is...
- ..Connor.
- Wow!
LA on the map! Let's go!
For my third pick...
..Emerson.
Woo!
The next member
of Team Ramsay is...
- ..Cole. Welcome.
- Yes!
Welcome!
Go!
Back to back again.
Team Blais is going with...
Darian.
Let's go, Darian.
Bring it up front!
- I'ma make you a winner.
- Let's go.
We have this, like,
win-at-all costs vibe
so I'm going to go with someone
who knows competition
more than anyone else here.
I can't believe they're
still out here. Team Blais
- selects Jared. Let's go.
- Wow!
Let's go, Captain America!
The next member
to join Team Ramsay...
Say Amber!
I'm here!
..Amber! Let's go.
Woo!
Team Ramsay!
Oh my God!
You're pissed now, aren't you?
I clearly see
that you have a theme
going on here
with the badass women.
- Oh, yes.
- We love that but you guys
have left two chefs
that I've wanted from the start.
Machete!
Welcome to Team Arrington!
I love the flavor you bring.
I love the vibes you bring.
Eh!
Hell yeah!
Our final chef,
to round us out...
Mr. Matt!
Welcome to Team Arrington, sir.
Mareya and Elise,
honestly I can't believe
you two are still out there.
I'd gladly take both of you.
Tom Brady was picked
199th overall, and guess what?
He won seven championships.
I'm not worried.
Right. The final member
joining Team Ramsay...
Mareya, welcome.
Welcome. Let's go!
Elise, this played
right into our hands.
Join team Blais.
Hello, gentlemen!
That's fine.
Everyone can doubt you.
It doesn't matter because they
don't know what you can bring.
The teams are set.
Everybody excited?
Let's go, baby!
Now it's time
for your first
big important challenge.
I think we should have
a bit of a celebration.
- Yes!
- Or better yet, a fiesta...
Yes! Let's go!
..because, for your first
team challenge,
we are heading
south of the border...
- Let's go!
- ..with a Next Level taco party!
Let's talk about it!
Let's "taco" 'bout it!
Y'all want this smoke over here!
Taco time!
I know I got this, ma'am.
Five-time
Houston's best taco champion!
Right. Here's the good news:
you'll have 30 minutes to create
three identical
Next Level tacos.
Yes. We got this.
The chef that creates
the best tacos today
will keep their entire team
safe from elimination...
- Fire.
- ..and move your team
to the top level
next time round.
Sadly, the two losing teams
will each send a chef
into that dreaded cook-off where
one of you will be eliminated.
Don't let it be you.
- Right. You guys ready?
- Yes, chef! Let's go!
Okay, Team Blais?
I've been waiting to say this
this for a really long time.
- As reigning champions...
- Oh, Jesus!
..we will start
on the top level.
- Let's go!
- Head to the elevator.
I'll see you there soon.
Let's go, team!
The only way is down!
I can't wait to put this
blue apron on.
- Teamwork makes the dream work!
- ♪ Next Level Chef!
Team Blais, baby!
Alright!
Chef Blais assembled
the Avengers.
Assemble!
That's Captain America for ya!
We're blazin' blue:
the hottest part of the flame.
Feels so good
to be in this kitchen!
We're a team now!
The girl power,
you can taste it!
- The Gordon Girls!
Oh, my gosh!
It's like home sweet home.
I don't need that one no more!
This looks nice!
Let's go!
Team Arrington! Let's go!
Right. Come here.
I have three daughters,
and when I told them the news
that I've got an all-female
team, they were so excited!
Okay? So excited.
Alright, everyone?
How we doin', guys?
Let's do it! Let's go.
Bring it over here.
So this is a taco challenge, but
it's not a Mexican challenge.
This could be a taco from
New Orleans, a Chinese taco.
Like, whatever it is,
we're always thinking about
making the challenge ours.
"What do I do well?"
Alright, let's line it up
over here on the door.
Here it comes. When the light
goes green, it's go time.
-Alright, guys,
-Back-to-back champs this year.
Go!
Alright, here we go. Proteins.
Make sure you grab a protein.
The first thing I see
is flank steak. And I'm like,
I love a steak taco.
Of course I'm gonna pick that!
Alright, chili.
There's corn, salsa.
Oh my gosh! What kind of tongue
is that? I'm not touching that.
I'm like, "You know what?
That's going to the basement!"
Alright.
Chipotle in adobo. Tomato paste.
See that pork loin? Beautiful
fat cap. Grab that immediately.
Gochujang's right behind you.
Gochujang: it looks like gold
shining at me.
Alright, grab that.
Five seconds left.
There's garnish, citrus,
fresh herbs and citrus.
Right, if you can grab it,
you can get it.
Grab it or regret it!
Good luck, Gordon!
You'll need it!
Okay, let's go, ladies!
Let's go!
Right. Scallops there.
There's some goat scraps there.
The first thing I see
is a ribeye.
Let's go, baby!
I see some refried beans.
I see peanuts!
- Tripe. Mahi mahi.
- Ooh! Mahi mahi.
That is perfect.
Prime gold protein for tacos.
I have no idea what
they're doing upstairs,
but I'm happy they sent this
down me.
Five seconds, ladies.
Pepper? Good.
- Oh my goodness me!
- Holy crap!
Platform is on the move, guys.
Let's go!
Go, go, go!
Next Level taco!
Everybody's going down
the alleyway.
My ass goes around the table.
I see tongue.
Hell no!
Tripe? Disgusting.
Lo and behold - the cod.
I grab the cod.
The easy taco decision.
Cola? Why not?
Fifteen seconds, guys.
Let's go.
The platform
has been picked over.
- We got tripe.
- You want the tripe?!
The ingredients that are left
are straight garbage.
So I grab the beef tongue.
Grab it! Grab it! Grab it!
Back to your station.
Organize yourself.
This is not a good choice.
How do you elevate beef tongue?
And I tell myself all the time,
"Keep it simple, stupid."
And sometimes
I don't keep it simple.
Sometimes
I go towards the stupid side.
Alright, guys,
your 30 minutes starts
right now. Let's go!
MattDad! Welcome to
Team Arrington, buddy.
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
I saw it at the very beginning.
It's you and me.
I grabbed beef tongue.
I've been dreaming about beef
tongue - not wanting to get it -
but I dreamed about it,
so I was prepared for it.
- I love that.
- Beef tongue's not easy,
but I can make a bacon jam
that's kind of sweet,
salty, spicy,
so I'm making crispy beef tongue
tacos with bacon jam.
Delicious depth of flavor here.
You gotta get it cooking, okay?
Got it.
I'm on it.
Bro, look at
all this good stuff.
Machete! I mean,
the man for a taco challenge!
You know what I'm saying? The
kingpin! King Taco! Let's go!
- What you got?
- I got some cod over here.
I'ma do like
a nice cola-battered cod.
We don't need a beer batter.
I got Coca-Cola.
I got everything in there
I need for it!
Come on, baby.
Dang you, the basement!
- Connor, what you got?
- Let's go. I got goat.
Goat? Amazing. We love goat.
Reflective of
my captain right here!
'Cos it's the GOAT, baby!
- Emerson!
- Alright, I got
tripe taco so I'm
doing a birria...
Birria! Don't forget the sauce
on the side, okay?
Okay. And I'm going to make
a fresh salsa,
and then I'm going to make
a homemade, like, crema sauce.
Really smart.
Really, really creative.
- I love it.
- Thank you, chef.
In Filipino culture we eat tripe
with many of our dishes,
but you need to know
how to cook it,
get the right texture.
You gotta know how to season it.
Once you nail all of that,
tripe is beautiful.
Oh, this is tasting good, chef.
Five minutes gone, 25 to go.
- Mareya?
- I'm gonna do chicken thighs,
almost shawarma style.
How are you gonna cook
the chicken?
I'm gonna sear them and then
pop them in the oven, I think.
We're good,
we're good. You good, you good.
Right, protein-wise,
what did we get?
- Tiger prawns.
- Yes! Come on!
I love seafood tacos.
Everybody loves my tacos.
My whole family,
like, we love getting together
and just, like, serving it up.
Something from California.
Some great tacos there, right?
Southern California
has the best.
- What're you gonna do with this?
- Turn it into a glaze.
So I'm gonna cook the prawns
separately,
then finish with a glaze on top.
- You got lovely flavors here.
- Thank you.
Right, what did you grab?
Ribeye! Lovely.
I'm toasting my peanuts
right now
to make a rub,
just inspired by Cameroon.
I was born and raised
in Cameroon, West Africa.
Suya has this peanutty base
and then just that
little hint of spice.
It's the best!
Elise, how we doin' here?
We got a flank steak?
We do.
I'm gonna marinate this
in some buttermilk and
some traditional spices.
My kids have a tough time
chewing through
a lot of meat and protein,
and so I'm just going to
marinate my flank steak
in buttermilk.
It's a thing that I do
fairly often.
I know that my kids
would appreciate it.
So you're marinating it, um,
almost like a tandoori chicken?
I just want it tender. I want
it juicy. I want it delicious.
Let's start cooking that meat
and start working on the flavor.
Yes, got you.
Breathe! Everything is okay.
Twenty minutes remain.
Twenty minutes.
- Feelin' good, Christian?
- All good. So good.
You look good over there!
Okay, Christian,
what are we doing?
I'm doing a gochujang
sweet glazed grilled pork loin
and a really spicy
chili arbol salsa.
Just be mindful that we don't
have too much spice going on.
The gochujang and the chilies
- ..can be both spicy.
- Yes, chef.
I worked on a show called
Hot Kitchen.
I make spicy food good.
That's my thing!
Ooh yeah... Oh! Shoosh!
She's a spicy
No one goes home today.
Listen, mid-round drop! You
gotta go to the platform now!
I see a bunch of balls of dough.
I was like, "Wait,
do I not have to make
my own tortilla?" Amazing!
You got masa tortillas,
fresh made.
I saw the pink of the beet.
Love that color! Let's roll!
It was pretty.
Uh, ladies? You got to grab
a masa dough, now please.
You got charcoal flavor,
red corn here,
ancho chili flavor.
I'm just gonna play it safe
and go with the white corn masa.
I just don't have experience
working with dough.
Quick, quick, quick.
Seconds to go, guys.
Yeah, good color.
Alright, guys, we need
a tortilla to make a taco.
Grab a masa that makes sense
with your flavors.
Red corn masa.
- I'll take red corn.
- It's not staying!
The platform's going up...
..I reach my hand in there,
I grab the squid ink dough.
I have two... Oh. Okay.
This'll work!
Takin' a run!
- Hey, we unstoppable.
- We unstoppable!
We're halfway down, guys.
Make sure your tortillas
are not too thin.
Not pretty...
..we're gonna start over.
That's okay.
Boom!
How we doing over here?
Not great. We're struggling
with that thing.
- Struggling with the press?
- It's not working for me, yes.
I've just come off
from being last picked
and I'm just frustrated
with the dough.
You're a frickin mess!
It is extremely difficult
to get me angry,
and I am pissed
working with that tortilla.
It is just... a wreck!
Oh, come on!
So over it.
Alright, get it together, girl.
I'm not going home
over a frickin tortilla.
It's a Murphy's law situation.
Whatever can go wrong is
going wrong.
Oh no!
I'm running out of time.
Oh my gosh.
Ten minutes remain.
Yes, chef. Hey, what do you do
with your tortillas once done?
Yeah, you can throw 'em
in a towel. Let 'em wrap.
That one needs a little
more time. It's still raw.
Yes, chef.
Appreciate that.
Tim? Alright,
Texas has got to represent
- with the tortillas.
- You got it.
- You feeling okay?
- Feeling good!
Alright. Let's go, dude.
Come on. I've seen you online.
I watched you, dude.
I watched you.
- Just like on the IG, okay?
- That's right.
Get your pans on,
ready for your tortillas.
Do not wait too long.
I can't believe I'm cooking
for Chef Ramsay right now!
We're good.
You good, you good.
Everyone got
their tortillas, yes?
- Making mine now, chef.
- Uh, where's your...
- Do you need this water?
- No.
Not too thick on those, yeah?
It's good.
A touch thinner, alright?
- You got it, chef.
- This one's falling apart.
Corn tortillas break
really easily.
I only have one
that's not falling apart.
Ladies, we are not losing this.
- We're not losing, chef.
- We are not losing.
Six and a half minutes left!
No one goes home today.
- Darian, we're good?
- Yes, chef.
Pineapple salsa is already
working. Nice, dude. Nice.
So I'm making my jerk spice
right now.
- Okay.
- I'ma grind this up.
- Get some flavor going.
- Alright. Homemade jerk spice?
- Homemade jerk spice.
- Love the idea.
Put jerk on anything,
it's gonna be delicious.
You see a crocodile running by?
Let's put some jerk on
that thing. It's gonna be tasty!
- Christian, you're good?
- Yes. Chopping up protein, chef.
That's a thing I think
you can finish on that griddle.
There we go. There we go.
Thank you, chef.
Alright, Jared,
what do we got going on?
Here we got this ground brisket.
We got some hot sauce Tabasco.
- It's gonna be nice.
- So was this draft
very similar
to the, uh, NFL draft?!
Yeah! It did have that
same kind of high octane feel,
a little bit different though
when you have Gordon Ramsay
up there calling out your name.
But hey, you had my back
when it was O-line dinner so
I'm pumped to be on Team Blais.
Let's go, let's go, Jared!
Five minutes, guys!
Be smart, okay?
Heard, chef!
Ooh, that goat
smells crazy good.
- Machete?
- Yeah.
This is right
in your wheelhouse, huh?
- Oh, I love this.
- You started with $1 tacos
outside your dad's shop, right?
- Yeah, a mechanic shop too.
- I love that.
- You know what I mean?
- I do!
Now I feel like
I'm really back alley again!
- How we doing, MattDad?
- I, I feel good.
That's my, uh, beef tongue.
A little southwestern-type
seasoning.
- Delicious.
- Thank you, chef.
Dude, this knife sucks!
Oh my God!
Chef, you should try this tripe.
Oh, trust me, I will.
Delicious.
I don't even like tripe.
Delicious. Now you have to
bring it together.
Just over four minutes to go,
ladies, okay?
How's everybody feeling?
Y'all got this?
- Yes.
- Let's go!
Flavor town, flavor town.
Oh, it smells so good!
Cole, explain these
to me. So, they're...
- They are like a taco empanada.
- Empanada, yeah.
- And you've sealed them?
- Yes, chef.
- Yeah? Good.
- It won't be a traditional taco.
I didn't just
put my tortilla on the grill
and then stick my mahi mahi
in there.
I wanna make sure I stand out
on this very first challenge
that we have.
- Yeah, nice.
- Yes, chef.
Beautiful!
Two minutes left.
You plate now.
Do I have a protein?
Do I have a tortilla?
- Do I have some sort of sauce?
- Yes, chef.
Did I have time to make a little
garnish together?
- Yes, chef.
- No one misses the platform
on Team Blais ever.
No, chef.
Okay, what am I missing?
The platform will be here soon.
Platform's going past,
ladies. We hold our nerve.
Yeah, really beautiful.
Nicely seasoned.
- This is, like, falling apart.
- Don't worry. Don't worry.
The plating
just looks like garbage.
My tortillas are too big.
I don't have enough time
to redo them.
Oh, God!
You got it. You got it.
Deep breaths.
- Thirty seconds.
- Yes, chef.
Don't forget, you need time to
get on that platform, right?
- No missed platforms, right?
- No missed platforms.
Make it your competition to win.
Right?
- Heard.
- Platform's here!
Let's go!
The platform waits for no one.
Connor, let's go.
Matt? Matt!
- Let's go! Please.
- Heard, chef.
Emerson, let's go.
Stop!
You're done.
Get there, Matt!
Get there, Matt! Let's go!
Get it on the platform. Please
don't miss the platform. Now!
Get there!
Oh! No!
Agh! My God!
Damn it!
The platform
waits for no one. Let's go!
Emerson, you're done!
Please don't miss the platform.
Get on that platform!
Oh! No!
Agh! My God!
Damn. Damn it!
That was my fault, man.
That's my fault,
and no one else's fault.
And I... I let my team down.
It's alright. All good.
It's okay.
I had a damn good dish that...
..really would have...
brought us to the top.
Emerson? I hope you learned
a lesson: when I give you a time
and I give you a direction,
you have to listen to it.
I'm here to help you.
There you go.
Uh, ladies?
I need it on here now.
Platform, now. Let's go.
Get on the platform now!
It's gotta go.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Mareya, it's gotta go! Gotta go.
Andy, it's gotta go.
Gotta go!
Gotta go. Gotta go. Gotta go.
Well done.
Well done. Next?
Oh my
I'm hoping that, man,
those babies are
tucked in nicely to that holder,
and I'm praying
they didn't budge.
I want you to remember
you just started cooking too.
Look where you are.
- Look where you are.
- Yeah.
The platform is here, guys.
Gotta go now! NOW!
Now! NOW!
Darian, now!
Let's go. Timmy, now!
Jared, you gotta go, dude.
Finish all the way through...
Dude! Dude!
Let's go, let's go.
Team Blais!
- Chef, how you feelin'?
- I'm okay.
Good.
Look at these!
The fragrance is incredible.
Great job.
Right. Shall we, uh,
start in the basement?
- Yes, please. Definitely.
- Nyesha, please.
One, two, three, four. Did
someone fall off the platform?
Oh no, Emerson.
What happened?
I had it up there. I was
stretching myself as much as
I could. I'm not as tall
as Jared, and it fell.
I had it done.
It was done.
It should've just been
on that platform.
I'm kicking myself for it.
First up,
we have a crispy tongue taco.
This has a bacon jam salsa.
Delicious balance.
It's a basement ingredient.
Definitely brought to life.
Great effort.
The protein's cooked nicely.
The tortilla's just a touch
too thick for me.
Yeah, I mean, the tortilla sort
of falls apart as you eat it,
but this dish is all about this
delicious salsa that's in it,
giving me
sort of barbecue vibes.
Great job.
Next up, we have
a Cola-Battered Cod
with a cod skin chicharrón,
and a kimchi crema.
This is squid ink tortilla.
Love the idea
of that cola batter.
It's nice and sweet, crispy,
and I love the little pickling
with the ginger.
Delicious.
Safe to say, this is probably
not this chef's first taco.
The sauce is
super, super delicious.
The tortilla holds together.
It's really well done.
Next up,
we have Seared Goat Taco
served with a salsa macha
in a charcoal tortilla.
The goat is delicious.
I mean, it's super lean.
It's got the heat there
and it tastes so tender.
Lastly, we have
a Baja Style Scallop Taco
with a kale and mango salsa.
It's, uh, really, really tasty.
Really balanced.
Smart way of using a sort of
unwanted leaf in a taco.
Great job.
Shall we move
to the middle level?
Let's start off with
a Suya Cameroonian Style
Rubbed Ribeye.
I know this individual's
a little bit upset
'cos they nearly missed
the platform as well,
but it's a messy taco, right?
Not supposed to look pretty.
I have never had
a suya taco before,
and, um, I think
I'll be adding it
to a list of things
to try again.
Maybe I would have liked
to see the ribeye
chopped up on it,
but it's very tasty.
"Messy." But there, I...
I will take it!
Next up, um, the Spiced Snapper
with a cabbage slaw.
These are served
with blue corn tortillas.
The fish in here is cooked
beautifully. I love this,
especially with the slaw
and the salsa. Beautifully done.
The fish is
a little large for the tortilla
that it's in, and it's lacking
a little seasoning.
Next up is a mahi mahi
deep fried taco,
almost like a sort of empanada
with a saffron tortilla.
This is the type of dish
that I want to dive into -
the texture is so craveable,
I went in for a second bite.
I think the overall
presentation lacks a little bit.
Maybe I would've loved
a little bit more sauce,
but frying the tortilla
is super smart.
Right. Next up, it's a sort of
take on a Chicken Shwarma Taco,
tomatillo crema,
and a white corn tortilla.
- It's a little bit messy.
- Okay.
I am so devastated
because this is not
my best work.
This isn't even close.
Tacos should be easy to eat and
these are challenging to eat.
I think what this is missing
is a little bit more time
on the execution, and the
tortillas not being broken.
Last up, this is a Prawn Taco -
apple kohlrabi slaw
and ancho chili tortilla.
Mmm!
Wow. I really appreciate
the flavor
of the prawn and apple kohlrabi.
Classic pairing. Delicious.
They taste beautiful.
Alright, let's head
to the top floor.
- We'll start off right here.
- Oh, God.
This is a Buttermilk Marinated
Flank Steak Taco
with a habanero salsa
and a beet tortilla.
Yeah, it's a shame. I mean,
I've never marinated flank steak
in buttermilk. It doesn't
do it justice, if I'm honest.
Flank steak needs a hard sear
and a hard seasoning,
and the tortillas
are really thick
and they can't even fold
properly.
Um, I sort of had to cradle
mine, sadly,
to stop it from falling apart.
Next up, we have
a Chili Rubbed Tri-Tip
with a roasted chili salsa
and an achiote tortilla.
The smoky notes
that come off of the tortilla
play really nicely
with the salsa.
Uh, delicious, the tri-tip.
The texture inside these tacos
are beautiful.
It's a really good taco.
Okay, next up, we have
a Jerk Spiced Lobster Taco
with a pineapple salsa.
The lobster's cooked beautifully
but it's very, very, very spicy.
I love jerk spices,
uh, and it's my favorite way
to clear my sinuses!
Love the spice blend on this,
but this salsa...
put it in a jar and sell it.
It's seasoned so well.
Okay, so next up we have
a Grilled Gochujang Pork Taco...
- They look beautiful.
- ..with a chili salsa,
onion gremolata,
and a cactus tortilla.
I quite enjoy spicy food.
It is definitely very fiery...
..but delicious!
You're saying it's on fire?
I think the dish is fire!
They're eye-catching as well,
whoever put them together, so...
perfect taco.
Okay, lastly, we have
a Spicy Ground Brisket Taco
with a little queso fresco
and a nice pico de gallo salsa.
This reminds me a lot
of my mom's cooking.
- This is probably good.
- She was not a very good cook...
- Oh no.
- ..but she brought it
on Taco Tuesday.
She saved it for Tuesdays.
Thank goodness. That was quite,
uh... up and down there!
Excuse us.
Thank you.
Thank you, chefs.
- We got this.
- Yeah.
What a shame that one missed -
Emerson.
Oh! The most unfortunate
circumstances to happen.
That's unfortunate 'cos
just even from the auditions,
he knows how to cook
and he's wearing the dish...
What's that on his back?
- It's the delicious consommé.
- Wow.
I just feel really bad.
The one that
I don't want again though
is the taco shwarma-shwarma-raco
taco, like.
- Yeah, a bit messy.
- Those two were overfilled.
The red snapper was just
a little bit too clumsy.
It was challenging to eat.
The Buttermilk Marinated
Flank Steak with the beet...
..it was bland.
I really liked
the Cola Battered Cod.
Same. Really inventive.
I'm amazed that cod ended
in the basement, by the way.
- Yeah.
- I think the tiger prawn...
- ..from my floor was the best.
- It was lacking some salsa.
Oh my goodness!
It's not a salsa competition!
It tasted like a spring roll and
needed a little dipping sauce.
Oh my goodness me!
Your best? Outstanding taco?
Oh, I mean...
spoiled for choice.
- There was a lot of good...
- Oh, my!
The pork loin might have been
the most beautiful.
- Stunning.
- It's one of the better
dishes upstairs.
A lot of great dishes there.
But it's the first challenge,
and already you're starting out
as if all your tacos
are delicious? Come on!
I'm not, no.
How great was that salsa?
If it was a salsa competition...
- It's not a salsa competition!
- You're agreeing with me?
- I'm just sharing my notes but...
- Yeah, we're allowed to.
I know. You write 'em down
in your little book.
I did. Trust me. I'ma write
some notes about you too.
- Oh, my...
- Blais is gonna bat
for whoever they don't like.
I can feel it.
- "Does not take criticism well."
- ..Take criticism. Wow.
Back there,
we all fight for our teams,
but we also fight
for the best dish of the day.
Richard, Nyesha and myself
have come to a consensus.
The winning taco of the day...
..earning safety
for their team and the right
to cook in that top-level
kitchen next time round,
was cooked by...
Christian!
Congratulations.
- Let's go, Christian!
- Go, baby!
- Team Blais.
- Great job!
Top dish, first round?!
Are you kidding me?
Wow.
- All of you are safe.
- Nice job, Team Blais.
Head back to the lounge,
and we'll see you
really, really soon. Enjoy it.
I am so fortunate
that Christian saved me today.
I mean, I owe him, like, a
margarita or something!
- What?!
Good job.
Thank you, Christian!
Eh! Thank you, guys.
Gordon and Nyesha,
you each must choose
one member from your team
to head into
the elimination cook-off.
Emerson, I would love to give
my fellow mentors
an opportunity
to taste your magic
so you will be going into
the elimination this evening.
The person I'm sending
into elimination is...
- ..Mareya.
- Yes, chef.
Get yourself back to Team Ramsay
quickly, please.
Okay.
Mareya, Emerson...
..for your elimination cook-off,
we'll be staying
south of the border
as you get ready
to create one of Mexico's
most iconic and adored dishes.
Mole.
Okay!
I've never seen the fear of God
in someone's eyes.
Emerson went...
I've never cooked a mole
in my life!
I don't even know
what's in a mole.
- Let's go, Emerson!
- Good luck.
- Mareya, you can do this!
- Emerson?
Bring the energy, right?
Mole!
Let's go.
I'm gonna have to lean
on my team.
- Breathe, baby!
- I ain't going home!
You got it, Mareya!
She's in the zone.
When I'm... locked in,
I'm laser-focused.
Emerson's super talented
but it's a boxing match
right now,
and I'm going all the rounds.
- Okay, everyone. We doing good?
- Yes, chef.
Emerson? Mareya? Line up
with your teams over there.
- We got you.
- Okay, listen, you have one
last chance to save yourselves
in this competition.
Thirty minutes to create
a Next Level mole entrée.
- Yes, chef.
- Listen, here's the thing:
make sure you have your proteins
and everything else you need
to build this dish
because, listen, we're gonna
make it a little bit tougher.
The platform is not staying
this season.
Grab it or regret it.
It's already freaking hard
to make a mole in 30 minutes
and they're like, "Well, we're
gonna make it harder." Really?!
Here it comes. When the
light is green, it's Go time.
Go!
- You got chicken.
- You got it! You got it!
Alright.
There's pork up here, Mareya.
Way to go!
All sorts of dried chilies.
- Chili! Chili!
- Okay, chipotle and adobo.
Raisins are up here.
Chocolate is up here.
Damn!
That platform isn't staying.
I miss those key ingredients on
the grab, there goes the mole.
- Make sure you get chocolate!
- There's guajillo in the back!
- Dates!
- Plantain! Peanut butter!
- Lime! Lime! Grab a lime!
- Tortillas!
Okay, if you can grab it, it's
yours. Grab it or regret it.
Okay, back to your station.
Your 30 minutes starts now.
Oh my God!
Okay. Traditionally,
any mole starts
with toasting some chilies.
What kind of dish
are you gonna make, Emerson?
I'm going to do like a chicken,
uh... pollo asada.
Like, a dark mole? You got some
sweetness to balance it out?
- Yes, chef.
- You got some dates over here,
and those plantains will have to
really thicken this up.
I like this.
You got your onions charring,
garlic, toasty almonds.
Right?
- Ooh! Okay, alright!
- Alright! Let's see some flavor!
That's looking good.
So this is what type of mole?
Do you have something for
sweetness? Yes, you've molasses
- Yeah I'm gonna grab spices too.
- Okay, I like that. I like that.
- Calm and collected, girl.
- Love it!
Get that chicken on that pan!
The skin side down.
Corn is the most important key,
it's that element of yellow
that's gonna pop
in that brown dish.
20 minutes remain.
You have your mole base.
We're gonna get that mixture
to our blender.
Nice! You got this, girl.
That looks great.
- Beautiful.
- Gorgeous color.
- No more chili! No more chili!
- No más!
You're okay with all the seeds
of the chilies being in there?
- Yes, we want it a little spicy.
- Listen to chef.
- Yeah, listen to Blais.
- Will do. Will do. Will do.
My team is screaming at me.
I will pull the stems out.
I'm starting to panic.
I really screwed up
'cos I missed the platform.
Woo!
I don't want to be
the first one to go home.
You got this, Mareya!
Watch that pork, girl.
Get it in that skillet!
Get it in that skillet.
Wide pan. Yes, that's
looking beautiful, my boy.
That's what I'm talkin' 'bout.
- Looks good.
- It's glossy.
Hers looks great too!
I mean, man...
- Check your chicken.
- Oven! Oven! Oven!
There you go. There you go.
Looks good. Looks good.
Halfway through. Mareya?
Emerson? Halfway through.
Love the tasting, Mareya.
I'm feeling good.
I am leaning into
the flavors of my heritage.
Trust your instincts!
My game plan is...
just focus on
flavor, flavor, flavor.
Mmm!
Yesss!
- That's good!
- That's a lot. That's a lot.
No more. No more sugar!
No more sugar.
What is going on?!
A knife! A clean knife!
A clean knife?
We got his back,
but he looks so overwhelmed.
- Corn! Corn!
- Emmerson, your corn!
Oh my God!
My dawg is in trouble.
What's up, Emerson? You're
giving me nervous energy here.
Oh my gosh.
- Woo! Hot!
- Okay. Deep breaths.
It is so important to get this
mole right, or else I'm gone.
I gotta look this way.
I can't look right now.
- Emerson, breathe. You got this.
- We got you. We got you.
I'm feeling all the pressure,
but I got my team behind me...
Good job. Good job.
..and my wife and my kids know
me as a fighter.
- I'm gonna...
- Up to you. Do riblets maybe?
I ain't givin' up.
I owe it to them.
Alright. Two minutes.
You can plate now if you want.
Two minutes left.
Mole on top!
Mole on top, Emerson.
Yeah, coat it.
Don't be shy with it.
It's a mole challenge, right?
Gorgeous. Gorgeous!
It's looking beautiful.
I like that.
Ooh!
- Nice!
- Beautiful! Beautiful.
What?!
- No! No!
- No way!
That's number two
in two different ways!
- Do you like the way that looks?
- No.
- Okay. Do you need a new plate?
- Uh... the blue one.
Blue, yes!
I love it. Way to pivot.
Switching plate, okay.
Good, good, good. Good call.
Gorgeous. Gorgeous.
You got this, girl!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Stop cooking.
- Nyesha. Gordon.
- How was that?
Oh my gosh. You know
how hard it is to make a mole...
- Yeah.
- ..and both competitors
absolutely threw down.
Okay, so first dish
is a chicken leg with
ancho and pasilla chili mole.
Shall we?
Could do with
a touch more seasoning.
Um... but overall, it's good.
Very good.
Chicken's cooked beautifully,
by the way, whoever cooked that.
Well, this mole, for me,
it's leaning
a bit on the sweet side...
..which I love.
The depth of flavor
and the smokiness achieved
is quite a feat.
Next up,
we have a seared pork loin,
and this is with a
mulato and chipotle mole sauce.
That mole is nice.
There's a lovely vibrancy,
but a lot of spice in this one.
If anything,
it needs to be cooked out more.
Pork is a little bit overcooked
I got to say, in 30 minutes,
tons of depth of flavor.
Alright. Two Next Level moles,
but we have to eliminate one.
Gordon, I'm going to start
with you -
which dish
will you be eliminating tonight?
The dish I'm eliminating...
I'm going to eliminate the pork.
Okay, Nyesha, same question.
Tough choice.
The mole that
I will be eliminating...
..is...
..the pork.
- That was cooked by Mareya.
- Oh my gosh.
Damn.
Damn, damn, damn.
You know... the short time we
got to know you...
you're clearly talented.
You've done yourself proud,
your family proud,
and uh... I'm proud of you.
It's been a pleasure
being on your team.
- Likewise. I wish it was longer.
- Short time.
I wish it was longer.
Please say goodbye
to your teammates and head
to the elevator. Thank you.
Good job, Mareya.
Damn.
I cooked my heart out today,
and I have no regrets.
It's...
something I'll never forget.
Emerson,
get your timings right, okay?
That platform,
it waits for nobody.
I'm still here.
I ain't goin' nowhere!
Get some rest, all of you.
Because when we see you
next time,
the one thing
that none of you can afford
is a breakdown in communication.
- Thank you, chefs.
- That was a clue.
- Good night, guys.
- Clean that jacket.
Send the tacos on the platform.
Don't wear them.
Next time on Next Level Chef.
You're about to see some things
I've never seen in my career.
There are monsters
on this platform.
- Oh my God!
- I have trouble with proteins
that still have
their heads on them.
He was moving
like a samurai in there.
- Here we go, Team Blais!
- Pipe down! Pipe down!
- Somebody's mad over there.
- Best dish of the day.
We have three mentors,
and my choice is the other dish.
They fightin' back there.
Is he gonna be
like this all season?